<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Aggressive Inline (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Aggressive Inline</name>
		<desc>Combine the many tricks and styles of the extreme sport, inline skating, with a Tony Hawk style system, complete with objectives and huge arenas, and you have Aggressive Inline.

Progress through the career mode, where you must complete objectives (such as grind a certain object(s) to jump over large gaps and gain points) to open up further arenas, which there are 7 in all, and once you are bored with them, you can make your own in the park editor. The game doesn't use a hard time limit but the so-called "juice meter": it fills up when performing stunts and if it gets empty, the level ends. During the game, you level up your character in seven stats, e.g. speed and grinds. The game uses a "learning by doing" approach to this, meaning that the stat improves if you perform the associated actions often enough. There are also five hidden keys in each level that open up new areas within the level.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animal Crossing (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing</name>
		<desc>Occasionally strange but completely addictive, Nintendo's Animal Crossing for the GameCube is not so much a game as a simulation of life on a small town. Players begin the game by setting out to live life on their own in a colorful town, where they are greeted by a seemingly endless supply of things to do and characters to meet.Time passes in Animal Crossing in real-time, as the month, day, season, and time of day matches that of the player's. Holiday seasons come and go in Animal Crossing, just as they would in the real world. Experience the freedom to fish, decorate your house, go bug catching, garden, write letters, and even play original Nintendo NES games in this imaginative, and addictive game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos : Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean</name>
		<desc>The existence of Earth, a planet of continents surrounded by deep oceans, has long become a mere legend. People live now on islands that are floating high in the skies. They also have wings - "Wings of the Hearts" - growing on their backs. Kalas is a young man who was born only with one wing - he replaces the second with an artificial wing manufactured by great masters. He is on a quest to find the murderers of his grandfather and his brother. He meets a girl named Xelha, who is out to stop an evil conspiracy that threatens the country, and they join forces against the newly appeared evil.

In this game, you don't only control Kalas and his party, but also play the role of Kalas' Guardian Spirit. From time to time Kalas will pose questions to you and ask for advice. Your answers will determine Kalas' general disposition and also his behavior in battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Baten Kaitos Origins (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos Origins</name>
		<desc>Baten Kaitos Origins is a prequel to Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean. Long ago, the evil god Malpercio attempted to destroy the other gods; a large battle of the gods ensued, and following this the people of the world were forced to flee to various islands floating in the sky. 1000 years after the war the people live peacefully in the sky for the most part; but Emperor Olgen, the emperor of one of these islands, has begun a plot to gain control of all the islands.

The main character of the story is Sagi, a "Spirit-born" individual who has been given a secret mission to assassinate Emperor Olgen. In similar fashion to Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean, you don't actually control Sagi in the game but rather his guardian spirit. Throughout the game you can give Sagi advice, and as you progress the story will unfold revealing the plot that may threaten all of the islands...</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battalion Wars (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Battalion Wars</name>
		<desc>You play in a fictional world, where war has erupted between the Frontiers and the Tundrans.  You are ordered to command the Frontiers to victory.  Using your troops you can command them to attack, defend, and follow you, as well as garrison them in bunkers, capture bases, and hop in vehicles.  You can switch between a first-person view, and control one of your men to lead in battle, or you can use the top-down view, where you have a good view of the battlefield.  Through an expansive campaign, a number of different nations, and a garrison that would impress even Napoleon, you can see just how fun war may be.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kuju Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA) (En,Es).rvz</path>
		<name>Beyond Good &amp; Evil</name>
		<desc>In the future, on the planet Hillys, the population suffers from constant attacks from the alien DomZ. The situation is gradually getting worse, as the rate of DomZ kidnapings increase. The Alpha Section forces, who are in charge of protecting citizens, seem to be completely ineffective, not even fighting the DomZ. In the midst of this situation, the secretive organization IRIS alleges that the Alpha Section is involved in a massive government conspiracy, and seeks to expose the truth through journalism.

You control the young reporter/photographer Jade, with her companions Pey'j and Double H. After experiencing first-hand a DomZ attack, she is contacted by IRIS, who recruit her as an action reporter. Jade is now tasked with infiltrating the Alpha Section, exposing the government conspiracy, and ultimately finding the truth for herself.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg</name>
		<desc>A boy and his friends playing in the forest get transported to a magical land. Separated from his friends billy finds...a chicken suit? This suit lets him hatch eggs in his quest to bring back morning, save the giant egg, and defeat the evil crows who want to destroy it. On the way he can hatch eggs that he finds when he does he is rewarded with mystical creatures and ''hats''. These help him defeat the crows and save the giant egg.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar : Primal Fury</name>
		<desc>A spin-off title in the series, Primal Fury adds new characters, arenas and special attack moves for each returning character from BR3. Improvements are also made in graphical lighting and textures.

The same control style and gameplay seen in the original three Bloody Roar titles is here, where at a touch of a button your character can morph into beasts of increased strength and ability during play. Smash through breakable arenas and perform devastating combo attacks to defeat the enemy or a friend in two-player mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Generation (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Bomberman Generation</name>
		<desc>Bomberman returns with a new cel-shaded 3D look. The same storyline applies, however. Bomberman has been given the task of taking back a powerful element of magic, and protecting it from the hands of evil. To do so, he must use his bombing abilites to blast his way through mazes filled with crazy enemies and hidden secrets. There are 5 worlds in all, each with 16 levels to complete. And after completing cetain objectives and picking up items, Bomberman will learn new techniques and abilities to improve his range with his bombs or use new weapons.

Also included is a 4 player classic bomberman multi-player modes. Unlike the adventure mode, all of the multi-player modes are set in the original 2D, top down style perspective. The last man standing wins in most rounds, with the added twist of other enemies on screen and timed battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal </developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO</name>
		<desc>A fighting game featuring characters from various Capcom and SNK games. Enhancing the main gameplay feature of Capcom vs. SNK, "Grooves", sets of gameplay mechanics from Capcom or SNK games selectable before battles, have now been made more granular. Compared to the previous two, there are six grooves in total, three for each company, plus Groove Edit Mode, where the player may define a custom groove.

In the Japanese GameCube and Xbox releases, the "EO" acronym means "Easy Operation"; in the European releases it means "Extreme Offence". Both refer to EO mode, an optional easy-mode added in this edition, which causes right analog-stick directions to instantly execute moves that usually require a series of inputs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos Field (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Chaos Field</name>
		<desc>Chaos Field is a top-down space shooter similar in concept to the Gradius series, or Ikaruga. You control one of three ships, each with their own pilot and unique weapon systems. 

The game takes place over 5 phases, in each phase you face a number of boss battles. Unlike other games if this genre, almost the entire game is composed of boss battles, each boss requiring a different strategy to defeat. 

The game also uses a unique in-game difficulty adjuster. Called "fields", you can play in either Order or Chaos. Compared to Order, the Chaos Field offers you increased fire power and abilities, but also does the same for your enemies. Order Field is more relaxed on both sides. If you can play in the Chaos Field, you stand to gain substantially more points.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>O3 Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure!</name>
		<desc>Gamers take control of the Chibi Robo, a pint-sized machine designed specifically to take care of a family's house. The robot needs to keep the house "happy." To do that, Chibi must walk around the home and clean it up, interact with other machines and people, and even -- according to the storyline - stop a group of bumbling thieves from making off with precious valuables. An electricity counter located in the bottom-right corner of the screen constantly counts down. When Chibi is getting low, players will want to recharge. The game features a day and night system, where days last about 10 minutes and nights the same. The environments slightly change depending on the time of day. For instance, a character not available in the day might be sleeping on the couch at night, and robots normally roaming the level in the afternoon might be gone in the evening.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skip</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jungle Beat (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jungle Beat</name>
		<desc>After the Donkey Konga games, Nintendo thought of a novelty use for the DK Bongos device. In Jungle Beat, you still have to match the rhythm by hitting the bongos timely, but the visual presentation is a platformer, much like a regular Donkey Kong game. You control Donkey Kong by hitting the left or right bongos while tapping both drums together or clapping allows for jumps, vine-swinging, wall-kicks, ground-pounding, and other moves.

You have to cross 40 areas to rid the island of evil kongs. During your journey, you can travel using a variety of animals, and they each need a certain rhythm to control. Aside from the input device, it is a regular platformer with power-ups, bananas to collect, many enemies, and end bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doshin the Giant (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).rvz</path>
		<name>Doshin The Giant</name>
		<desc>Doshin the Giant is a game where you are god. You are the incarnation of the sun Doshin! As Doshin you may wander Barodu Island in helping you island native worshipers by bringing them trees altering land and, fending off disasters and marauding monsters. The more you help the larger you grow... However it's not easy always being so nice... 

With the touch of a button you become the feared Jyashin! Jyashin a winged red  Doshin, only wish is to destroy. Using fireballs and his great strength level whole civilizations to feed of the islanders hate and grow larger.By no means is the object of the game just to grow, you know that the villagers must build 16 monuments in your honor... However you know that when this happens a horrible fate will meet the island. Will you chose to forever serve or torment the populace or will you help build the monuments that you know must be built?
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Param</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eternal Darkness - Sanity's Requiem (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Eternal Darkness : Sanity's Requiem</name>
		<desc>Eternal Darkness: Sanity's Requiem is a psychological thriller epic starring the adventures of twelve characters that span across the world and two millennia. From time immemorial the forces of evil from beyond have been trying to manifest themselves in our world, and it is only through the actions of these forgotten heroes that the world has been saved from being overrun. Chapters take place in Ancient Rome, Persia, the Middle East, and modern-day Rhode Island. Throughout the game, the protagonists will have access to several weapons appropriate for their era, from bastard sword and gladius to flintlock pistol and shotgun.

The game features an involved Magick system, which allows different spells to be created through the combination of runes. These spells can attack enemies, dispel illusions, and heal both the body and items.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon Knights</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evolution Worlds (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Evolution Worlds</name>
		<desc>Evolution Worlds is a re-release of two games:

Evolution: The World of Sacred Device
Evolution 2: Far off Promise
The first game underwent a significant reduction. Most dungeon areas from the original release have been removed. Some cutscenes are omitted as well, while the remaining ones have been expanded. Voice acting was added to the dialogues. The second game has no major changes compared to the original version.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ubi Soft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero GX (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>F-Zero GX</name>
		<desc>The classic Nintendo franchise that has inspired countless futuristic racing games returns with F-Zero GX on the Nintendo GameCube. Long-time rival Sega collaborated with Nintendo to redefine the futuristic racing genre with intense competition, blazing speeds, and brilliant track designs. F-Zero GX offers 20 different tracks and over 30 unique pilots, as well as a custom craft editor where players can create their own vehicle. Multiple game modes including Grand Prix, Time Attack, Versus mode, and the all new challenging story mode offer a multitude of alternatives to traditional racing. Players can laso save their game data on a memory card and use it to race custom vehicles in the arcade version of F-Zero GX.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles (USA).ciso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Square's first game for a Nintendo console since the days of the Super NES takes the lush fantasy world from the Final Fantasy franchise and adds in hack-and-slash-style four-player action. The game does away with traditional experience points and instead focuses on action-oriented combat with a unique co-op slant. Up to three friends can join in on the quest, by using Game Boy Advance units connected to the GameCube as controllers. While all the main action takes place on the screen, the GBAs enable the players to access menus, organize their spell spheres, and perform upgrades without slowing down the action.The initial release of this game included a GBA Cable to allow players instant access to the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Designer's</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Path of Radiance (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem : Path of Radiance</name>
		<desc>First console installment of the strategy-RPG series since the SNES days. Previously released on Famicom (Japan-only), Super Famicom (Japan-only), and Game Boy Advance, Fire Emblem leaves the 2D overhead maps of old behind to serve up 3D villages, fields, and caves, and polygonal battle sequences. The continent of Tellius is divided into humans and half-man/half-beast demi-humans. These two races have battled for centuries and only recently established an uneasy peace. Now, a new force threatens to tear apart the seven kingdoms and reignite the flames of war. Joining the Fire Emblem ranks are new units, such as such as the shape-shifting laguz who transform into beasts to attack their foes. Additionally, characters can now learn unique skills as they gain experience, giving players even more ways to customize their strategy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Tactical RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Geist (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Geist</name>
		<desc>John Raimi is assigned to infiltrate the Volks Corporation in Southern France. This corporation specializes in weapons but has been conducting bizarre experiments. John becomes a part of one of those experiments, and his spirit is separated from his body. As a ghost, he must possess other beings to find out what happened to his body. John has to find his body before it perishes.

Players start the game as John Raimi in human form. The game plays as though it is a regular first-person shooter. Players in human form can strafe, aim, run, and shoot enemies. In spirit form, they must possess people or animals to keep from being pulled into the afterlife; they can also drain the life from plants. To possess a being, first players have to frighten it. Players achieve this by possessing objects in the environment and making them do strange things.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Godzilla - Destroy All Monsters Melee (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Godzilla : Destroy all Monsters Melee</name>
		<desc>Legendary monsters battle among Earth's cities to determine the planet's fate. In Godzilla: Destroy All Monsters Melee, you can play as Godzilla or any of his longtime rivals as they fight hand-to-hand, at close range, and with special moves. Each massive beast has different physical attributes and special projectile weapons. You'll fight in cities such as Tokyo and San Francisco--all featuring real building destruction and physics. For multiplayer fighting mayhem, you can bring three of your friends into the battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pipeworks Software</developer>
		<publisher>Atari SA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gotcha Force (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Gotcha Force</name>
		<desc>In Gotcha Force, up to 4 players can use robots to unleash powerful attacks and projectile weapons along with jumping and sidestepping your opponent's attacks. Winning battles gets you new parts to upgrade your robot or trade them for better parts.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Gun</name>
		<desc>Experience the brutality, lawlessness, greed, and lust, that was the West. When life robs Colton White of all that matters, the only thing left he can trust is his GUN. From award-winning developer, Neversoft, and accomplished screenwriter, Randall Jahnson (The Mask of Zorro, The Doors), GUN follows Colton on his quest for discovery as he seeks to exact vengeful justice on those who have wronged him. GUN is a realistic epic action/adventure that lets gamers experience the brutality of the lawless West.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon - A Wonderful Life (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon : A Wonderful Life</name>
		<desc>The latest in the Harvest Moon series, a Wonderful Life pits gamers in a real-life simulation that spans the equivalent of 30 years. As you blossom from a young man into a mature adult you will be able to date, get married, and have a child that will eventually become a huge part of your life. For instance, you might have a boy who will grow to work side-by-side with you helping to farm your crops. So, having a child will have a huge affect on your life. The third-person roleplaying simulation features more than 40 characters to interact with as well as Game Boy Advance link-up.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon - Magical Melody (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon : Magical Melody</name>
		<desc>The Harvest Goddess has turned to stone and the Harvest Sprites need your help to bring her back. You need to collect Musical Notes throughout the game in hopes of restoring her to her former self. There are 100 Musical Notes in the game and to collect the notes you must do a variety of different things, some more challenging than others. Such as shipping a certain number of items, winning a festival or making friends with the wild animals found around your farm. Only by collecting a certain number of notes will the Harvest Goddess come back!Harvest Moon: Magical Melody is filled with features that Harvest Moon fans have come to expect in a Harvest Moon title ? plenty of crops, a variety of animals to care for, tons of festivals to participate in and loads of events to create a fun and entertaining game play experience.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hitman 2 - Silent Assassin (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Hitman 2 : Silent Assassin</name>
		<desc>The sequel to Hitman forces a retired assassin back into action by treason. Visit the dark recesses of the world corrupted by crime, greed, degradation, and dishonor. Your contracts will take you to exotic locations around the globe including Sicily, St. Petersburg, Japan, Malaysia, and India. A diverse arsenal of equipment, from armor-piercing rifles and explosives to chloroform and poison darts, are at your disposal. Stalk and eliminate your targets up close and personal, in either first- or third-person perspectives. You must decide whether to use stealth or aggression, but be careful--you'll have to deal with the consequences.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>IO Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hunter - The Reckoning (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Hunter : The Reckoning</name>
		<desc>Played from a third person perspective, Hunter immerses players in the nightmarish setting of Ashcroft, a town plagued by creatures of the night. Throughout the game's many gothic environments, players will face over 30 creature variants from bloodthirsty vampires to unstoppable legions of the walking dead. Hunter has already garnered stellar reviews and has been called a spiritual successor to games like Smash TV and the Gauntlet series, with the ability for up to four players to play cooperatively on the same screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikaruga (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Ikaruga</name>
		<desc>Battle fiercely, move swiftly, and act cleverly in a space crusade of intense firepower and hypnotic beauty. Take control of the ship Ikaruga--alter your energy field, evade epic maelstroms of fire, and terminate enemies with a devastating arsenal--all to protect an aging, exiled people. Battle the evil Horai by yourself or with a friend. This combination of manga-style storytelling and exciting arcade heroics challenges you to find the calm amid the chaos.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Atari SA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killer7 (USA) (Rev 1).m3u</path>
		<name>Killer7</name>
		<desc>Directed by Suda 51 of Capcom's Production Studio 4, Killer 7 features some of the most mature themes in a videogame to date. Players take control of the wheelchair bound assassin Harman Smith, a man who can conjure up in physical form the seven deadly personalities that exist in his mind. When a terrorist group known as Heaven's Smile threatens the safety of the United States, the government enlists Smith and his assassins to find and kill the man behind the organization.Killer 7 features extremely stylized cel-shaded graphics and over-the-top gore. Gameplay is a mix of third-person-based exploration and first-person view gun fights.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grasshopper Manufacture</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Air Ride (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Kirby Air Ride</name>
		<desc>Prepare for fast and furious racing action as Kirby hits Warpstar speed. Use simple controls to race and battle your friends in one of three hectic game modes. In Air Ride mode, you'll race to the finish line against your friends or computer-controlled competition. Top Ride mode lets up to four players race to the finish line using wild items like buzz saws, drills, and freeze fans to pester the competition. In City Trial mode, you'll race around a gigantic fantasy city in a quest to build the ideal machine to use in a random challenge that occurs after a set time limit. Don't let Kirby's cuteness fool you--Kirby Air Ride is crawling with tough challenges suitable for players of all ages.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kururin Squash! (Japan).rvz</path>
		<name>Kururin Squash!</name>
		<desc>After two adventures on the Game Boy Advance, Kururin goes 3D on the GameCube. In Kururin Squash!, you have to direct Kururin in his helicopter-like Heririn spinning stick through narrow mazes, while avoiding obstacles or courses' sides. The gameplay is spiced up with colourful backgrounds, bizarre enemies,  weapons and bounce pads that change the spin direction. When you get hit three times, the Heririn shatters.

The GameCube version introduces water levels with a submarine, guns, boxing gloves, twisters, flame-throwing and boss battles. In the main puzzle mode, you have to collect loot and in the race mode, you have to finish the mazes within a target time. Multiplayer includes four-player split-screen frenzy and a battle mode where you have to collect coins while using the weapons to hold off your opponents.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Collector's Edition (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Collector's Edition</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: Collector's Edition is a compilation of several installments from The Legend of Zelda series. It features both games released for the NES and Nintendo 64, with the former including revised texts fixing the original mistranslations, a demo of The Wind Waker, and various promotional videos.
Full games: The Legend of Zelda / The Adventure of Link / Ocarina of Time / Majora's Mask Extras: 20-minute playable demo of The Wind Waker, including scenarios for a dungeon, stealth, and an island / The Legend of Zelda retrospective / The Wind Waker special movie</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Four Swords Adventures (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Four Swords Adventures</name>
		<desc>This four-player Zelda connectivity adventure combines gameplay on both the GameCube and Game Boy Advance for a mix of competitive and cooperative multiplayer fun. By hooking up GBAs to the GameCube, the action will move from the television screen (when players are on the overworld map), to the GBA screen (when entering houses and caves). Players work together to brave 24 challenges in eight levels in Hyrule Adventure (1-4 players, multiplayer only with GBAs) or compete in 10 frantic multiplayer versus battles (2-4 players, GBAs required). Takes place in similar environments as the SNES classic Link to the Past, but features updated character sprites, new special effects, and overall improved graphics. The Japanese version included an additional mode, known as Navi Trackers.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time &amp; Master Quest (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time / Master Quest</name>
		<desc>Originally released as a bonus disk for those who pre-ordered The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker, The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time / Master Quest contains GCN versions of Ocarina of Time and the never-released 64DD Ura Zelda (a remixed version of Ocarina of Time with harder dungeons ... Only true heroes will make it through this quest alive!).
                Fans of Nintendo's acclaimed series can play both of these games on their GameCubes, and enjoy a few technical improvements over the N64 versions, namely a higher 640x480 resolution, Dolby Pro-Logic surround sound support, and 480p Progressive Scan support. Veterans and newcomers alike will find something to enjoy with this excellent port of the classic N64 game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - The Wind Waker (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : The Wind Waker</name>
		<desc>Nintendo's thematic action-adventure sequel to Ocarina of Time takes the series back to its more cartoonish roots. Utilizing a completely new look with cel-shaded graphics, the game casts players in the role of a familiar young boy, who sets out to save his kidnapped sister. Gameplay is vintage Zelda, only that the game's overworld is covered by water. Players have to control the direction of the wind to sail across the ocean and find dungeons, towns, and plenty of secrets. A special Game Boy Advance link-up option lets another player join the quest and give hints and assistance via the handheld.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20030324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Twilight Princess (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Twilight Princess</name>
		<desc>Link, a young man raised as a wrangler in a small, rural village, is ordered by the mayor to attend the Hyrule Summit. He sets off, oblivious to the dark fate that has descended upon the kingdom. When he enters the Twilight Realm that has covered Hyrule, he transforms into a wolf and is captured. A mysterious figure named Midna helps him break free, and with the aid of her magic, they set off to free the land from the shadows. Link must explore the vast land of Hyrule and uncover the mystery behind its plunge into darkness. As he does, he'll have to enlist the aid of friendly folk, solve puzzles and battle his way through dangerous dungeons. In the Twilight Realm, he?ll have to use his wolf abilities and Midna?s magic to bring light to the land. Besides his trusty sword and shield, Link will use his bow and arrows, fight while on horseback and use a wealth of other items, both new and old.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20061211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost Kingdoms II (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Lost Kingdoms II</name>
		<desc>After the events of the original Lost Kingdoms, the Kingdom of Argwyll stands on the brink of destruction. Now you must take the role of Tara as she summons the guardian creatures to battle the invading evil force, uncover its origins, and save the kingdom. In the game's enhanced card-based battle system, you can now collect and power up more than 200 creature cards. New abilities allow you to transform into creatures and fight in different battle areas.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FromSoftware</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Luigi's Mansion (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Luigi's Mansion</name>
		<desc>Luigi steps out from the shadow of his brother Mario and into the gloomy shadows of a very haunted house in this, his first-ever starring role.

Armed with a flashlight and a customized vacuum cleaner, Luigi must rid the mansion of Boos and ghouls -- and find his missing brother to boot. As Luigi, you'll search for the keys that open the many locked doors; vacuum coins, cash, and gold bars; and explore vases, bookcases, and drawers.

From the brick-walled basement to the gloomy grounds, Luigi's Mansion is packed with chills, thrills, and creepy surprises.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart - Double Dash!! (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Kart : Double Dash!!</name>
		<desc>The Mushroom Kingdom just got a whole lot more hectic as Mario and friends double up for furious kart racing. This time around, each kart holds two racers that can switch places at any time, so choose from a huge cast of favorites and pair them up any way you see fit. The character in front handles the driving duties, while the character in the rear doles out damage with six normal items and eight special items that only specific characters can use. Get ready for some intense multiplayer mayhem with your favorite characters, including Mario, Luigi, Donkey Kong, Peach, Bowser, and Koopa.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 4 (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Party 4</name>
		<desc>Toad, Koopa, and other party-planning pranksters have hidden birthday presents for their closest friends inside the Party Cube. To win the presents, Mario, Yoshi, Peach, and other Mushroom Kingdom favorites will have to plunge into a circus of minigame trickery. As always, keep an eye out for Bowser and his trouble-making goons. Even Whomp and Thwomp have rockin' surprises for you in their Extra Room. Packed with surprises, wild multiplayer action, and zany challenges, Mario Party 4 is your ticket to a good time.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 5 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Party 5</name>
		<desc>Mario and his friends are trying to restore peace to Dream Depot by racing around a collection of all-new game boards on their quest to collect stars. The second GameCube installment in the multiplayer series that began on N64, Mario Party 5 now sports 3D boards, more than 70 new mini-games, more playable characters, and a new single-player story mode that cuts down on wait time. Players can also compete in mini-game tournaments against friends or the CPU, assemble machines and do battle in the Super Duel Mode and test their mettle in three bonus modes: Card Party, Beach Volleyball and Ice Hockey.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 6 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Party 6</name>
		<desc>Mario Party 6 offers a new batch of games that require both your fingers and your voice. In this installment in the Mario Party series, you can use the included microphone controller to talk your way to victory. More than 80 minigames are included. You can play as Mario, Bowser, or other characters from the Mushroom Kingdom. New characters appear on the board depending on what time of day it is. The game supports up to four players.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 7 (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Party 7</name>
		<desc>You can play more than 80 new minigames in the most recent Mario-themed party game, Mario Party 7. Mario and pals needed some time off, but they forgot to invite Bowser on their cruise. You can battle against an angry Bowser or up to seven of your friends on a single GameCube system. Mario Party 7 includes a few new characters and brings back microphone support from Mario Party 6.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Power Tennis (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Power Tennis</name>
		<desc>The Mushroom Kingdom has hosted tennis tournaments before, but never one as explosive as this one. The wild multiplayer action of the smash Nintendo 64 hit, Mario Tennis, returns with even more powerful shots and new, character-specific power-ups guaranteed to make for the craziest matches ever! Instead of just striking a ball back and forth, opponents in Mario Tennis will launch flaming volleys and slam hits with oversized mallets. Gamers play amidst all-new courts and obstacles, as well as some new characters and game modes. For example, you now get to play in the courts of Luigi's Mansion and below the packed stadiums of Peach Dome. Each court brings its own set of challenges. Each character also boasts his/her own set of moves, and each of them fitting the personality of its respective character.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Smash Football (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Mario Strikers</name>
		<desc>Nintendo's foray into sports titles continues with Super Mario Strikers, a soccer game that's unlike anything ever to hit the pitch. Whether players are freezing their opponents with an ice-cold shell, unleashing a spiny shell on their hapless opponents or making entire teams flee in terror with a roving Chain Chomp, they're sure to see something new around every corner kick.
                Super Mario Strikers features all the favorite characters from the Nintendo universe, as well as four-person multiplayer action that will have players and their friends cheering all night long. Get ready for the world cup of gaming.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Next Level Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football (Soccer)</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Superstar Baseball (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Superstar Baseball</name>
		<desc>Continuing the tradition started by such games as Mario Power Tennis and Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour, Mario Baseball lets you play in arcade-style baseball. You can clear all the trials in Challenge mode, or sit down for a game in the Toy Field. With multiplayer options for up to four players, wild, character-specific power moves, intense minigames, and more than 50 characters from the Mario universe, Mario Baseball offers a complete arcade baseball experience.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X Collection (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mega Man X Collection</name>
		<desc>You can relive the classic Mega Man X series in the seven-game compilation Mega Man X Collection. Mega Man X is the series of 2D platformer Mega Man games featuring the game's namesake and his partner, the sword-wielding Zero. The collection features Mega Man X through X6, as well as the North American debut of Mega Man Battle &amp; Chase, the only Mega Man racing game. In addition to the classic titles, the collection features remixed soundtracks, sketch art, and other Mega Man goodies.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Arms - Glitch in the System (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Metal Arms : Glitch in the System</name>
		<desc>Set to the backdrop of a distant universe inhabited exclusively by robots, Glitch is on an adventure to save his home planet Iron Star from the evil General Corrosive and his various mechanical minions. You take control of the colorful machine ? think of him as a mini-mech ? who seems innocent enough but in actuality is armed to the teeth with various weapons and unique abilities. The setup results in an experience that approaches perpetual carnage, and it's all paced along and broken apart by some witty banter, too. But the real draw is the character's ability to sneak up behind robot foes equipped with open rear data panels and hack into and take control of them. Add to that split-screen multiplayer battles, and you've got total robot destruction, third-person-shooter-style.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Swingin' Ape</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid - The Twin Snakes (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid : The Twin Snakes</name>
		<desc>In a joint development effort between Silicon Knights, Nintendo and Konami, the classic PlayStation hit Metal Gear Solid is recreated with updated graphics and an expanded story on the Nintendo GameCube. This overhauled version of the PS One best-seller features graphics on par with the MGS sequels on PlayStation 2. Snake is able to hang from ledges, shoot from a first-person perspective, and hide himself and enemies in lockers. In addition cinematics and audio (featuring all the original voice actors and added music), the game also packs additional weapons, story points, and added replay options.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon Knights</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime (USA) (Rev 2).rvz</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime</name>
		<desc>Everyone's favorite heroine, Samus Aran, is back! Packed to the gills with exploration, creative power-ups, and wicked enemies, Metroid Prime is a first-person adventure worthy of the Metroid stamp. An action-packed adventure set in the first-person perspective, Metroid Prime takes place just after the events in the original Metroid (NES). It has lead character Samus Aran, a bounty hunter by trade, chasing down the evil Space Pirates. Their intention is to use a genetic mutagen called Phazon to create a super army and take over the universe. While the installments in the series before have never been home to deeply involving storylines, Metroid Prime breaks the shell to offer up one of the most intriguing and read-worthy sagas yet. Developed by Texas-based Retro Studios. Metroid Prime brings all of the elements of the acclaimed franchise into a massive 3D arena.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime 2 - Echoes (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime 2 : Echoes</name>
		<desc>In this highly anticipated sequel to Metroid Prime, become the bounty hunter behind the visor once more and travel to a planet torn into light and darkness. Hunted by a mysterious entity and a warring race called the Ing, Samus Aran must explore the light and dark worlds of this doomed planet to discover secrets and augment her suit's weapons and abilities. And now, for the first time in the history of the celebrated Metroid franchise, up to four players can battle each other as they search for weapons, grapple across ceilings, and turn into Morph Balls to make their escapes.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nickelodeon SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants : Battle for Bikini Bottom</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob Squarepants: Battle for Bikini Bottom is based on the immensely popular Nickelodeon cartoon series. In this game, players control SpongeBob, Patrick and Sandy through 30+ levels of zany and hilarious platform gameplay, doing such outrageous moves like tongue-boarding, underwear bungee jumping and lasso-coptering.

Plankton's latest diabolical scheme to steal the Krabby Patty formula hinges on the creation of an army of evil robots, who will do his bidding. But because Plankton forgot to throw the "Obey Plankton" switch, the army of robots have run amuck and are terrorizing Bikini Bottom. Help SpongeBob, Patrick and Sandy save Bikini Bottom!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heavy Iron</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Odama (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Odama</name>
		<desc>Odama is a quirky pinball title set in ancient Japan.  You are in control of a giant steel ball, called the Odama, which you use to crush the enemy army (and hopefully not your own soldiers) so that you have an easier time leading the Ninten Bell to its destination.

The game also takes of advantage of the GCN microphone (included with most versions of the game), which you use to command your troops. You must use the commands and pinball skills to successfully lead the Ninten Bell to its destination before sunset in each mission.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivarium</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./P.N. 03 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>P.N.03</name>
		<desc>The Computer Arms Management System (CAMS) is the basic form of defense for planets against any enemy. But a terrible accident leaves an entire colony dead, and its up to a human to put an end to the out of control system.

Enter Vanessa Z. Schneider, a freelance mercenary, who has been charged with the task of bringing CAMS under control. But she has another mission in hand: revenge for CAMS destruction of her family.

Control Vanessa through the various landscapes in a 3rd person perspective, using her upgradeable abilities to destroy the CAMS, while dodging fire with a range of acrobatic moves.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario - The Thousand-Year Door (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Paper Mario : The Thousand-Year Door</name>
		<desc>Get ready for a new role-playing adventure as Mario returns to paper form to stop a dangerous threat. In Paper Mario 2, Mario can dodge, inflict damage, and impress the crowd to strengthen his attacks. Also, Mario and his friends have more paper abilities. They can now turn sideways to slip through cracks, fold into a paper airplane to fly, roll into a tube, and more. They can also use a variety of items like hammers and thunderbolts to defeat their enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pikmin (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Pikmin</name>
		<desc>Pikmin may be small and plantlike, but they can be a space traveler's best friend. Stranded on an unknown planet, Captain Olimar must enlist the help of these native Pikmin to rebuild his spaceship before the life-support system runs out. In the meantime, you'll have to fend off attackers and solve various puzzles. To produce additional multicolored Pikmin you must defeat enemies and carry them back to the Pikmin nests called onions. But beware--watching giant predators gobble your Pikmin might make you angrier than you'd expect.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pikmin 2 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Pikmin 2</name>
		<desc>Captain Olimar has returned to the planet where the Pikmin live, and he's all business this time. The company he works for is going bankrupt, so to save it, Olimar must salvage the treasure buried all over the planet. Of course, he'll need the help of the Pikmin to do that--he can't do anything by himself. Control one of two main characters--Olimar or his assistant--as you command your Pikmin to defeat enemies, propagate more Pikmin, collect precious doodads, and solve puzzles. With unlimited time, new colors of Pikmin, and two-player cooperative play, Pikmin 2 improves on the original in many ways.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Colosseum (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Pokémon Colosseum</name>
		<desc>Pokémon fans can now battle their favorite Pokémon on the grand stage. Starring a brand new leading character, Pokémon, Colosseum offers a story mode that pits you against tough trainers who routinely catch damaged Pokémon. In Battle mode, you can use the Game Boy Advance cable to send your team from your Pokémon Ruby or Pokémon Sapphire Game Pak to your Gamecube, then witness the true potential of your team. Rescue Pokémon and watch them come to life in spectacular Colosseum battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genius Sonority</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon XD - Gale of Darkness (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Pokémon XD : Gale of Darkness</name>
		<desc>XD centers on Dark Pokemon, Pokemon who've had their hearts sealed away and now use Dark Skills to attack you and your Pokemon friends. You play as a nameless main character who adventures with his little sister, Mana. Your quest is to free the Dark Pokemon from their misguided trainers and open their hearts back up. To do this, you'll make use of an eye piece called the Aura Searcher, which identifies Dark Pokemon by their characteristic purple glow, and your Snatch Machine, which plucks the Dark Pokemon from battle. XD features a full RPG-style quest, taking you to various towns and locations. You'll meet a number of human characters on your travels. Nintendo seems to be preparing a more fleshed out quest this time around.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genius Sonority</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo Pop Fever (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).rvz</path>
		<name>Puyo Pop Fever</name>
		<desc>Puyo Pop Fever is a puzzle game of the falling-block variety, the goal of which is to clear your blocks (Puyos) by combining four or more of the same color, which will then vanish. This will produce Nuisance Puyos. These colorless Puyos will fall onto your opponents screen, thus blocking chains and combos they could create. These pesky Puyos can only be exterminated by removing neighboring Puyos.
When an opponent sends Nuisance Puyos to your screen you can try to "offset" by clearing your own Puyos and limiting the number that would fall on your screen. This will also increase your Fever Meter. When this meter fills you will be given a set of prearranged Puyos with which you can wrack up giant combos and send tons of Nuisance Puyos to your opponent. When any player's field becomes so full that they can no longer drop Puyos they lose the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle / Fall</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil</name>
		<desc>Raccoon City. A secluded mountain community, plagued by a storm of vicious attacks, is completely overrun. Mutant beasts, blood-thirsty zombies infest the landscape. You are S.T.A.R.S - Special Tactics and Rescue Squad. Your mission: investigate the ominous mansion at the core of the horrific disaster. Uncover secrets behind a radical, genetic research facility. With unspeakable horrors lurking around every corner, the ultimate test may be just to make it out alive!

Turn out the lights. Lock the doors...Live the Nightmare.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2</name>
		<desc>In Resident Evil 2, the classic action, tense exploration, and puzzle solving gameplay that defined the Resident Evil series returns.

Players join rookie police officer Leon Kennedy and college student Claire Redfield, who are thrust together by a disastrous outbreak in Raccoon City that transformed its population into deadly zombies. Both Leon and Claire have their own separate playable campaigns, allowing players to see the story from both characters' perspectives.

The fate of these two fan favorite characters is in players hands as they work together to survive and get to the bottom of what is behind the terrifying attack on the city. Will they make it out alive?</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3 : Nemesis</name>
		<desc>A month and a half have passed since the mansion lab incident and now the secrets come back to haunt you in Resident Evil 3: Nemesis. Join Jill Valentine in her attempt to escape a nightmarish city in ruins. Around every corner lurk hordes of flesh-eating zombies, hideous mutants, and a relentless new nemesis. You'll soon rely on cunning and brute force to stay alive. The Resident Evil series has taken a horrifying turn, unveiling new layers in the Umbrella Corporation's devious activities.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 4 (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 4</name>
		<desc>The story is about Leon S. Kennedy, one of the survivors of the Raccoon City disaster; he is sent on a special mission to rescue Ashley Graham, the daughter of the president of the United States, who has been kidnapped by a strange organization based in Spain. But his investigation is hampered when a horde of violent villagers attacks him for no apparent reason. It is an action-adventure survival horror video game. For the first time in the series, the closed, linear environment is left aside to include larger, more dynamic settings as the story takes place in a town in Spain.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil Zero (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Zero</name>
		<desc>Before the events of Resident Evil, the residents of Raccoon City lived their lives unaware of the dark fate that surrounded them. Now, along with your S.T.A.R.S. Bravo Team, you're sent in to investigate a series of grisly murders in the area. As Rebecca Chambers, a rookie cop, or Billy Cowen, an escaped convict, you'll fight zombies, solve challenging puzzles, and slowly uncover the truth behind the murders. A new Partner Zapping System lets you quickly switch between each character.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Second Sight (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Second Sight</name>
		<desc>Join John Vattic, a man endowed with psychic abilities, as he attempts to escape a US medical facility. As you discover more and more of John's psychic powers, you'll slowly uncover the events that landed him in the hands of the researchers. You'll gain access to a variety of psionic abilities (such as Psi-Blast, Telekinesis, Projection, and Charm) and powerful weapons (including handguns, tranquilizers, and machine guns). Complete your objectives using a combination of shooting action and stealth tactics.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040921T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Free Radical Design</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skies of Arcadia Legends (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Skies of Arcadia Legends</name>
		<desc>Grasp the wheel of your air-ship and prepare to embark on a legendary adventure. You are Vyse, a young member of the Blue Rogue pirates. Together with your childhood friend Aika and Fina, a mysterious girl, you are locked in an epic struggle with a powerful enemy nation for the fate of the world. You must gather your own crew of air pirates and journey through uncharted skies to vanquish the empire from every corner of the map. Along the way, you'll wage battles against savage monsters and evil pirates as you make a name for yourself on land and in the sky.</desc>
		<releasedate>20030129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Overworks</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2 - Battle (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).rvz</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2 Battle</name>
		<desc>Sonic and company are back and better than ever in Sonic Adventure 2: Battle for Nintendo GameCube. Dr. Eggman is up to his old tricks, and it's up to Sonic, Tails, and Knuckles to stop him yet again. Sonic Adventure 2: Battle features faster action, all-new two-player games, and a branching storyline that lets you choose to save the world as the Hero side, or conquer it as the Dark side.

Two new playable characters enter the Sonic universe -- a mysterious dark hedgehog called Shadow, and a jewel-thieving bat named Rouge. In the single-player mode, you'll go through more than 30 unique stages, which include everything from a forgotten pyramid, an abandoned military base, and a giant space station. Then there's the expanded two-player mode, which features 12 playable characters competing in new head-to-head games. All of this adds up to Sonic's biggest adventure yet!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Mega Collection (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Sonic Mega Collection</name>
		<desc>Sonic has appeared in many games in the last decade, and now you can relive seven of them from Sonic Mega Collection. This compilation includes the first three Sonic the Hedgehog titles, plus Sonic &amp; Knuckles, Sonic 3D Flickies' Island, Sonic the Hedgehog Spinball, and Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine. With additional content such as character illustrations, movies, and comic-book covers, this game celebrates Sonic's long career and introduces his world to new generation of gamers.Games list:* Sonic The Hedgehog* Sonic The Hedgehog 2* Sonic The Hedgehog 3* Sonic &amp; Knuckles* Blue Sphere (Unlockable)* Knuckles the Echina in Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (Unlockable)* Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles (Unlockable)* Sonic 3D Blast* Sonic Spinball* Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine* Flicky (Unlockable)* Ristar (Unlockable)</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soulcalibur II (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>SoulCalibur II</name>
		<desc>Open the next chapter in world of Soul Calibur.

Soul Calibur II features seven distinctive gameplay modes including: Arcade, Versus, Time Attack, Survival, Team Battle, Practice, and the console exclusive Weapon Master.

Collect up to 200 different weapons and battle characters with their own styles, strengths, and abilities. In addition to the 13 fighters, each platform has unique special fighters: Link for GameCube, Heihachi for PS2, and Spawn for Xbox.

Prove yourself through soul and sword.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox - Assault (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Star Fox : Assault</name>
		<desc>Team Star Fox is back for more intense combat as they engage a new threat by air and by land. A few years after disaster was barely averted on Dinosaur Planet, Lylat Central Command gets wind of a new threat spreading throughout the solar system. The Star Fox team--composed of classic team members Fox McCloud, Slippy Toad, Peppy Hare, and Falco Lombardi, along with some new faces--is sent in to engage this new enemy. Now, as part of the Star Fox team, you can participate in solo or co-op missions or plug in with up to three other players.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox Adventures (USA) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Star Fox Adventures</name>
		<desc>General Scales has unleashed powers that are tearing apart the once-peaceful Dinosaur Planet. With the survival of his home planet at risk, Fox McCloud receives an urgent message to battle Scales and his vast army of SharpClaws. As Fox, you'll gain support from Star Fox Team members Slippy, Peppy, and Rob. You must rely on the mystical powers of a unique staff as you battle Scales' minions, befriend peaceful plant-eaters, and encounter eerie spirits that hold the key to the planet's survival.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Rogue Squadron II - Rogue Leader (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Star Wars Rogue Leader : Rogue Squadron II</name>
		<desc>In Star Wars Rogue Squadron II you get the chance to jump into the cockpit of an X-wing and join Luke Skywalker and the Star Wars galaxy's most daring pilots as they return to face off against the Empire. As in the original hit game for N64, you'll relive favorite Star Wars battles including the perilous Death Star trench run, a daring space attack on a Star Destroyer and the legendary battle on the ice planet Hoth. Rogue Leader features stunning, movie like visuals and immerses players in an intense action-arcade experience. Aerial conflict takes place in a variety of craft such as the legendary X-wing, A-wing, and B-wing. For the first time, the game also features on-foot ground combat in missions directly based on or inspired by the original movie trilogy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Strikers (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Mario Strikers</name>
		<desc>Nintendo's foray into sports titles continues with Super Mario Strikers, a soccer game that's unlike anything ever to hit the pitch. Whether players are freezing their opponents with an ice-cold shell, unleashing a spiny shell on their hapless opponents or making entire teams flee in terror with a roving Chain Chomp, they're sure to see something new around every corner kick.
                Super Mario Strikers features all the favorite characters from the Nintendo universe, as well as four-person multiplayer action that will have players and their friends cheering all night long. Get ready for the world cup of gaming.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Next Level Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football (Soccer)</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Sunshine (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Mario Sunshine</name>
		<desc>Mario, Princess Peach, Toadsworth, and Toad have come to Isle Delfino for some relaxation. Upon arrival, however, they discover the island has been polluted causing its energy source, the Shine Sprites, to disappear. The culprit is similar in appearance to Mario, who is blamed for the mess, so the portly plumber is forced to clean up the island. Mario is given an invention called FLUDD (a backpack with several water nozzles) to help him clean up graffiti and mud and capture the real villain. Gameplay features a combination of action and puzzle solving, with numerous stages and multiple episodes to each stage, and plenty of hidden secrets and surprises.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Monkey Ball (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Monkey Ball</name>
		<desc>Call your friends and warn your neighbors, it's time to have a ball! Go bananas with 90+ stages, multi-player madness, and 7 cool ways to play! Equal parts "party" and "game", Super Monkey Ball could be the most "well-rounded" game you've ever played!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Monkey Ball 2 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Monkey Ball 2</name>
		<desc>The object of Super Monkey Ball 2 is to guide a monkey trapped inside a plastic ball through a maze to the goal. There are three variations, story mode, challenge mode, and practice mode. In story mode you have unlimited number of tries to complete a stage, and after clearing 10 stages a movie clip is shown followed by a new world of 10 stages. In challenge mode, you have a limited number of monkeys and a time limit to complete numerous levels of increasing difficulty. In practice mode you can play any stage already completed in the other two modes. In addition to the main game options, numerous party games are also included. These are monkey race, monkey fight, monkey target, monkey billiards, monkey bowling, monkey golf, monkey boat, monkey shot, monkey dogfight, monkey soccer, monkey baseball, and monkey tennis. The party games can be played by one to four players.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. Melee (USA) (En,Ja) (Rev 2).rvz</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros. Melee</name>
		<desc>Nintendo's all-star cast of combatants is back in Super Smash Bros. Melee, along with a new batch of brawlers ready to tear it up. The sequel to Super Smash Bros. keeps the same basic premise: Characters duke it out in interactive environments, using special attacks and various items to knock each other into the abyss. Some new defensive techniques add an even deeper level of complexity to the combat. In addition to traditional battle royale matches, players can select all-new ways to play like Coin mode and Tournament mode.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20011202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Symphonia (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Tales of Symphonia</name>
		<desc>In a dying village on Sylvarant, legend has it that a Chosen One will one day appear from among the people, and the land will be reborn. Now, you must enter a cel-shaded world in which you command real-time battles. Execute and combine hundreds of special attacks, magic spells, and combos. Each character grows to suit your fighting style, and the storyline changes based on the characters' relationships. The line between good and evil blurs in this immersive adventure where the fate of two interlocked worlds hangs in the balance.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tube Slider - The Championship of Future Formula (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Tube Slider</name>
		<desc>Sometime in the middle of the 21st century, shortly following the development of hydrogen-based power, a global treaty prohibiting the use of fossil fuels was passed which banned all motor sports. Although the world established a culture of peace and environmental preservation, people wanted a sport that would whet their appetites for speed and competition...

Get your adrenaline fix as you race at incredible speeds in hover vehicles that slide through futuristic gravity-defying race courses enclosed in tubes... reaching speeds over 1,000 miles per hour! The future of championship formula racing is faster, sleeker, and more dangerous. You may be able to finish a race, but can you take home a championship?</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nd Cube</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Viewtiful Joe (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Viewtiful Joe</name>
		<desc>Joe is your normal everyday guy, watching movies and hanging out with his girlfriend, Silvia. But when Silvia is sucked into a movie reel by an evil force, Joe's life is turned upside down. It's up to you to take everyman Joe and turn him into a superhero to end all superhero's and save his girl.

With a heavy dose of comic books, Viewtiful Joe is a action packed 2D side-scroller inside a 3D world, that will have you using the amazing abilities of the hero in question as you slice and dice the many enemies on screen with VFX special moves, such as Slow and Mach Speed.

You'll have the chance to earn 'Viewtifuls', which will boost your abilities with new killer moves and special items. You'll need them as you progress further into the seven episodes and big bosses at the end of each.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clover Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Viewtiful Joe 2 (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Viewtiful Joe 2</name>
		<desc>Joe and Silvia are back in this sequel to Viewtiful Joe. This time you have more style, new special moves, and more than 40 new enemies to defeat. Now Joe's trusty aircraft transforms into various shapes to support his activities throughout the game's many stages. In addition to Joe, you can play as Silva, Joe's girlfriend. Call upon the powers of Joe and Silvia, and get ready to both solve new puzzles and save the day.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clover</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario World (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Wario World</name>
		<desc>While Wario enjoys the riches from his many adventures, a mysterious black jewel in his trove transforms gems into monsters. Now, Wario must scramble to recover his riches in an alternate world filled with quirky puzzles, swarming enemies, and lots of loot. As Wario, you'll punch, kick, jump, grab monsters and objects, and inhale surrounding coins like a vacuum cleaner. You must cling to 3D balls to fight bosses, find hidden areas through trap doors, and bash your surroundings to uncover secrets.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarioWare, Inc. - Mega Party Game$! (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>WarioWare, Inc. : Mega Party Game$!</name>
		<desc>Wario is back in the video game biz, and this time the tightfisted microgame master is servin' up some insane party games on Nintendo GameCube. The 200+ hysterical microgames from Wario Ware, Inc.: Mega Microgame$ are making a triumphant return on the big screen, supported by wildly creative multiplayer matches starring Wario's crazy crew of video game developers.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wave Race - Blue Storm (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Wave Race : Blue Storm</name>
		<desc>Wave Race: Bluestorm is a sequel to Nintendo's Wave Race 64. It incorporates several modes of play, a variety of racers, customization options, and tracks. Players can race in four tournament cup series, compete in time attack mode against the best track times, compete for points in stunt mode, and simply take in the eye-poppingly beautiful graphics in Free Roam mode. Multiplay is supported in Stunt and Race modes. There are a total of eight racers to choose from, each with a different balance in engine and handling.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Water</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star Online Episode I &amp; II (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es) (Rev 1).rvz</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star Online Episode I &amp; II</name>
		<desc>The planet Ragol is once again in peril. New character classes and weapons are at your disposal, but only your skills as a Hunter will keep you alive. Brave the depths of evil alone, or enlist the aid of three Heroes in split-screen play. Once you have conquered the Darkness, go online and take your experience to the next level. However you choose to play, know this: Evil has returned to Ragol, and a new adventure awaits.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf - Toadstool Tour (USA).rvz</path>
		<name>Mario Golf : Toadstool Tour</name>
		<desc>Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour updates the Mario Golf series with more swing control, new courses, and fun side games. Carefully select your club, choose the optimal contact point and trajectory, compensate for wind and green speeds, and then swing away. You'll also have to compensate for each character's weaknesses and for each course's terrain--from beautiful rolling hills to fantastic pipes and sand traps. One to four players can enter a tournament, which rewards skillful play with trophies, badges, prizes, and secrets.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030729T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<playtime>71</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260628T093223</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
