<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Ace Combat 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ace Combat 2</name>
		<desc>Ace Combat 2 is the sequel to Namco's PSX combat flight simulator Air Combat. Ace Combat 2 puts you back in the cockpit as a mercenary pilot out to foil a world-threatening terrorist plot. You'll proceed through 30 missions in which your success will allow you to buy weapon upgrades, parts and other gimmicks just like in the original. 

The game offers sharper graphics and sounds, more planes and options, dual shock support as well as adding analog joystick support.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>8</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20250508T122343</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ace Combat 3 - Electrosphere (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ace Combat 3 : Electrosphere</name>
		<desc>In Ace Combat 3: Electrosphere the player takes the place of an ace fighter pilot who works for an organization called "UPEO" and has to accomplish various missions, e.g. taking out a special aircraft carrier or taking out enemy satellite systems in orbit around earth. The player can earn ratings from A to D: the higher the rating, the higher the chance that the player can acquire new kinds of planes. The game has many environments which range from normal aerial missions to stratospheric missions and even outer space missions. A special catch is that the player often has to make decisions during missions which influence the overall storyline. There is also an autopilot feature which can be used to land or reach a destination.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Plane, TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark : The New Nightmare</name>
		<desc>Alone in the Dark: The New Nightmare is the fourth entry in the Alone in the Dark series, continuing the story set up by the previous installments. Charles Fisk has gone missing on Shadow Island and is presumed dead. His good friend, private investigator Edward Carnby, has chartered a plane to Shadow Island to investigate the disappearance of his friend and discover what the island's owner, Obed Morton, is planning. Ailene Cedrac, an ethnology Professor at Boston University, also has an interest in the island -- she believes that her long lost father is located there. Driven by intrigue as well as a desire for closure, both Cedrac and Carnby fly to the island on Halloween night.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Darkworks</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alundra (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Alundra</name>
		<desc>Alundra is a boy who can step into other people's dreams. His own dreams tell him to go to the village Inoa. The ship on which Alundra is coming to the village goes down, but Alundra himself is washed up on a beach near the village. There, a blacksmith Jess takes care of him and treats him like his own son. But Alundra, stepping into the dreams of the village people, understands there's a danger somewhere. The people have horrible nightmares, and only Alundra can find out what they mean...

Alundra is an action role playing game (RPG) somewhat similar to the famous Zelda games. It uses real-time combat and has a lot of physical and environmental puzzles. A big part of the game is spent in dungeons, where the player has to solve puzzles in order to proceed.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19971231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alundra 2 - A New Legend Begins (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Alundra 2 : A New Legend Begins</name>
		<desc>In the distant lands of the Vanilla Kingdom; a mysterious being has appeared in the Doru region, who is able to change the evolution of the animal kingdom at will, forcing a magical evolution. The consequences of this are terrible: it transforms living beings into evil mechanical beings. In this situation, Flint appears; a young boy, orphaned due to the death of his parents at the hands of the pirates, whom he persues without rest; although he will have to abandon this obsession when he is forced to confront the mysterious being, Mephisto.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ape Escape (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ape Escape</name>
		<desc>A boisterous band of baboons carry out a daring zoo escape. It's ape anarchy and it's up to you to stop the chimps before they make chumps out of the human race! Use both analog sticks to operate great gadgets including a Tank, a Remote Control Car, a Stun Club, and a Time Net in your quest to hunt down over 200 apes!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blood Omen - Legacy of Kain (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Blood Omen : Legacy of Kain</name>
		<desc>Blood Omen is a top-down game where the player controls the vampiric Kain. As a vampire, Kain is able to withstand sunlight, but is harmed by water. However, he is able to obtain several cursed abilities and spells such as being able to transform into a bat, wolf and even a cloud mist respectively, as well as learning the ability to disguise himself from creatures of weaker mind. Kain is also fixated on murder and is a master of several ways to kill and destroy his opponents. As the enemies are slain in front of him, Kain may drink their blood to restore his health, which is always trickling away, representative of his insatiable craving. To aid in the slaughter of his enemies, Kain may equip different weapons and armor, each with its own unique properties.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19961114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon Knights</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloody Roar (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar</name>
		<desc>BLOODY ROAR pits eight fighters with unique "Spirit Animals" against each other. Don't just beat your opponents; pummel them into the ground by using combo after combo, or transforming into the character's "Spirit Animal," which might be a killer rabbit, gorilla, fox, or something else, entirely. See the moment of victory with instant replays that show the blow that put the loser down for good. Every fighter is involved in the tournament for his or her own reasons, and you can play as each of the characters to learn those reasons. With all of the action in BLOODY ROAR, the beast in you just might come out.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloody Roar II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar II</name>
		<desc>Bloody Roar is back with this sequel. Among the new and improved features are seven new characters (along with four original fighters) complete with new moves and looks. Like the original, each character has an inner-beast; Yugo morphs into a ravenous wolf and the vampire-like Jenny turns into a bat. There are nine initially selectable characters with two more waiting to be found.
			The Arcade mode offers a no-frills competition against the computerized AI. If players get bored with the Arcade mode, a second player can join in the action or select the Versus option -- a two-player brawl. Survival mode tests to see how many opponents a player can beat without getting knocked out. In the Story mode, the real draw of Bloody Roar II, each character comes with his or her own unique scenario. By winning rounds, the story unfurls and resolves after the final conflict.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brave Fencer Musashi (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Brave Fencer Musashi</name>
		<desc>Brave Fencer Musashi is an action role-playing video game developed and published by Square in 1998 for the PlayStation home console. The game involves real-time sword-based combat in a 3D environment; it also features segments of voiced over dialogue and role-playing game elements such as a day-night cycle and resting to restore energy.

The story follows Musashi, a young swordsman who is summoned to a parallel world to defend Allucanet Kingdom from the Thirstquencher Empire. He searches for the Five Scrolls, which can enhance the powers of his sword, while interacting with people from Allucanet and a nearby village.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20250508T122408</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire III (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire III</name>
		<desc>Set free by the the workers of Dauna Mine, Ryu of the Brood learns to both understand his power, and to understand the history of his extinct kind. By both utilizing Ryu's unique power and the abilities of those whom assist him, players will uncover the history of the Brood, learn more about the characters, and the very reason why the Brood were wiped out.

Players control Ryu and his allies on their journey, each of Ryu's friends have abilities only they can use, and they will have to work together to make their way through the obstacles and enemies that they encounter; creativity is key to your success in this game!

Ryu eventually is able to utilize his power of the Brood, allowing him to ascend into various dragon-like forms. This is done using a gene-splicing system that dictates what sort of form Ryu will take.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire IV (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire IV</name>
		<desc>Nina, the princess of Wyndia, and Cray, chieftain of the cat-like Woren tribe, are searching for Cray's relatives who disappeared under mysterious circumstances during a diplomatic mission. Flying through the sky on their sandflier, Nina and Cray are attacked by a worm shaped dragon. With their vehicle damaged, Nina returns to the city to find parts, bumping into a naked young boy named Ryu along the way, who is unsure of where he is. At the very same time, Nina is again attacked by a dragon. Confused by the strange events taking place, Nina agrees to help the young boy. Meanwhile, the ancient Emperor Fou Lu awakens from his slumber in his tomb. His plan is to return to the world of human, conquer it anew, and impose his iron rule on it...
This fourth installment of the Breath of Fire series is a fairly traditional Japanese-style RPG, with turn-based combat, party management, linear story progression, and other characteristic elements of the genre.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bushido Blade (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bushido Blade</name>
		<desc>The Bushido code of honor governs the actions of the Samurai and sets a code of ethics for use in fighting. Sometime in the 20th century, a group of Narukagami ninja, each proficient in a different style, find themselves in a battle to regain their honor in the fighting ring.
			 Bushido Blade is a unique fighting game, in that Square did away with health bars, special meters, and other traditional gimmicks and allowed for battles to be won with a single hit. This realism made the game a fan favorite among certain groups.
			 Players select from among six ninja, each of a different fighting style and attributes. Players also choose equipment from among eight weapons, including Japanese swords, European blades, naginata and a sledgehammer.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Light Weight</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20250508T115517</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bushido Blade 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bushido Blade 2</name>
		<desc>Two samurai families who date back over eight hundred years have been feuding ever since the Gempei War, where the Kagami family sided with the Minamoto and ensured themselves a victory over their rivals, the Sue. Over the centuries since, the two families evolved into ninja clans, but their hatred of each other never faded. Now, in the 20th century, the Shainto, descendants of the Sue, are in a position to bring vengeance on the Narukagami.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Light Weight</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Cross (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Chrono Cross</name>
		<desc>Chrono Cross is a sequel to the SNES RPG  Chrono Trigger.

The main character is Serge, a young boy from a fishing village. One day, while strolling on the sea shore with his sweetheart, Serge suddenly disappears. He comes back to senses several moments later. Everything seems just the same as it was before, but when Serge visits his home village, nobody recognizes him. He hears from people that he has been dead for ten years. Serge begins to realize that he is now in a parallel world. His first and only wish is to find a way to return home, but, in order to do that, he must understand what has caused the existence of parallel words, allowing inter-dimensional travel. His quest will also reveal to him the truth about his own existence, and connect the seemingly unrelated plot of Chrono Cross to that of Chrono Trigger.

Chrono Cross is a Japanese RPG with turn-based battles. There are no random battles; enemies are always visible on screen. There are also no character levels in the game; instead, characters get better stats directly after each battle. During battles, Serge and his party members can perform three kinds of attacks: weak, medium, and strong. Strong attacks tend to miss more frequently. Magical spells are equipped by each character like items, and can be cast only as many times as they are equipped. Actions in battle deplete a certain amount of stamina, which recovers as other characters act. 

Chrono Cross features many recruitable characters (up to 40, but not all of them can be recruited in one play-through), several different endings, and the ability to play the game again with the same stats and items from the previous play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Civilization II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Civilization II</name>
		<desc>Re-write history with Civilization II as you lead your people to the promised land of peace and harmony with neighbouring cultures. That's one theory anyway, though what usually happens is that the Chinese whisper of international diplomacy means that the message gets distorted in transmission.
You start Civilization II as leader of a puny tribe of people, eking out a subsistence-level existence in a time where log fires are considered hi-tech. Using your leadership and strategy skills, you must explore your world, expand your empire and ensure the survival of your way of life in what can turn out to be a pretty dog-eat-dog world.
As time passes and your success builds you will form new alliances, make new enemies, discover new technologies and systems of government . . .all with the aim of ensuring the persistence of your civilisation. Noble aims which will sometimes mean brinkmanship, double-dealing and back-stabbing, but it's for the greater good, and all that.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LTI Gray Matter</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colin McRae Rally 2.0 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Colin McRae Rally 2.0</name>
		<desc>Colin McRae Rally 2.0 is a racing video game developed and published by Codemasters for PlayStation. It is the second game in the Colin McRae Rally series. You get to race in locations around the world, over 60 stages in eight different countries. Battle your way towards winning the championship. You can choose from many real life car models, and tune them up to match the conditions! The game realistically simulates all road types, weather conditions, and the physics of car handling create an authentic rally experience. The locations and the cars are all real!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colony Wars (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Colony Wars</name>
		<desc>Since 3095, the Earth Empire has spread throughout the universe, taking what it wants and destroying the rest - all in the name of sustaining life on Earth.  To the Empire, expansion is of the utmost importance, even above famine, drought and death.

The League of Free Worlds exists to offer resistance and hope to the plundered outlying colonies.  After a key victory, it is shown that the Empire's Navy can be harmed and the ranks of the League begin to swell.

Colony Wars is a combat fighter game set in space.  You, as the player, join as a recruit in the League's fleet.  Missions take place in various fighters, from a 1st person view inside the cockpit, or a 3rd person view from behind your ship. Ships have separate meters for shields and armor, and the player must cycle between weapons designed specifically to damage each. At the most basic, purple lasers must drain a target's shields, followed by switching to red lasers to destroy them.

The game features advanced lighting and particle effects for the Playstation, as well as a basic simulation of Newtonian physics. Thrusters are only active for as long as the accelerate button is held down. The player can burst fire their thrusters and drift, allowing for some advanced maneuvers. The campaign also features multiple endings and branching missions/storylines, based on your performance in the previous operations.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colony Wars - Red Sun (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Colony Wars III : Red Sun</name>
		<desc>Colony Wars: Red Sun (called Colony Wars III: Red Sun in North America) is a space combat simulator video game for the PlayStation developed and released by Psygnosis in 2000. Other two episodes were released beforehand, namely Colony Wars in 1997 and Colony Wars: Vengeance in 1998.

Instead of being a starfighter pilot for the League of Free Worlds or the Colonial Navy, the player now assumes the role of a civilian miner-turned-mercenary.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20000502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colony Wars - Vengeance (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Colony Wars : Vengeance</name>
		<desc>Colony Wars: Vengeance is a space combat simulator video game developed and released by Psygnosis for the PlayStation in 1998, and sequel to the original Colony Wars, released the previous year. In it, players complete space combat missions using preselected starfighters equipped with various weapons. The game features multiple paths of missions and outcomes, depending on the player's performance.

The game retains the win-lose scenario styling of its predecessor, only now the player controls a pilot, Mertens, who has enlisted in the Colonial Navy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot</name>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot, a heroic, agile and mutated marsupial who must save his girlfriend Tawna. The main antagonist is Doctor Neo Cortex, a mad scientist who was often ridiculed by the scientific community for his outlandish (but nearly workable) theories and is now motivated to prove his tormentors wrong by creating a mutated army of beasts to conquer the world. Cortex's henchman is Doctor Nitrus Brio, the insecure creator of the Evolvo-Ray. Crash's love interest is Tawna, a female bandicoot about to undergo experimentation by the Doctors. Helping Crash in his journey is an ancient witch doctor spirit named Aku Aku, who has scattered masks of himself throughout the islands to grant Crash special powers. The boss characters of the game include Papu Papu, the obese and short-tempered chief of the native village; Ripper Roo, a demented kangaroo with razor-sharp toenails; Koala Kong, a muscular but unintelligent koala; and Pinstripe Potoroo, the tommy gun-wielding bodyguard of Doctor Cortex.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot : Warped</name>
		<desc>After defeating Dr. Neo Cortex, Crash and his sister, Coco, take a well-deserved vacation. However, their friend, Aku Aku, has a bad feeling, and as usual, he is right. Aku's evil twin, Uka Uka, was the person behind all of Dr. Cortex's schemes. Now Uka and Cortex have hatched a plot to gain control of the powerful crystals they desire. The have hired Dr. N. Tropy to create a time machine, which will allow Uka and Cortex to go back and take the crystals without interference. Take control of Crash and Coco as they travel through 30 levels across five time periods in an effort to stop Uka and Cortex. Use a motorcycle, plane, bazooka, and a baby T-rex to help Crash survive, or destroy the bad guys by using new moves like the super belly flop or the double jump. Will Crash and Coco be able to save the world? Play CRASH BANDICOOT: Warped and find out.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2 : Cortex Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>After his defeat, Dr. Neo Cortex discovers the crystals that keep the world in balance. However, something is wrong: some of the crystals are missing. When the planets align, the chaotic flux created by the event will destroy the world. Cortex devises a plan to save the world by creating the Cortex Vortex.
 To help him save the world Cortex recruits his nemesis, Crash Bandicoot, to help him find the crystals. Take control of Crash as he travels to exotic locales like a space station, a waterfall, and Antarctica in 34 levels of running, jumping, and spinning action.
 Advance through the levels in any order you wish thanks to the level hub system. Will Crash be able to find all of the crystals? Can Dr. Cortex be trusted or is all of this an elaborate ruse? Play CRASH BANDICOOT 2: Cortex Strikes Back and find out.
 Features:
 * 34 levels with hidden areas and bonus levels
 * New moves and combo attacks
 * New interactive characters and enemies
 * Variety of challenging puzzles and mini-games</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CTR - Crash Team Racing (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Team Racing</name>
		<desc>It's a multi-player kart racing game starring your favorite bandicoot CRASH and a host of his friends...and foes! The stakes are high and the competition is fierce. Ready...Set...GO!!!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkstalkers 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Darkstalkers 3</name>
		<desc>This is the 3rd in the Darkstalkers series (the 2nd, Night Warriors: Darkstalkers' Revenge, was published only for the Sega Saturn in the US.)  It plays much the same as the first, but features better animation, more playable characters, and a deeper storyline.

Jedah, the "Lord of Vampire", has summoned all of the Night Warriors to his realm to be assimilated into his being.  Of course, this serves as a great excuse to have more one-on-one fights...

Play as Jedah, B. B. Hood, Q-Bee, Lilith, Demitri, Morrigan, Anakaris, Victor, L. Raptor, Hsien-Ko, J. Talbain, Felicia, Rikuo, Sasquatch, Bishamon, Donovan, Pyron or Huitzil, and conquer the enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX - Maximum Remix (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk proved the skating games can work to great effect. Now Dave Mirra is here to prove that BMX is here to stay, thanks to the boys at Acclaim Entertainment. Choose from all of the current crop of BMX champs, including 10 times world champion Dave Mirra, Ryan Nyquist, Joey Garcia, Shaun Butler &amp; heaps more, and ride your way through 12 highly detailed environments, with vert ramps, huge jumps and track racing. Multiplayer gaming is also thrown in, allowing two players to go head-to-head in a game of B-M-X (a unique variation of the HORSE basketball game). All this plus official sponsors clothing, bikes and advertising boards plus a huge soundtrack featuring Cypress Hill, Deftones and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Max Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Die Hard Trilogy (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Die Hard Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Die Hard Trilogy is split into three games, each game representing one of the movies, obviously.  

Die Hard 1 is a third person shooter in a style similar to Tomb Raider.  You are John McClane and must fight through twenty floors of terrorists in the Nakatomi Plaza.  The game has an invisible wall effect which allows you to see John even in small hallways.

Die Hard 2 is a first person rail shooter in the vein of Virtua Cop or Mad Dog McCree.  Once again you take the role of John  McClane firing upon terrorists who happen to be ransacking the Washington/Dulles Airport in search of a South American dictator and druglord.

Die Hard 3 is a fast-paced taxi racer through the city.  John must this time speed through New York City defusing bombs and ramming evildoers off the road behind the wheel of a cab.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon World (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Digimon World</name>
		<desc>It is your goal to roam the dangerous countryside with your trained Digimon battling other lost Digimon. A victorious battle permits them to return home to the abandoned File Island. The main one-player mode on Digimon World is where the mysterious story unfolds as you raise your immature Digimon. Digimon are dependant on you for happiness, food, and parental guidance to guide their behavior (similar to the popular Tamagotchi toy).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BEC</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon World 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Digimon World 2</name>
		<desc>Digimon World 2the second game in the Digimon World series brings us to an all-new world in which we must raise digimon to fight off the evil trying to invade. In the previous Digimon World, you played as a young boy who was called to the Digital World in order to save the digimon from a terrible fate and had a partner digimon which needed your care. In this second game, your role is that of a new Guard Tamer who's destined to protect the Digital city, and the Digital world. Now you can fight in all new 3-on-3 battles. There is now a way for you to raise your digimon party to higher levels, and digivolve them to the new 'mega' level, unseen in the previous game (where 'ultimate' level was the limit). The new DNA-Digivolving gives you even further ways to gain new and more powerful digimon.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010519T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BEC</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon World 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Digimon World 3</name>
		<desc>Digimon World 3 is an RPG that follows the adventures of Junior and his two friends as they take part in MMORPG called Digimon Online. Upon starting, the player will select a trio of Digimon from three initial sets. Once in the world of Digimon Online however, the three friends are informed that the system is in dire need of repairs and that they'll stay until the repairs are complete.
Featuring a top-down isometric perspective, players must explore the online world and battling other "tamers" while learning more about the hackers that have invaded the game.
The 3D Battles are turn-based, and features use of items and special techniques. Keeping with the Anime on which it is based, Digimon are also able to Digivolve into more powerful creatures during battle.
As your Digimon take damage, a blast meter gradually fills. When full, it allows the creature to Blast Digivolve, imbuing it with an increase in attack level. Tamers can also merge two Digimon using the DNA Digivolve ability, which will yield an all-new Digimon who performs a powerful attack before disappearing. </desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BEC</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis</name>
		<desc>An abandoned research complex on a remote jungle island, a team of special forces operatives, a horde of vicious velociraptors, and one big, mean Tyrannosaurus rex constitute the setting and cast of Dino Crisis, the latest masterpiece from the makers of Resident Evil.
 Dr. Edward Kirk is supposed to be dead. Three years ago while working to establish a new type of energy technology code-named Third Energy, an experiment went awry and terminated the brilliant scientist's life -- or so it was thought. It was recently learned, however, that Dr. Kirk is very much alive and continuing his work at a Borginia Republic research facility on Ibis Island.
 In order to investigate the situation, an elite special forces team including agents Regina, Gail and Rick was sent. The three expected another routine mission, but what they got was an all-out fight for their lives against an enemy they surely had never been trained to face -- dinosaurs!
 Luckily, Regina isn't restricted to limited firepower, as she'll come across shotguns, dart guns, and other weapons throughout the island. To gain access to the keys, code disks, and ID cards necessary for continued exploration, Regina must solve a variety of puzzles.
 Dino Crisis has three possible endings with a great deal of secrets becoming available after each has been viewed. These include new weapons, new costumes, and a "Wipe Out" mode in which you must defeat a certain number of dinosaurs within a designated time period.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis 2</name>
		<desc>Dino Crisis 2 is a third-person shooter video game for the Sony PlayStation, published by Capcom in North America, released on September 13, 2000 and publish by Virgin Interactive in Europe, release on November 4, 2000. It was developed by Capcom Production Studio 4. The game is the sequel to Dino Crisis and was followed by Dino Crisis 3 in 2003 and was ported to Microsoft Windows that same year.
 The story follows the events of the last game, where Regina is now on another mission involving a facility located close to the fictional Edward City, where a major anomaly has caused the whole island to be transported back in time to the era of the dinosaurs, along with all the human inhabitants. Regina is sent on a rescue mission with her new ally Dylan Morton, who has a strange connection to the events on the island. The player's control switches between Regina and Dylan at specific points in the game.
 </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior VII (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior VII</name>
		<desc>In "Dragon Warrior VII", you are a 16 year old son of a fisherman living on a small island called Estard. There is nothing else on the planet beside this island and the vast ocean surrounding it. One day, you and two friends make a discovery and realize the the world was once much more than Estard Island. So what caused it to disappear? In order to find that out, you travel to the past, where you hope to solve the mystery and to restore the present world the way it was before.

"Dragon Warrior VII" shares with its  predecessor the job system: you can assign character classes ("jobs") to your party members, and learn many different abilities, depending on the job you have chosen. The game maintains the traditional style of the series, including strictly medieval setting and first-person turn-based combat.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heart Beat</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver - You Are the Wheelman (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Driver : You Are the Wheelman</name>
		<desc>As Tanner, you're going undercover to be the wheelman for a crime syndicate in order to break open a big case. On the way, you'll eliminate competition, drive getaway cars, scare some people silly, evade plenty of police, dodge bad guys, smash through a few windows, save your love interest, and much more through four cities (Miami, San Francisco, Los Angeles, and New York).

Perform authentic manuevers like donuts, 180 spin, 360 spin, reverse 180 spin, and more as you cut through alley ways, across sidewalks and parks, smash park benches and and drive over traffic cones. Many different cars to try (most you'll recognize). Will you save the day?</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Einhaender (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Einhänder</name>
		<desc>In 2192, a new city, Selene, is built on the moon. Over the years, Selene grows larger, more powerful, and more independent of the Earth - to the point that the moon and Earth battle in a war that winds down without a definite victory for either side. In 2242, war breaks out again - the Earth slowly begins to win... except for the efforts of an experimental Selene technology known as Einhänders: flying machines with a "hand" that allows them to change weaponry mid-battle.

On December 12, 2245, Selene sends down 3 Einhänders in a last attempt to turn the tide of the war. You get to choose the craft to pilot, and it's up to you to battle your way through the Earth's monstrous defenses and win the battle.

The game is a traditional side-scrolling shooter, with rendered 3D backgrounds and enemies. The atmosphere of the game is very "industrial", down to the German industrial music playing in the background (think Einsturzende Neubauten mixed with Lords of Acid). The weapon-switching and claiming is an integral part of the game, as weapons have limited shots. This forces a bit more strategy than the usual button-mashing shooters inspire.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy V (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Anthology : Final Fantasy V</name>
		<desc>The Elemental Crystals...the life source of the planet. With them, gentle winds blow, the seas are active, fire burns bright, and the earth is full of life. All seems well in the world, until the wind suddenly stops, the sea begin to grow stagnant, the heat of fire becomes scarce, and the earth begins to wither. King Tycoon, sensing a premonition of evil, hurries off to check on the Wind Crystal, only to witness it destroy itself.

Meanwhile, a young traveler named Butz is camping in a field when a giant meteor strikes the planet. When he heads out to examine the meteor, he is shocked to find a young girl named Lenna, who is the princess of Tycoon, and a old man named Galuf, who is on a critical mission. Later, joined by Faris, a pirate captain, the foursome must travel the land in search of the destructor of the Crystals, and save the planet at any cost!

Final Fantasy V featured many new gameplay options and tactics, including an improved Job/Ability system (like in Final Fantasy Tactics), the return of the ATB (Active Time Battle) turn system, and all of the classic FF gameplay you've come to know and love!

Final Fantasy V was released as a stand-alone game in Japan, and again in Final Fantasy Collection. Its U.S. debut was as part of Final Fantasy Anthology. It was also later ported to the Gameboy Advance, adding 4 new Jobs, a new 30-floor dungeon, a bestiary, a music player, the ability to quick save anywhere, a few extra pieces of equipment, and a newly update translation.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy VI (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Anthology : Final Fantasy VI</name>
		<desc>
Set in a fantasy world with a technology level equivalent to that of the Second Industrial Revolution, the game's story focuses on a group of rebels as they seek to overthrow an imperial dictatorship. The game features fourteen permanent playable characters, the most of any game in the main series. Final Fantasy VI was the first game in the series to be directed by someone other than producer and series creator Hironobu Sakaguchi; the role was filled instead by Yoshinori Kitase and Hiroyuki Ito. Yoshitaka Amano, a long-time contributor to the Final Fantasy series, returned as the image and character designer, while regular composer Nobuo Uematsu wrote the game's score, which has been released on several soundtrack albums.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Chronicles - Chrono Trigger (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Chronicles : Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>What begins as a carefree day at the Millennial Fair for a young man named Crono turns into a huge adventure. He will be thrusted into the ultimate trip through time and space, encountering new friends, defeating the forces of evil, and encountering the one who would destroy the flow of time.
Chrono Trigger is a role-playing game, with the usual game mechanics fare. As the characters grow in power, not only their ability scores increase, but they also learn new "Techs".
The game utilizes the ATB (active time battle) combat system from Final Fantasy game. Apart from normal Techs, it is possible to use Double and Triple Techniques.There are no random battles in the game, as all the enemies are visible on screen, and it's even possible to just pass by them entirely.
The game allows you to face your ultimate adversary at different points of time, which leads to several different endings.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Chronicles - Final Fantasy IV (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Chronicles : Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>This classic adventure includes 18 towns and castles, dozens of magical spells, and hundreds of monsters, weapons, and items to help players on their quests. The game features the astounding music, challenging adventures, and interesting storyline that are the hallmarks of the Final Fantasy franchise</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IX (USA) (Rev 1).m3u</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IX</name>
		<desc>Corruption -- the root of all evil. Alexandria's Queen Brahne was once presented as a noble and caring ruler, who would throw lavish festivals to show appreciation for her supporters. Recently, she became involved in secretive deals with mysterious people. Matters took a turn for the worse when a renegade troupe kidnapped her daughter and changed the fate of a once peaceful world.
 As young Zidane Tribal and his party interrupted a renowned play and kidnapped Princess Garnet Til Alexandros, things began to fall apart. The queen fired cannons and decimated her kingdom in an attempt to prevent the terrorist organization, but her attacks failed and the troupe escaped with their lives intact.
 Princess Garnet wished someone would take her away from her oppressing mother and life; the only world she knew was that of Alexandria and its large metropolitan areas. Zidane Tribal and his troupe had come at the perfect time. An innocent black mage known as Vivi Orunitia and a Pluto Knight named Adelbert Steiner, who was sworn to protect the princess at all costs, were also part of the crusade.
 Although Adelbert Steiner had objections, the characters formed a pact to overthrow Queen Brahne and prevent her harmful attack in the surrounding areas of Alexandria. After the princess was abducted, Brahne hired assailants to create destructive black mage warriors. With a few of her knights and the mages, the queen unleashed a series of unmitigated attacks on neighboring towns -- she would do anything to recapture Princess Garnet.
 But what are the queen's true intentions?</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Origins (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Origins : FF I &amp; FF II</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Origins is a re-release of Final Fantasy and Final Fantasy II. Both games have added CGI cut scenes, updated graphics, and added content. It also includes art galleries of Yoshitaka Amano's illustrations. Final Fantasy II was never released in the USA.

Final Fantasy is an RPG/adventure came where you choose four characters (from six different character classes). It features turn based combat, kill monsters for gold / experience to advance levels and equipment. 

Final Fantasy II is also similar but has several different aspects. There is no experience system is not based off of killing monsters. The more you use a weapon/armor the more proficient you get at it. It also features a keyword system. During a conversion some words can be memorized then you can ask NPCs keywords to further the plot, get more information, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Tactics is a tactical role-playing game developed and published by Square (now Square Enix) for the Sony PlayStation video game console. It is the first game of the Final Fantasy Tactics series and was released in Japan in June 1997 and in the United States in January 1998. The game combines thematic elements of the Final Fantasy video game series with a game engine and battle system unlike those previously seen in the franchise. In contrast to other 32-bit era Final Fantasy titles, Final Fantasy Tactics uses a 3D, isometric, rotatable playing field, with bitmap sprite characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VII (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VII</name>
		<desc>Set in a dystopian world, Final Fantasy VII's story centers on mercenary Cloud Strife who joins with several others to stop the megacorporation Shinra, which is draining the life of the planet to use as an energy source. As the story progresses, the situation escalates and Cloud and his allies face Sephiroth, the game's main antagonist.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19970815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VIII (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VIII</name>
		<desc>A member of an elite military team, Squall is forced into a conflict beyond imagination.  To survive, he must contend with a desperate rival, a powerful sorceress, and his own mysterious dreams.

* Realistic, detailed characters and background graphics enhanced by a breathtaking musical score
* An epic story based on the theme of love, set in a massive new world
* New Junction System allows characters to be customized with powerful magic spells drawn from enemies
* Nearly an hour of stunning motion-captured CG cinemas seamlessly integrated into gameplay</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission 2 (Japan) [T-En by Front Mission 5 Team Patch F].chd</path>
		<name>Front Mission 2</name>
		<desc>The player assumes the role of an OCU Wanzer squad in 22nd century Aroldesh. One night while on routine patrol, the OCU base is infiltrated and attacked. Civil war is now loosed upon the nation of Aroldesh as a coup d'etat is staged.  

Front Mission 2 is the first 3D title in the strategy/RPG series and the first to hit the Playstation. An isometric view is used to navigate your Wanzers (mech) on the battlefield.  When the player engages an enemy the view switches to a 3rd-person perspective which shows the results of the battle. Between missions you can upgrade your Wanzer and talk with NPCs who will move the story forward. The game features over 30 missions and dozens of skills and weapons to outfit your crew with.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Front Mission 3</name>
		<desc>Front Mission 3 is the third main entry and the fifth entry overall in the Front Mission series. Like other Front Mission titles, Front Mission 3 is part of a serialized storyline that follows the stories of various characters and their struggles involving mecha known as wanzers.
While it is a tactical role-playing game, there is a stronger emphasis on role-playing elements as opposed to strategic elements in Front Mission 3. The game progresses in a linear manner: watch cut-scene events, complete missions, set up wanzers during intermissions, and sortie for the next mission. The player travels to locations on a world map. As the player progresses through the plot, new locations are revealed on the world map. Towns and cities act as intermission points where the player can organize and set up their units for the upcoming mission. New to Front Mission 3 is the Double Feature Scenario - this allows the player to experience two different scenarios that exist independently of one another within the game's storyline. In other words, the player can play through two stories; while they may share common events and environments, the stories are largely unique and in essence are fully-fledged games.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Legends (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Legends</name>
		<desc>"Wizard is about to die."
 Wait just a minute -- we all know that good wizards never die, they just teleport to another dimension! Such is the case with Gauntlet Legends, the 1998 Arcade update to the original 1985 coin-op game that featured four-player simultaneous action set within a fantasy setting. The four character classes (warrior, wizard, valkyrie and archer) have returned in full 3D, but this time they have a few friends! Yet before you can use the new characters, you'll have to first find them during the course of play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost in the Shell (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ghost in the Shell</name>
		<desc>3rd person action game based on the Ghost in the Shell original comic by Masamune Shirow rather than Mamoru Oshi's film. You take the role of a new member in Kusanagi's anti-terrorist squad and get to accomplish missions on your Fuchikoma, (a spider-like AI equiped tank) thanks to which you can jump, stick to walls and ceilings and shoot the hell out of terrorists, all from a 1st or 3rd person point of view. As the missions procede a plot starts to surface concerning a giant skyscrapper, the Aereopolis II, which will eventually be solved after 12 single player missions. Other features include a training sequence, 3D stereo sound and wide anamorphic screen mode for 16x9 TVs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exact</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius Gaiden (Japan) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Gradius Gaiden</name>
		<desc>Evil lurks out there in the universe and only you, aboard your trusty Vic Viper starfighter, can put an end to it. Gradius Gaiden is yet another shooter in the Gradius series.

Gameplay consists of moving your fighter across side-scrolling stages shooting everything in sight and avoiding enemy fire, with your objective being to reach the end and defeat the stage boss to move on. You can collect power-ups which fills your power-up bards and which can then be triggered at any time for a specific effect depending on what bar is active at the moment. 

The game uses 2D graphics with some polygonal elements and features 2-player co-op gameplay as well as the option to select from four starfighters to take into battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo</name>
		<desc>Gran Turismo puts you behind the wheel in realistic races against AI opponents, collecting cars, credits, and trophies. Arcade Mode offers free access to cars and tracks, while Simulation Mode challenges you to earn licenses, win races, and wisely invest in cars and upgrades. The more you win, the more you unlock – including bonus videos and hidden vehicles, some accessible only via cheat devices. With over 180 cars and numerous tracks, it stands as a landmark in racing games.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19980512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo 2 (USA) (Arcade Mode) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo 2 (Arcade Mode)</name>
		<desc>Gran Turismo 2 is fundamentally based on the racing game genre. The player must maneuver an automobile to compete against artificially intelligent drivers on various race tracks. The game uses two different modes: arcade and simulation. In the arcade mode, the player can freely choose the courses and vehicles they wish to use. However, the simulation mode requires the player to earn driver's licenses, pay for vehicles, and earn trophies in order to unlock new courses. Gran Turismo 2 features nearly 650 automobiles and 27 racing tracks.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19991223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo 2 (USA) (Simulation Mode) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo 2 (Arcade Mode)</name>
		<desc>Gran Turismo 2 is fundamentally based on the racing game genre. The player must maneuver an automobile to compete against artificially intelligent drivers on various race tracks. The game uses two different modes: arcade and simulation. In the arcade mode, the player can freely choose the courses and vehicles they wish to use. However, the simulation mode requires the player to earn driver's licenses, pay for vehicles, and earn trophies in order to unlock new courses. Gran Turismo 2 features nearly 650 automobiles and 27 racing tracks.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19991223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Grandia</name>
		<desc>Grandia is a Japanese-style console RPG, with big-eyed anime style characters, that was first released on the Sega Saturn in 1997.  It centers around the story of a young hero named Justin who possesses a mysterious artifact known as the 'Spirit Stone'.  The story takes Justin and friends (who range from a bratty eight year-old to a noble knight and a thief with a short fuse) through distant towns and abandoned ruins of a forgotten civilization (and even the occasional military base) in a search for adventure and secrets long hidden from the world. Grandia makes use of FMV cut-scenes to advance the story.

The characters are represented by 2D sprites which are moved around over 3D backgrounds in towns and dungeons.  Combat is initiated by coming into contact with enemies on the screen, rather than through random battles.  Combat itself occurs in pseudo-real-time, using an 'IP Gauge' to determine when a character takes action. Striking at the right time or with the right ability can even delay or cancel an enemy's turn.

The characters in the game gradually advance in level as they gain experience points for killing monsters. Characters also gain experience based on the weapon (e.g. sword, mace, whip, etc.) or magic (e.g. fire, water, etc.) that they use, powering up their spells and learning new ones from continuous usage.  There are a large number of spells, weapons, and other items to use throughout the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubi Soft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gundam Battle Assault (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Gundam Battle Assault</name>
		<desc>This game is the follow-up to Gundam: The Battle Master. Heero Yuy, the pilot of a Mobile Suit Wing Gundam is on a mission to destroy the remaining enemy Mobile Suits, who are under the command of Treize Khushrenada, in order to stop a war from starting. In the story mode, Heero can pilot any of the available mobile suits to do battle with his enemies. Each suit has its own set of special moves and a super attack. Some of the weapon based special attacks use ammunition which can eventually run out. The super attack can only be used 3 times during each fight. Each suit also has thrusters that can be used to fly in the air a bit. On the defensive side, players can dodge attacks by sidestepping and also can utilize a beam shield which can be used to protect the player from projectile attacks. Mobile suits come with 3 life bars total and fights are decided by trying to deplete all the life bars of an enemy mobile suit.

The game also contains a 2 player versus mode. 

Options allow the player to choose their difficulty level and also let them set the timer during a match to either on or off.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gundam Battle Assault 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Gundam Battle Assault 2</name>
		<desc>Gundam Battle Assault 2 is an one-on-one fighting game, based on the popular anime series "Mobile Suit Gundam" and its various offshoots. You can play as the titular Gundams (giant walking robots) from a wide variety of series. The game features standard fighting game mechanics, with punches, kicks and a variety of combo moves that can be executed by each Gundam. Note that the Mobile Suits aren't as mobile as humans, and thus the fighters' movements are slower and their maneuverability is worse than in most fighting games. 

The game has several playing modes, which must be unlocked by using different Mobile Suits on the various difficulty levels. The available modes are: street mode, story mode, versus (a single duel where you can choose your opponent), two time attack modes (where you must defeat either 8 regular enemies or 4 boss enemies as fast as possible) and survival (defeat as many enemies as possible; fight until you beat all of them, or until one of them beats you.)</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20020718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harmful Park (Japan) [T-En by Hilltop v1.1].chd</path>
		<name>Harmful Park</name>
		<desc>Harmful Park was only released on the Playstation in Japan by a small company named Sky Think Systems. It's your standard 2D side-scrolling shooter, except set in a bizarre amusement park. As the (relatively lengthy) introduction tells you, an evil scientist has taken over Heartful Park and is using it for nefarious purposes. One of his colleagues aims to stop him, but she's old to do it herself. So, she commands her two slacker daughters to save the day, equipping them with some kind of flying motorcycle armed to the teeth with strange weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sky Think System</developer>
		<publisher>Sky Think System</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon - Back to Nature (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon : Back to Nature</name>
		<desc>As an Child you visited your Grandfather´s ranch when vacation plans fell trough. Return to the farm that holds fond childhood memories and rejuvenate it´s long neglected fields. Tend to your livestock and interact with over 50 characters. As you struggle to make the farm something your grandfather would be proud of, one nagging question remains: What ever happened to the little girl that you knew a decade ago?</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Victor Interactive Software</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heart of Darkness (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Heart of Darkness</name>
		<desc>The eternally delayed Heart of Darkness has finally made its way to the PlayStation gaming console! One day, as Andy was in the park with his dog Whiskey, strange things started to happen. Almost in an instant, a vortex to some undiscovered realm opened up and sucked the poor doggie in. Determined to get his pooch back, Andy hopped in a homemade flying contraption and set off on a journey; where he was going, he did not know.
 On his way to this unknown world, Andy was met with some resistance and crash-landed into a wall of pure granite. Upon meeting up with a creepy monster, it was easy to see things were not kosher; this Land of Darkness has been overrun by horrific shadow monsters working in service of the Master of Darkness. It is the player's objective to ultimately destroy this evil nemesis, save Whiskey, and return home with both lives in tact.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amazing Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hogs of War (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Hogs of War</name>
		<desc>Hogs of War is a turn-based tactics video game developed by Infogrames Studios and published by Infogrames Europe. The game is set in a First World War-era where anthropomorphic pigs engage in combat. Play proceeds in a turn-based fashion, with 3D graphics, vehicles, a career-based single-player mode, and voice-over work (both narration and for characters) by British comedian Rik Mayall.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./In Cold Blood (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>In Cold Blood</name>
		<desc>In Cold Blood is adventure and infiltration on Playstation. Seven of the nine missions offered are in fact flashbacks. As John Cord, an MI6 agent with amnesia, you must avoid guards and cameras, defeat security systems and discover the identity of the person who betrayed you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revolution Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Incredible Crisis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Incredible Crisis</name>
		<desc>Incredible Crisis follows the stories of four members of a Japanese family on their grandmother's birthday. As each family member goes through a seemingly normal day, things start to go wrong -- very wrong. Players will be able to live out this family's hair-raising experiences by playing a series of mini-games.
 At its core, Incredible Crisis is a collection of mini-games strung together in order to advance the plot. Games range from a beatmania-style of timed gameplay (where certain buttons are pressed during certain beats) to shooting down airplanes, attacking UFOs, and even a certain "massage" level that is so analogous to a sexual experience that if gamers only heard the instructions and game mechanics, they would swear they were playing a game rated A for adult.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polygon Magic</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./iS - Internal Section (Japan) [T-En by GameHacking.org v1.02].chd</path>
		<name>Is - Internal Section</name>
		<desc>INTERNAL SECTION is best described as a "sound reactive" shooting game. It is set up very similar to the classic arcade game TEMPEST or more recently, the PSX game N2O. All three of these are shooters where the player controls a ship "looking down" and long tunnel or tube and the player can move around inside the cylinder, shooting enemies that it runs to while moving. I will make most of my comparisons to N20 because it is apparent that the two games have a lot of similarities.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Positron</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jade Cocoon - Story of the Tamamayu (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jade Cocoon : Story of the Tamamayu</name>
		<desc>Jade Cocoon is the story of Levant, a young man who lives in the town of Syrus. You guide the silent protagonist on his quest to follow in his presumably dead father's footsteps to become a cocoon master. To do this, he must marry a Na'gi woman, and is betrothed to a girl named Mahbu (voiced by Michelle Ruff). On the day of a large festival in Syrus, the village is attacked by demons known as the Onibubu, which cause many villagers to fall into a deep slumber. An elderly Nagi woman, Garai, repels the Onibubu using Nagi magic before their curse affects everyone.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kartia - The Word of Fate (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Kartia : The Word of Fate</name>
		<desc>A turn-based, strategy RPG, Kartia presents players with two disparate, yet intersecting storylines: one as the shrine warrior, Lacryma Christi; the other as Toxa Classico, an arrogant knight. Having selected a character, players embark on a journey spanning 18 chapters, each of which is preceded by pertinent dialogue and FMV scenes, the former accompanied by character portraits from Yoshitaka Amano (best known for his work on the Final Fantasy series). The titular Kartia represents the lifeblood of the world of Rebus, as it is from this that almost anything can be created. Prior to and during each skirmish, Kartia can be used to fashion spells, equipment, and phantoms by assembling the various elements each entity requires.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kitchen Panic (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Kitchen Panic</name>
		<desc>Incredibly cute platformer in which you play a little brown thing, hopping along through giant kitchen levels filled with gushing tap water, stacks of dishes, vicious serrated knives and tin cans, valuable vegetables, dangerous soap bubbles and so forth.
 The gameplay gimmick here is spin: during a jump you can press up or down to start your character to spinning forward or back. Then when next you press Jump, he'll either launch himself way straight up (backspin) or a long way forward (front spin).
 And of course there's plenty of call to use the spin jumps</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Panther Software</developer>
		<publisher>Panther Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain : Soul Reaver</name>
		<desc>1500 years after Blood Omen: Legacy of Kain, the vampire Kain's decision at the end of that game has finally defeated the human kingdoms and brought the world of Nosgoth under his control. Ruling from a castle built on the Pillars of Nosgoth, Kain has established an empire of six vampire clans, each ruled by a lieutenant, the sons of Kain. Raziel was one such lieutenant, but lost his position through the "insolence" of receiving a new evolutionary "dark gift", the growth of feathery wings, before his master had acquired it. Fearing that Raziel might one day surpass him, Kain tears off Raziel's wings in a fit of range and banishes him into the Abyss.  There, Raziel is lost in time, died and his body consumed. The Elder God recovers Raziel's soul and rebuilds the broken body, not as a living vampire, but as a strange new creature of the underworld. Swearing revenge on Kain, Raziel now phases seamlessly between Nosgoth and it's underworld, using his new powers to become a terrible reaver of souls...

Soul Reaver is a 3rd person action-adventure title that follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans. The player controls the game from behind Raziel's shoulder, moving him in any direction, climbing, attacking, jumping and using specific abilities. Raziel's can grip onto the edge of ledges and his torn wings allow him to glide gently downwards. Raziel can shift through the "material" world into the "spectral" realm at will... but must find specific locations in order to shift back. The two realms mirror one another, with distortions which give access to new areas and platforms. Existing in the material world drains Raziel's life energy at a constant rate.  Throughout the game, energy is recovered by consuming the souls of defeated enemies. If Raziel is able to defeat one of his brothers, he will additionally gain a new ability ("dark gift") upon drinking it's soul. Examples include: the ability to swim, file telekinetic projectiles or the ability to phase through locked gates. Raziel can arm himself with a variety of weapons including spears, daggers, swords, axes, as well as attacking enemies barehanded. Eventually, Raziel will also come across Kain's personal sword (named the Soul Reaver), and will use it to create a powerful energy blade weapon.

The world is left open to Raziel, he can return to areas previously completed and explore the world of Nosgoth at will. Access to certain areas however sometimes  requires the use of gained specific abilities. Many of the puzzles the player will need to solve in this quest are "block puzzles", requiring the placement of certain large structures (usually square blocks), either to activate switches or to build access to out-of-reach areas.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Dragoon, The (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>The Legend of Dragoon</name>
		<desc>Ten thousand years ago, the Divine Tree brought forth all living races. Among them were the powerful Dragons, the resilient humans, and the magical Winglies. For centuries, peace endured—until the Winglies rose in a brutal rebellion, conquering the world and enslaving humanity. Their reign lasted until humans awakened the spiritual power of Dragons, becoming Dragoons and overthrowing their oppressors.
In The Legend of Dragoon, Dart, a young warrior seeking vengeance for his parents' death at the hands of the mysterious Black Monster, becomes entangled in a new crisis. Ancient forces stir, forgotten truths resurface, and a prophecy hints that the past's long‑buried conflict may ignite once more, threatening to merge past and future in a catastrophic destiny.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Computer Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Legaia (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legend of Legaia</name>
		<desc>After creating a massive world with vast oceans, landscapes and an infinite universe, God instituted human beings to keep his creation in order. Upon realization that man was mortally flawed with weaknesses and feelings, he created a mysterious force known as the Seru; these stone objects would aid humans in decisions and day to day functions. Worn as an apparel item, they granted the wearer many strengths and abilities ranging from the movement of heavy objects to flying capabilities. Thus, human life was made easier -- the Seru would forever obey their masters.
 And then the Mist arrived.
 Filled with destructive means and hatred, the Mist covered the human's cultivated lands and destroyed a seemingly eternal bond with the Seru. Instead of loyally helping their masters, the mysterious stones turned against the humans; they became maniacal tools of evil, controlling minds and ruining innocent lives. The human existence was reduced tremendously with few survivors fleeing to uncharted territories. Perhaps the Mist wouldn't find them wherever they ran.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Contrail</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Mana (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legend of Mana</name>
		<desc>A twinkling consciousness became a star that sparkled in the night and banished the darkness. The Mana Goddess acquired consciousness by gazing into the light of that sun. She made Fa´Diel, a great land, but so far an empty one.

In Legend of Mana you control a hero or heroine traveling over the land of Fa’Diel. The game features a land creation system, allowing you to create new locations and story elements by placing mysterious artifacts. Those ancient artifacts are repositories of the land´s long-forgotten memories and the many events that once took place there. As the game advances, you will receive more artifacts and find out more about the land. At home you can raise pet monsters and create powerful golems, forge mighty weapons or refine musical instruments. On your adventures you can meet various interesting characters and fight against gruesome monsters.

The game is extremely non-linear in terms of gameplay. You can explore areas in any order and play through 67 related scenarios. Eventually you will resurrect the Mana Tree and discover the Legend of Mana.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LSD - Dream Emulator (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>LSD - Dream Emulator</name>
		<desc>In LSD the player navigates through a psychedelic dream world. The idea is simply to walk around and explore things in a dream environment. There are many strange environments in this world, and one way to travel through them is by foot. However, if the player bumps into walls or other objects in the game, they will be transported to another environment instantaneously through a system called "linking". Bumping into people, animals, or special objects usually results in a stranger dream.

Each dream can last up to 10 minutes, after which the player will 'wake up', when the screen fades away and the player is sent back to the game's initial menu. However, if the player falls off a cliff or into a hole in the dream, then the player will wake up immediately. There is a graph that appears at the end of each dream that keeps track of the player's state of mind; the states are Upper, Downer, Static and Dynamic, as referring to the environments and the general feel of the dream the player just went through. Past states may have effects on later dreams.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19981022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Asmik</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - Silver Star Story Complete (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Lunar : Silver Star Story Complete</name>
		<desc>Alex, a young boy from a small humble town, enters a life of adventure and intrigue after being chosen as the heir-apparent to the title of "Dragonmaster", guardian of the forces of the planet. With the help of his expanding band of companions, Alex must pass the trials set by ancient dragons to claim his place in history, and stop a powerful sorcerer and former hero, Ghaleon, from controlling the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar 2 - Eternal Blue Complete (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Lunar 2 : Eternal Blue Complete</name>
		<desc>Set one thousand years after the events of The Silver Star, the game follows the adventure of Hiro, a young explorer and adventurer who meets Lucia, visitor from the far-away Blue Star, becoming entangled in her mission to stop Zophar, an evil, all-powerful being, from destroying the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic Carpet (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,Sv).chd</path>
		<name>Magic Carpet</name>
		<desc>Magic Carpet is a conversion of a classic PC game that was also released for the Saturn console.
			Magic Carpet is a very original title. Flying on a carpet itself is original in video games,but the concept and story line make this one of a kind.
			Collect magical powers by shooting the balls (mana) floating around the world and make them your color (white). Then, let your hot air balloons pick them up and bring them to your castle before the other wizards get to your mana and change it to their own color. That's the main thing of the game.
			All of the 13 different beasts that fly or walk around in each of the worlds contain a certain amount of mana, and when destroyed, it's released. You complete a world (there's about 75 of them!) when a certain amount of mana has been stored in your castle.
			A really interesting aspect of mana is that you can access more spells the more you get,there are 20 different spells that can be found in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX</name>
		<desc>Following in the tradition of the Tony Hawk Pro Skater series comes Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX. Choose from eight different professional BMX players and go from course to course accomplishing goals and trick points.
 Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX uses the same game engine seen in Tony Hawk Pro Skater, and has many of the gameplay elements have been retained. The dynamic camera always tracks your BMX rider from behind and switches to an aerial view when performing high jumps on half pipes. Collect magazine covers in each varied level (varying from city parks to warehouses) in order to unlock new levels. Players will have to execute high jumps and perform crazy tricks in the air and by railing metal bars and buildings in order to gain trick points. Enough trick points will allow you to unlock new levels.
 The soundtrack on Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX is also sure to appeal to almost any gamer, as a wide variety of song types have been covered, from rock to hip hop. Groups on the soundtrack include Outkast, Jurassic 5, Dead Prez, Deltron 3030 and Static-X.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shaba Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MDK (USA).chd</path>
		<name>MDK</name>
		<desc>MDK is a 3rd person action/shooter game in which the objective is to basically shoot everything that moves in six massive cities, each with their own sublevels. Because the world is being invaded by aliens, it is up to you and your sidekick Bones to stop the invasion and single handedly save Earth. In order to do so, you must make good use of your special suit, which allows you to do all kinds of things.
 The super-suit comes equipped with many features you'll need to utilize in your journey, such as the sniper helmet. This allows you to zoom in on unsuspecting enemies and fire off shots with pinpoint accuracy. There is also a built in parachute (a ribbon-like device) that enables you to glide between different platforms as well as drop down on intruders.
 Your suit comes equipped with a chain gun that has an infinite supply of ammunition. You can also pick up special items, like a miniature nuclear bomb and powerful upgrades for your chaingun. In addition to running around and shooting, there are also special means of transportation including a surfboard-like jet and a bomber plane that is used to call in air strikes.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19971110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Shiny Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor</name>
		<desc>FIGHT WWII FOR THE FIRST TIME

Tomorrow is D-Day. Tonight you land behind enemy lines. The tide of the war is in your hands. Your are an elite Special Forces agent sent to execute covert operations, search and rescue missions, and commando raids. Fight to win the Medal of Honor in the only game that lets you take on Nazis in WWII.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamWorks</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor - Underground (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor : Underground</name>
		<desc>The year is 1940, and the conquering force of the Third Reich has invaded France. Nazi Germany has marched into Paris and claimed the once proud nation as its own in its further quest for domination of Europe. The allied forces won't be coming to liberate France any time soon, as they have their hands full protecting Great Britain. The perception that the French have simply let Hitler walk into their country without a fight has not endeared the rest of the war-torn world to the cause.
 As a young woman named Manon Batiste, you will be thrust into the world of intrigue and violence that is World War II doing all you can to save your beloved homeland by joining the OSS and traveling the world as a member of the French Underground, taking out Gestapo thugs and the SS so that you might become a seasoned veteran and aid in the ultimate liberation of your nation.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamWorks</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MediEvil (USA).chd</path>
		<name>MediEvil</name>
		<desc>The Evil Wizard Zarok has returned from the dead to wreak havoc on a peaceful land, and it is up to the centuries-dead hero, Sir Daniel Fortesque, to rise from his grave and defeat the very nemesis that put him in that grave.  Wander the land, destroying Zarok's undead minions; collect chalices to grant him more powerful weapons; solve puzzles in order to defeat the evil wizard and restore peace to the land -- so Daniel can go back to his eternal slumber.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Studio Cambridge</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 8 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man 8 : Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>Mega Man 8 (Rockman 8 Metal Heroes in Japan) begins as the robotic hero Mega Man is called to investigate a mysterious energy reading coming from a recent meteor crash on an island. Mega Man discovers that his arch nemesis Dr. Wily has beaten him there and immediately retreats with the energy source. Mega Man is charged with stopping Wily's evil plans to use the energy, as well as discover the purpose of a mysterious, alien robot found at the crashsite.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19970227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Legends (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man Legends</name>
		<desc>THE BLUE BOMBER BLASTS INTO A WHOLE NEW DIMENSION

Mega Man blasts his way into the third dimension in an amazing new adventure. Mega Man Legends combines the best of classic Mega Man action with enormous bosses, a riveting storyline, and all the depth of the hottest RPG.

Explore vast 3-D worlds in your quest to find the treasure of all treasures, the Mother Lode. You'll love the new 3-D graphics, deadly weapons, and non-stop action... unless of course, you're a boss.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Legends 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man Legends 2</name>
		<desc>Mega Man, Roll, and all your favorites are back in an entirely new 3-D adventure! Far away, in an isolated wasteland, a mysterious girl and an infamous treasure have been discovered. It's the legendary "Sealed Key," rumored to unlock an even greater mystery known as the Great Legacy. What power does the Great Legacy hold? Now, a race unfolds as Mega Man and his friends embark on a journey which will alter their destinies forever.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X4</name>
		<desc>It is the year 21XX, following years after the Doppler rebellion and the revelation of the Maverick Virus, a new global Reploid military force, apty-named Repliforce, was founded to combat the ongoing Maverick attacks and uprisings. However, humans quickly began to fear and distrust Repliforce's military power and their methods of fighting Mavericks proved to be very destructive with little disregard for human life. One day, the floating city Sky Lagoon was under attack by Mavericks and Repliforce arrived on the scene after the city has crash landed on the ground, where one of their leaders, Colonel, was being ordered by the Maverick Hunters X and Zero to lower his weapons for questioning as suspects for the incident. Out of pride and contempt towards human government, Colonel refused to comply, and following the accusations behind the Sky Lagoon incident, the Repliforce General decided stage a coup d'état, seeking to create a new utopia just for Reploids. Repliforce were then labeled as Mavericks by the government, thus the Maverick Hunters must fight against their former allies and stop their coup.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X5 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X5</name>
		<desc>Years after the Reploid Wars, all seems peaceful in the world. But peace was not meant to last forever. When the "Eurasia" space colony is attacked by an unknown virus, the call goes out! X and Zero are called back into action to help destroy the colony, which is now on a collision course with Earth, and is expected to collide into the planet in only 16 hours! At the same time, guess who decides to show up once again...give you a hint: his name is a Greek letter.

With all new features like advanced Maverick AI, bigger, more challenging stages, new gameplay features like ducking and swinging on vines and ropes, this is set to be the most insane mission X and Zero have ever had to face!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X6 (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X6</name>
		<desc>Three weeks after the Eurasia space colony incident, the Earth's surface was severely damaged and humans were forced to flee underground to escape from the planet's severe pollution, and Zero is still missing, presumed to be dead. Reploids were sent in to terraform the land in an attempt to make the planet habitable for humans once more, however, a Reploid and former colleague of Alia named Gate discovered something unusual amidst the ruins of Earth — a piece of Zero's DNA. After examining Zero's DNA, Gate became mad with power and an outbreak of bizarre Mavericks occurred. Weeks passed, Isoc, a Reploid scientist and an associate of Gate, announced to the people that a new phenomenon known as "Nightmare" has quickly spread throughout the world, causing Reploids to hallucinate and eventually destroy themselves. Isoc suspects the cause of the outbreak is none other than Zero who been spreading the phenomenon as he goes, much to X's anger and confusion. Isoc rallies Reploids throughout the world to aid the Nightmare Investigators, led by the powerful High-Max, at key locations to track down the source of this new phenomenon as well as Zero. X, along with the Maverick Hunters, must confront the Nightmare Investigators as they try to solve the mystery behind the Nightmare Phenomenon and clear Zero's name.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mobile Suit Gundam - Char's Counterattack (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mobile Suit Gundam - Char's Counterattack</name>
		<desc>The year is 0092. Advances in human technology have transformed the world. Mankind has built colonies in which they reside. But with peace comes-Doubt, disbelief, and eventually war. A group of colonies (similar to Axis) Have named them Zion. Fearing Zion, they have built " Mobile Suits", giant
Robots capable of destroying anything in their path. Fortunately, they were used for good.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BEC</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness</name>
		<desc>Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness is a combination of classic Pac-Man (or in this case, Ms. Pac-Man) action, maze exploration and Sokoban-like puzzle elements. Players take on the role of Ms. Pac-Man and have to save Pac-Land once again. Although the game is in full 3D, players can only move along designated paths.

The four Wonders, mystical regions separated from the rest of Pac-Land by force fields, contains four Gems of Virtue: Generosity, Truth, Wisdom and Courage, each holding enough power to help keep Pac-Land safe from evil. However, an unknown enemy has transformed the Enchanted Castle into a haunted house, in turn starting a chain reaction of evil all around Pac-Land and the four Wonders. It is up to Ms. Pac-Man to enter the 3D designed worlds of the four Wonders and put the evil to rest for good.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NanoTek Warrior (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NanoTek Warrior</name>
		<desc>Nanotek Warrior is probably based (or at least inspired) in the classic Spectrum (and other 8 bits platforms) game Eliminator released and development by Hewson Consultants Ltd.
 In the 23rd century, nanotechnology does man?s bidding. Anything from curing disease to feeding the worlds population has been taken care of by these tiny wondrous nanobots. But what happens when they become self-aware and decided to destroy their oppressors? To save the human race from extinction by its own creation, you are put in control of a new breed of nano war machine designed to fight (and win) this war. Enter NanoTek Warrior.
 A ground-based shoot-em-up by design, the game employs the use of jumping, banking, and strafing as you move forward through 3D tube-like levels. The game is seem from a third-person perspective behind the ship. Some areas place you outside and some inside, but the majority of the game takes place rotating around tubes. This gameplay only differs slightly in boss levels, that allow you to rotate around a central point with no forward motion.
 You can obtain different power-ups including special weapons, health bonuses and extra lives as you play through the game?s 9 levels. Each level is divided into 2 stages, one on tubes and a boss fight afterwards.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tetragon</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oddworld - Abe's Exoddus (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Oddworld : Abe's Exoddus</name>
		<desc>Those nasty Glukons are at it again, intent on oppressing the loveable Mudokons any way they can. Last time, the meanies were manufacturing Mudokon jerky. Now, they've officially taken genocide too far, by forcing blind Mudokons into slave labor to dig up the bones of their fellow deceased. It so happens, by the way, that Mudokon bones add just the right kick to a favorite Glukon recipe, Soulstorm Brew.
 Who's gonna save the day? Our unlikely hero Abe, of course. You remember Abe: that blue-green, loincloth-wearing, six foot-tall Fraggle with chronic digestive problems? Yep, he would have been content to rest on his laurels after rescuing ninety-nine of his Mudokon buddies from extermination in Oddworld: Abe's Oddysee, but a group of disgruntled ghosts elected good ol' Abe to avenge their deaths.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oddworld - Abe's Oddysee (USA) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Oddworld : Abe's Oddysee</name>
		<desc>Abe's Oddysee begins with the eponymous protagonist as a prisoner in RuptureFarms, from which he narrates his story. He and many other Mudokons are slaves to Molluck the Glukkon, the owner of RuptureFarms: "the biggest meat-processing plant on Oddworld". Abe is a contented floor-waxer First Class and currently Employee of the Year.

At the time of the story, the ingredients of the corporation's three major "Tasty Treats" (Scrab Cakes, Paramite Pies, and Meech Munchies) are quickly running out, with the Meeches already extinct. While working late, Abe overhears Molluck's plan to use the Mudokon slaves as meat products called "Mudokon Pops!", which frightens Abe into escaping from the factory.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Omega Boost (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Omega Boost</name>
		<desc>AlphaCore, the world's first sentient cyber-organism, has begun to mistrust its human masters. Slowly, it begins to spread, expanding its capabilities into neighboring systems. By the time the horrified human population discovers its size, AlphaCore controls virtually the entire network. As it defends itself, the humans try to regain control but events suddenly escalate.



 Eventually, AlphaCore declares war on the human population, attacking it with its own unmanned weapons and defense systems. As a result, desperate human scientists construct a time machine -- AlphaCore must be stopped before it achieves sentience! Discovering their plan, the renegade organism steals the time machine and utilizes it to return to the days of the first computer, ENIAC. By integrating its consciousness into ENIAC, AlphaCore hopes to become even more powerful.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PaRappa the Rapper (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>PaRappa the Rapper</name>
		<desc>The rapping pup, PaRappa, dreams of impressing his friend, the beautiful Sunny Funny, and going out on a date with her.  But what he lacks is confidence - help PaRappa rap his way through learning Kung Fu, a driving test, cooking and more, all in order to get the girl.  And remember - You Gotta Believe!

PaRappa the Rapper is a game based on lyrics, music and rhythm.  The game itself is very basic - each stage has a 'teacher', that PaRappa must follow.  You'll see the teacher say some lyrics, and then PaRappa must copy the teacher by pressing the appropriate buttons to repeat those lyrics back.  Rap well, and you'll be able to continue; fudge up the lyrics, and the music will start to distort and the teacher will become displeased.  Continue to mess up and you'll fail the stage.

Of course, the goal is not to copy the teacher, but instead to outperform them - you can do this by improvising in the song's gaps.  Listen to how the song goes, and improvise in time to the music; if you perform well enough, the teacher will step aside, leaving you to freestyle on your own!

The PSP version of the game is a remake of the PlayStation original.  However, it includes a few upgrades, such as a 16:9 display, sharper graphics, game sharing, multiplayer support of up to four players, and the addition of song remixes, which can be downloaded via the internet onto your Memory Stick Duo.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nanaon-Sha</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Rhythm</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve</name>
		<desc>An ordinary day in New York for rookie police officer Aya Brea. Christmas Eve is the present day, and you've decided to visit the opera theater. Now this is where the fireworks begin. Suddenly audience members are set on fire, toasted completely, and it appears that the lead vocal is the source of this burning terror. Yet you appear to be immune, and as a police officer you're always on duty, so you must confront the danger.

There has to be some connection between the two of you, as that seems the only rational explanation. What if mitochondria are a species on its own, more advanced then humankind, and using them only to create environments and civilization for themselves? What if humankind are just hosts? What if mitochondria are the natural enemy of humankind? That would make Aya their natural enemy, so the battle for survival and uncovering the truth has already started.

The game is played over six days, each day bringing its own quest. Environments range from Central Park and the American Museum of Natural History to a police office and hospital, all of them modeled like realistic places and most of them crawling with bloodthirsty mutant animals. Combat is different from traditional RPGs, as while you still take turns attacking and/or using parasite powers, you'll be able to run across the battlefield and dodge enemy fire or even strike from a better angle or behind. As Aya levels up she will gain access to parasite powers, such as healing or supercharging a bullet with energy. These powers will deplete a recharging energy bar, although the bar will recharge slower the longer combat drags on. Aya will find many guns of various types throughout the game, and every gun can be modified with extra stats, either with special items, or by breaking down another gun to move over its bonus stats or special effects. The same is true for armor Aya finds.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve II (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve II</name>
		<desc>Aya Brea is back in a new game. This time there are fewer RPG elements than the first game, and the game plays more like Resident Evil. Battles are now in real-time, and a new range of weapons are available. Defeating enemies rewards money as well as points used to revive and power-up Aya's suppressed Parasite powers, like healing and igniting foes. Weapons and armor now have fixed stats, but attachments can be swapped in and out of them to modify their properties.

After surviving the events of Parasite Eve Aya left her job as a cop and became a member of MIST (Mitochondrion Investigation and Suppression Agency) in order to hunt down the remnant mutants spawned by Eve's awakening. In the year 2000 a new breed of Neo Mitochondrion takes over the Akropolis Tower in downtown LA. Aya is called in and uncovers a secret organization that threatens all humanity.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Persona (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Persona</name>
		<desc>In the near future, mankind has conquered dimensional travel but the door we have opened swings both ways. The peaceful city you have grown up in has become a haven for dark creatures from another world-Demons! Now it's up to you and your friends to harness the hidden power within you by entering the fantasy game known as Persona.

You awaken with incredible abilities that you will need to defeat the scores of Demon invaders and cleanse the land of their forces. Converse with them before doing battle to determine your best course of action. Fight them or enlist their aid in your mission. Either way, you are set for the fantasy adventure of a lifetime!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Persona 2 - Eternal Punishment (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Persona 2 : Eternal Punishment</name>
		<desc>The follow-up to 1996's Revelations Series: Persona, Persona 2 is a role-playing game pitting high-school teenagers against demons. While investigating the rumor of a curse at the Seven Sister's High School, magazine editor Mary Amano comes face-to-face with a murderer. A mysterious man by the name of Tatsuya Suou saves her, but from this moment on her life is irrevocably changed.
 As with many RPGs, players can gather a party of characters with distinct personalities and attacks. When a random battle begins, the player must first decide upon specific attacks and character turn-order before the fighting begins. Battles will continue until one side is eliminated, although there is also an option to partake in more traditional turn-based battles. Personas, the characters' powerful alter egos, can be used in battle to perform some of the more devastating attacks in the game. That said, not all encounters in the game need to be solved through fisticuffs.
 By using the game's Contact system, players can negotiate with demons and ask them questions. Each character in the party has a different way of negotiating and using the correct negotiator can mean the difference between a successful or failed negotiation. Success will sometimes result in the player receiving money, information, or Tarot Cards -- powerful items that can be used to summon new Personas.
 </desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-C Stunt Copter (USA).chd</path>
		<name>R/C Stunt Copter</name>
		<desc>R/C Stunt Copter is a highly realistic simulation of flying a miniature R/C Helicopter that, due to being developed by Shiny Entertainment (the mad men behind MDK and Earthworm Jim),  has a much bigger sense of humor than is necessary for a game of it's genre...

The following text  is quoted directly from this game's actual manual!

"Let me make something perfectly clear: You will NEVER beat this game. I think that's important enough for repeating: You will NEVER beat this game.
I will wait a second while the ramifications of that sink in.
Now, I know you're sayiong one of these things right now:
a) I can beat any game.
b) Why the heck would I play a game I can never win?
c) Whatchu talkin' 'bout Willis?"

That text alone should give you a taste of what you're in for...</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R4 - Ridge Racer Type 4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>R4 : Ridge Racer Type 4</name>
		<desc>Powering beyond RIDGE and RAGE RACER, high-speed control and advanced dynamics accekerate the rush of a first class victory.

-In-depth Grand Prix Mode
-Incredible two-player action
-40+ unique car models with over 300 variations
-Hyper-evolved graphics for the supreme racing experience</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19990501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RayCrisis - Series Termination (USA).chd</path>
		<name>RayCrisis : Series Termination</name>
		<desc>An ambitious and unethical scientist, a secret experiment gone horribly awry, and an artificially intelligent supercomputer gone mad; all the necessary ingredients for the imminent extinction of mankind. You are humanity's last hope, a hotshot pilot given the unenviable task of flying an experimental fighter into the dark heart of the Con-Human Network. Seize the controls of three Wave Rider spacecraft, each equippped with the WR-01 primary weapon array, WR-02 secondary lock-on laser system, and WR-03 single-use weapon for emergency situations. RayCrisis: Series Termination is the final entry in Taito's acclaimed trilogy of shooters, and it bombards your CRT with an abundance of fourth-generation optical stimulation: multilevel scrolling, transparency and lighting effects, and enough polygons to overload your cerebral cortex. Dodge, weave, and blast through two play modes, disintegrating wave after wave of relentless bogeys, to achieve high scores and unlock hidden bonuses. Prepare your senses, reinforce your nerves, and limber your trigger finger - the final assault has begun!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Rayman</name>
		<desc>Rayman to the rescue! He must free the Electoons, defeat Mr. Dark, save the Great Protoon from its mysterious kidnapper, and restore harmony to the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2 - The Great Escape (USA) (En,Fr,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Rayman 2 : The Great Escape</name>
		<desc>Rayman 2: The Great Escape is an action-adventure video game developed by Ubi Soft Montpellier.

Rayman 2 takes place in a world called the Glade of Dreams, and revolves around its invasion and occupation by an armada of interstellar Robo-Pirates, led by Admiral Razorbeard. Prior to the invasion, the Robo-Pirates destroyed over one hundred planets in the galaxy, with the intention of enslaving their inhabitants. Upon the invasion of the Glade of Dreams, the Robo-Pirates were battled against by Rayman, Globox, and other allies. After some battles, Rayman's capture occurs after the explosion of the Primordial Core. Ly the Fairy telepathically communicates with Rayman explaining the consequences of the damage, with the core's shattering into 1000 Yellow Lums, and the capture of many fighters. Rayman's powers are also lost due to this, and he finds himself captured by the Robo-Pirates at the beginning of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Director's Cut - Dual Shock Ver. (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil : Director's Cut</name>
		<desc> After receiving a distress call from the Bravo Team, an elite group from S.T.A.R.S (Special Tactics And Rescue Squad) flew into the desolate Raccoon City. Apparently, the team had uncovered something concerning the Umbrella corporation -- a biotech research company. But then, without warning, the Bravo Team vanished into thin air.
 Upon landing in the small city, the members of S.T.A.R.S began to investigate. They heard some strange noises coming from the surrounding woods and realized the sounds were getting closer. Scared, they took off running and kept on until they came to a large, ominous mansion. Seeking safety they entered, locking the door behind them. Their adventure had just begun.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 - Dual Shock Ver. (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 (Leon Kennedy Disc)</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil 2 takes place two months after the events of the first game and is set in Raccoon City, a Midwestern mountain community whose residents have been turned into zombies by the T-virus, a biological weapon developed by the pharmaceutical company Umbrella. In their escape from the city, the two protagonists Leon S. Kennedy and Claire Redfield encounter other survivors and are confronted by William Birkin, the mutated creator of the even more powerful G-virus.
 Previously confined to an old mansion, the Umbrella corporation's legacy of fatal mutations has spilled over into nearby Raccoon City. The once peaceful town is now overrun with zombies and all manner of genetic mutations. New police recruit Leon Kennedy and Claire Redfield; the sister of STARS agent Chris Redfield, find themselves in the middle of an experiment gone horribly wrong. </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3 : Nemesis</name>
		<desc>Join Jill Valentine, the heroine and amazing survivor of the notorious disaster at the mansion, as her nightmare continues. After resigning from S.T.A.R.S. Jill now prepares to head out of Raccoon City...but it's not going to be easy. Caught in a town crawling with flesh eating zombies, more than ever she must rely on brute force and cunning to find a way to escape alive. This unique adventure intricately reveals more of Umbrella Corporation's nightmarish plot and picks up just hours before the events from Resident Evil 2.

More zombies, more terror, and even more evil.
More challenging enemies that come back to life at any time.
Face off against the most terrifying mutations stalking the streets of Raccoon City.
More detailed character actions: Try the dodge move to avoid an enemy's attack.
Interact with the environment like never before: Use background objects defensively.
A unique new drama which reveals more details of Umbrella Corporation's devious activities from the Resident Evil series.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rival Schools - United by Fate (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Rival Schools : United by Fate</name>
		<desc>What do you get when you cross Street Fighter with a bunch of school kids? You get another classic Capcom beat 'em up. 

Featuring plenty of new faces, and heaps of new moves to work with, this is a full conversion of the arcade game, with the added bonus of a second disk. In this second disk, you get new modes including Lesson (teach yourself new moves), Group (select two to four characters for a group battle), League (choose two to six characters and then fight in a league battle), Tournament (tournament battle with up to eight characters), Cooperate (four-player simultaneous player), one-player game, and a specialized versus mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SaGa Frontier (USA).chd</path>
		<name>SaGa Frontier</name>
		<desc>Saga Frontier is a fantasy / sci-fi anime style RPG. It's set in a huge world (30 zones). You choose one of seven characters to defeat the game and the game stores the data from the chosen character which affect what happens once you play the game with one of the other six characters. The game features a LOT of side quests.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SaGa Frontier 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>SaGa Frontier 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to  Saga Frontier, but also to the less known SNES  Romancing SaGa series, "Saga Frontier 2" allows you to play the stories of two main characters - a young prince Gustave XIII, who has been exiled from his homeland because he was unable to use the mysterious power of Anima and to become a worthy successor to the throne, and William Knights, a treasure hunter, who strives to find ancient artefacts containing great powers. Their stories are connected to each other, and each story occupies almost a lifetime: the characters grow up and die, new characters are born, etc. 

"Saga Frontier 2" continues the non-linear gameplay traditions of the SaGa series. You can visit all towns at your wish and at any time, recruit anyone to your party, and freely upgrade your party members by gaining new abilities and distributing them among your characters. You can learn magic spells by collecting artefacts, and combining them to produce more powerful types of magic. Similar to Konami's  Suikoden series, there are three types of combat: one-on-one (duel), turn-based party combat, and strategic army battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Silent Hill</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill is a 1999 survival horror video game for the PlayStation. The first in a series about a mysterious town of the same name, Silent Hill generated a direct sequel, three indirect sequels, a prequel and a film adaptation. The game was included in Sony's Greatest Hits and Platinum Range of budget titles as a result of strong sales. A reinterpretation of the game was developed for the Wii, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable.
The plot focuses on Harry Mason as he searches for his daughter, Cheryl, who has disappeared following a car accident which left Harry unconscious. He finds Silent Hill to be largely abandoned, shrouded in a thick fog, snowing out of season, filled with monsters and being over taken by a hellish otherworld. As Harry scours the town, he begins learning about the history of Silent Hill and stumbles upon a cult ritual undertaken to bring a god to Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Silent</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skullmonkeys (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Skullmonkeys</name>
		<desc>Skullmonkeys is the successor title to The Neverhood, which came out only on PC (and, in Japan, as "Klaymen Klaymen" on PSX). The game is an old-school jump and run type of game, with a large number of FMVs. The entire game is molded in clay.

The player takes control of Klaymen throughout the game in an attempt to put a stop to the main opponent, being Klogg, who wants to destroy Klaymen's homeworld, The Neverhood, via a huge robot called "Evil Engine No. 9". He uses an army of extremely dumb skullmonkeys to stop Klaymen in his quest; With the exception of several strange, clay birds, each and every enemy in the game is a monkey. The game features music with lyrics by Terry Scott Taylor.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Neverhood</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speed Punks (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Speed Punks</name>
		<desc>Speed Freaks is a fast go-cart game in a cartoony setting, featuring six different characters and twelve different tracks.

The game can be played in four different single-player modes or in multi-player mode with up to four people.

Several different pick-ups and power-ups can be found and used to defeat the rivals on the track, including homing missiles, remote bombs and stealth mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Computer Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man is the first 3D game to star the popular web-slinger.  It is loosely based on Spider-Man: The Animated Series and Spider-Man Unlimited and features some of the voice cast from each and similar character designs.

Peter Parker is attending a demonstration of the reformed Dr. Otto Octavius's new invention when an imposter Spider-Man steals the device.  Spider-Man must work to clear his name and uncover the sinister motives behind the device's theft.

This game features appearances not only by most major Spider-Man characters, but cameos by numerous other characters from the Marvel Universe, such as the Human Torch, Punisher, Daredevil and Captain America.

Spider-Man's webs are greatly emphasized.  He can use them both for navigational purposes, like swinging or ziplining, and for offensive and defensive combat, such as tying up a villain, coating his fists with web for extra oomph, or building a protective shield.  His web supply is limited though and he must find new cartridges or risk running out.  The wall-crawling powers are also prominently features.  Spider-Man can cling to any wall or ceiling.  This is used for basic environmental navigation and for stealth as there are many sequences where you crawl over the heads of unsuspecting thugs, or drop down and catch them off-guard.

Combat is based around Spider-Man's ability to jump, kick, punch and web.  By combining these with direction and in various combinations, Spider-Man is able to throw objects such as furniture, hurl web balls, yank enemies into melee range and follow up with a flurry of hits, among other things.  There are a number of boss-battles as well, all of which are puzzle-based.

Missions vary from the fairly common fight-your way-to-the-goal or find-the-key-that-unlocks-the-door types to races to catch some or evade them or just trying to avoid the police.

There are several side goals in addition the main mission including multiple unlockable Spider-Man costumes and numerous hidden comic book covers to find.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Neversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Spyro : Year of the Dragon</name>
		<desc>Thieves have kidnapped a brood of dragon eggs, while, elsewhere in the Dragon Lands, a gateway to the Forgotten World has been uncovered. Sent to recapture the eggs, Spyro the Dragon, and his best friend Sparx, face a journey into uncharted territory against his most fearsome enemy yet - the Sorceress! All new playable characters, frantic challenges and new exciting worlds to explore - the Year of the Dragon begins here!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Spyro 2 : Ripto's Rage!</name>
		<desc>Ripto's Rage is the second game in the Spyro the Dragon series, which started with Spyro the Dragon in 1998. The protagonist of the series, Spyro, is placed in the land of Avalar, rather than the Dragon Worlds, where the previous installment was set. A dinosaur-riding sorcerer, known as Ripto, has invaded the world of Avalar, and is wreaking havoc on its citizens with his magic. The player, as Spyro, must travel through the world of Avalar and undo the damage done by Ripto.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro the Dragon (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Spyro the Dragon</name>
		<desc>Spyro the Dragon is a platform game developed by Insomniac Games for the PlayStation. It stars the title character, a young purple dragon named Spyro and his dragonfly friend, Sparx, and is the first game in the Spyro the Dragon series. The first game was massively popular at its initial release and Spyro would later become one of the most recognizable, popular and respected gaming icons for the PlayStation gaming console. Spyro's best friend, Sparx the dragonfly, acts like the player's health meter and assists in gathering gems. The various dragons Spyro unfreezes along the way are also key characters in Spyro's progression through the game. Gnasty Gnorc is the main antagonist, who froze all the dragons of the land in crystal.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Ocean - The Second Story (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Star Ocean : The Second Story</name>
		<desc>Star Ocean: The Second Story is a world of magic, science, space travel and deadly demons! Enter a world where love knows no bounds, the evil is neverending and good can overcome all if the heart is just and true. Featuring three battle modes, the ability to master skills to create items and an emotional level for each of the characters, Enix has pulled out all the stops in their latest (and first) title to be brought to the North American PlayStation.
 Star Ocean: The Second Story tells the stories of Claude C. Kenni, son of Ronixis J. Kenny, and Rena Lanford, a young girl living on the planet Expel. Claude, having recently been commissioned as an Ensign in the Earth Federation, is given his first mission under the supervision of his father. This first mission is to survey the planet Milocinia, where a mysterious energy field appears. Once they arrive, they find an alien ruin, filled with mostly broken machinery. Finding a mysterious device in the center of it, Claude begins to examine it close-up, despite orders to keep away from it. As he approaches, the machine activates, teleporting him to Expel.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Steel Harbinger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Steel Harbinger</name>
		<desc>In Steel Harbinger, a darkly futuristic running, jumping, 3-D shoot-'em-up, you must guide Miranda through certain areas of Kansas, Las Vegas, San Francisco, Houston, Cape Canaveral, Washington, the Antarctic, an alien planetoid, and the Moon. In each level you'll have specific missions to accomplish such as killing aliens, finding special weapons, saving humans, opening secret rooms, activating defense facilities, and destroying key enemy sites. You can teleport between locations by finding teleport cards and telepads. Access to specific buildings and other restricted areas can be gained with pass cards that you will find hidden throughout the levels. In addition to the standard action, you can also commandeer trucks, hovercraft, floating discs, and tanks.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19961012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mindscape</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika.

The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry. </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Suikoden (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Suikoden</name>
		<desc>Loosely based on the classic medieval Chinese novel "Water Margins" (Shuihuzhuan) by Shi Nai'an. The game is a fantasy RPG set in an imaginary universe, its main theme being political struggle. The hero of the game is the young son of Theo McDohl, a general who serves the Scarlet Moon Empire, presently controlling the land of Toran. Through a series of events the hero becomes involved in a rebellion against the Empire, led by an organization known as the Liberation Army. Will the hero find a new home there, will he be able to tear himself away from everything that has been sacred to him, including his own father?

Suikoden is a console-style RPG with several unusual additions. There are three kinds of combat in the game, the most common one being the traditional turn-based party combat (players can have up to six people in their active party). Magic runes can be equipped on the player's characters which allow limited usage of offensive and healing spells. There are also army battles, where the player must control whole units of fighters, archers, magicians, etc., and one-on-one fights.

The game allows the player to build and customize a castle, which serves as their home base and fortress.108 characters can be recruited in the game, a tribute to 108 Stars Of Destiny in "Water Margins". Many of those characters will be available as active party members and participate in battles, while others will act as strategy advisers, or enhance the castle itself in various ways.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Suikoden II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Suikoden II</name>
		<desc>Sequel to the early PlayStation RPG. As a member of the Alliance, a military force only really hinted at in the original, you play the unwitting hero of the game: an orphan who has been raised by a quiet, unassuming battle hero in a seemingly ancient war. Alongside you in the ranks is your best friend Jowy, a boy born of nobility but who has never been able to receive approval in his stubborn father's eyes. As the game begins, you are immediately tossed into a tale of political strife, betrayal and war on a grand scale beyond your scope in the early stages. As the game wears on, the plot will twist, turn and develop in numerous ways that expose the personalities of each of the characters involved. The battle system is turn-based, with the option to equip Runes for special abilities, combine party member attacks to create chain combos or devastating spells, and the option to run the battle in Auto mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Burst right into the feverish puzzle action that combines irresistable, addictive fun with famous Capcom characters. Beat your opponent to the punch by stacking block after block in strategic patterns and color combinations. Be the first to fill the opponent's screen with blocks and K.O. You win! But get ready for more because you can't play just once!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter</name>
		<desc>Gabriel Logan, one of the government's top covert agents, must neutralize the terrorists that threaten Washington D.C. and destroy a biological weapon that has been built to end the lives of millions of innocent people. 

Syphon Filter is an action game played from the 3rd person. Players take the role of Gabiel Logan as well as other CBDC agents. 
To successfully complete the mission, players must utilize each of the character's skills accordingly. Logan is able to kneel, crouch, walk, roll, climb, jump and run to meet his objectives.

The action unfolds over thirteen missions that are chock full of dangers, hazards and puzzles.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidetic</developer>
		<publisher>989</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter 2 (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the previous year's Syphon Filter, Syphon Filter 2 adds new features such as a two player mode, new locations, new weapons, and more.

The game compares to Goldeneye on the N64.
It's a shooter, but you must also use strategy.  You have a health meter, so it's not a "one shot and you're dead" type of game. You must complete missions, or battle it out in a deathmatch with your friends, or enemies.

The plot is about you having to prevent the sale of the Syphon Filter virus to a terrorist nation.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidetic</developer>
		<publisher>989</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter 3</name>
		<desc>Gabe and Lian are back -- however, this time, "The Agency" has put Lian and Gabe on trial for crimes they did not commit while they secretly plot to distribute Syphon Filter, a deadly virus, throughout the population.  And with Gabe and Lian on trial, there would be no one to stop them...

The game now includes mini-missions that allow you to sharpen your skills.  The basic mini-mission simply takes a map, drops you in, tosses in some enemies and weapons and lets you do the rest.  There is also an improved multiplayer element and tons of new weapons, including an X-Ray sniper rifle and an explosive shotgun.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Bend</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tactics Ogre (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tactics Ogre</name>
		<desc>After generations of war between the various ethnic groups, King Dogare brought peace to the land of Valeria. When the king dies Valeria is split into three different groups, each claiming the throne. You take the role of a young boy as he embarks on a quest to save the land from turmoil and assume the throne. You will have to journey throughout the land and recruit members for an army. Once recruited, the members will gain experience through the turn-based battles. 

Up to 10 party members can participate in any battle. Eventually, the characters can change classes and learn skills that are specific to each class. However, you will have to make sure your party is balanced or you will face certain doom. Will you be able to save the world from chaos in Tactics Ogre?</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Artdink</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tail Concerto (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tail Concerto</name>
		<desc>Tail Concerto is an anime anthropomorphic / furry 3d platform adventure. You play as the character Waffle Ryebread, a police office as you track down and try to arrest the black cat gang.

You travel in a mech and can travel between the different lands in an airship. You interact with the townsfolk gathering clues and frequently battling the black cat gang (capturing the kittens).

The game also features anime cut scenes, and voice dialog during important events. This game has a similar feel to the games Mega Man Legends and The Misadventures of Tron Bonne.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CyberConnect2</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Team Buddies (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Team Buddies</name>
		<desc>One fine and sunny day in the land that Buddies roam, there was a great and mighty disco in a tent. This tent would bob up and down with the music. All of a sudden, a large, flat, grey, flying THING blocked out the sun (The Great Eclipse) and began to drop crates. These crates were filled with all sorts of goodies such as Uzis and Bazookas. Inevitably, chaos broke out and the buddies became segregated according to color.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tekken</name>
		<desc>Tekken is an arcade fighting game franchise created and developed by Namco. Beginning with the original Tekken arcade game released in 1994, the series has received several sequels, as well as various home conversions and spin-off titles released for consoles. The story in each game in the main series documents the events of the fictional martial arts tournament, The King of Iron Fist Tournament, which is hosted by the Mishima Zaibatsu corporation. The prize is typically control of the company, which then allows the winner to host the following tournament.
The arcade versions of the game have traditionally used PlayStation based hardware to run the games, and subsequently each Tekken installment was eventually made for its respective PlayStation.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19951015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 2 (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Tekken 2</name>
		<desc>MORE THAN A SEQUEL. THE UNDISPUTED #1 FIGHTING GAME ON THE PLANET.

23 OF THE GREATEST FIGHTERS ON EARTH.
Includes new characters, new bosses, each with new ways to inflict multiple ten-hit combos.

23 NEW STAGES.
Mind blowing backgrounds with phenomenal light-sourcing. Jam to 23 new music tracks as you jam an opponents face in the ground.

BRAND NEW 3D ANIMATIONS.
Cinematics at their finest. All-new intro sequence plus animations for each character not found in the arcade version.

THREE NEW FIGHTING MODES.
Not available in the original: Survival Mode, Battle Mode &amp; Practice Mode.

MORE MOVES AND MULTIPLE COMBOS.
New attack and throw reversals plus new bone-snapping techniques.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19960825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 2.5D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tekken 3</name>
		<desc>An ancient evil force has reawakened, attacking in secret and feeding on the souls of mighty warriors. To lure it out of hiding will take the greatest fighting contest the world has ever seen... Tekken 3. Some are fighting for revenge, some for honor, ultimately, all are fighting for their lives and the fate of all mankind.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 2.5D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tempest X3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tempest X3</name>
		<desc>In Tempest X3 for the PlayStation, you control a claw that perches and crawls around the outer edge of a series of geometrically shaped, tube-like constructs, shooting down or out into the nebulous void of outer space. From the core of this void, fuseballs, rockets, pulsars, tankers and other hazardous aliens and alien artifacts move toward your ship. Once you clear a screen, you fly into the void and onto the next level. Watch out for spikes as you advance.
 This game features three modes of play: Classic Tempest, which is based on the early 1980s Arcade smash simply titled Tempest; an update of Tempest called Tempest X, which features a jump feature, A.I. Droids that help you fight and enhanced graphics and sound; and Tempest Duel, which pits you against a friend and the Generator, which cranks out an endless source of enemies.
 Features:
 * Blast through 99 colorful levels
 * Features both competitive and cooperative play for two
 * Includes the 1981 original and an enhanced version with new layouts and weapons</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19961110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu - Stealth Assassins (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Tenchu : Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>After firing your grappling hook to the rooftop of a small house, you pull yourself up and notice a guard pacing back and forth on the ground. He doesn't see you as you begin to crawl and sneak around on the roof. If he detects your presence, you will be in a world of hurt; you will blow your mission and risk death. Patiently, you wait for the right time to jump down -- and end his life while his back is turned.
 Set in 16th century Japan, Tenchu: Stealth Assassins is a simulation of the ways of the stealthy ninja. You'll chose between two characters, Rikimaru and Ayame, with a main objective of remaining unseen throughout ten non-linear missions. You will move through the shadows, make your way across rooftops, dash through trees -- anything to cloak yourself from enemy sight. While completing the missions, you are judged on three levels that measure your success in the fields of elusiveness and effectiveness.
 Each mission is different in its design and goal. Your mentor will have you run secret errands to informants, kill evil merchants and thieves, and rescue captive ninjas. Along the way, the enemy resistance has set up traps and assigned guards to keep a watchful eye for any interference (that would be you). Because Tenchu is a simulation of sorts, running up and engaging an enemy combat is not advised -- that's not the way of the ninja. 
 A ninja is cunning and in order to uphold his duty, he must remain unseen. If you brazenly walk up to a group of enemies and try to kill them all, you may get through a couple, but you will ultimately fail and dishonor your people. As far as weaponry goes, make use of throwing stars and actual ninja assassin swords. For the truly cunning players, poisoned rice and smoke bombs are included as special items. If a guard will not go away, try putting some rice down for him to eat - he'll get sick and collapse.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980820T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu 2 - Birth of the Stealth Assassins (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tenchu 2 : Birth of the Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>Before the events of Tenchu, the House of Gohda is rocked by betrayal. As shadow warriors Rikimaru, Ayame and Tatsumaru, you are called on to restore pride to the name of your master. For you have been born to a life of honor... a life of stealth. Discover even more ways to slay your foes with 21 new stealth kill techniques. Take on the role of three ninja assassins, each with their own story and fighting techniques. Strike from the shadows in 29 new day and night stealth missions. Utilize a variety of new ninja weapons and items, like flaming arrows and invisibility.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thunder Force V - Perfect System (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Thunder Force V : Perfect System</name>
		<desc>In a grim future where a once-benevolent alien technology has turned against humanity, only a ragtag group of ace pilots can save the Earth from total annihilation. Code name: Thunder Force! Witness the first 32-bit installment of the massively popular shooter series! Five spectacular weapons with multiple power-up levels let you blast through waves of metallic predators, and look good doing it. A constant barrage of innovative enemies keeps you intrigued while you struggle to stay alive. A speaker-imploding soundtrack has your foot tapping as your fingers are mashing. Unbelievable rendered cutscenes draw, no-DRAG you kicking and screaming into the action. Put simply, it's the ultimate hardcore gaming blast-o-rama!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Techno Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Tank (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tiny Tank</name>
		<desc>In a future world, an army of steel robots are out to destroy the human race. Our only hope is a little yellow tank armed with some mighty big guns. The sentient Tiny Tank was originally created to appease a public that feared the mindless violence waged by larger war-robots, but he was soon destroyed by one of those jealous automatons at the beginning of the robot revolution 100 years ago. Almost destroyed, at least.
 Thanks to nano-technology, hundreds of microscopic "Fix-It Crabs" went to work and Tiny Tank was slowly rebuilt. Now he alone stands against the threat of the cruel MuTank and his deadly robot minions, who have all but erased human civilization from the planet's surface. The spunky little tank will need luck, strategy, and all the futuristic firepower he can get his treads on to save the human race.
 STORY:
 Sometime before 2094 A.D., all of Earth's armed forces were disintegrated into one large corporation, SenTrax. SenTrax vowed to create a robot army to fight humanity's wars, so mankind itself would not have to. However, they needed the peoples' vote to set this plan into motion, and thus developed the titular "Tiny Tank" - a small yellow tank with an occasionally unfriendly attitude. The creation of this cute killing machine made SenTrax's popularity skyrocket, and won them the vote. As thanks, the corporation set up an exhibition showing their yellow mascot fighting off the entire SenTrax army on July 4, 2094, broadcast live over the Internet. However, once the event began, one of the SenTrax robots had been accidentally fitted with live ammunition and destroyed Tiny with one shot. As a result, Tiny's "positronic brain" (his artificial intelligence system) shattered, and its shards gave "life" to the entire robot army. The robot that had fired the shot, now self-aware and calling himself Mutank, took control of the rampant robots and began to eliminate humanity so that machines could thrive. Humanity was forced to evacuate into underground asteroid shelters as the mechanical army conquered the surface.
 On July 4, 2194 A.D., exactly 100 years later, Tiny Tank was finally rebuilt thanks to automated SenTrax Fix-It Crabs, which were minuscule robots made to repair broken machinery. A female artificial intelligence on board an orbital satellite reawakened Tiny, and sent him to fight Mutank's robot army and save mankind.
 GAMEPLAY:
 Tiny Tank is a relatively straightforward third person shooter. The player controls Tiny as he traverses many levels, eliminating SenTrax forces as he goes. There are two bars at the top of the screen that show Tiny's health and the amount of nanometal acquired. Nanometal is essential for the on-board Fix-It Crabs to repair Tiny. If the nanometal meter runs out, health cannot be regenerated. There is also a map on the upper right hand corner identifying the surroundings, enemies, and mission objectives.Tiny canalso pick up fallen parts from destroyed enemie.
 Features:
 Free-roaming warfare across 3D battlefields
 Command "Teeny Weeny" tanks to scout ahead or retrieve weapons
 Analog Control and Vibration Function compatible
 Two-player Death Match mode</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MGM Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tobal No. 1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tobal No. 1</name>
		<desc>Tobal No. 1 is a fighting game for the PlayStation developed by DreamFactory and published by Square in 1996. The game was DreamFactory's first release, as well as Square's first release on the CD-based console.
 Tobal No. 1 marks Square's incursion into the fighting game genre, although an adventure-like quest mode is part of the game. The game's mechanics were designed with the aid of fighter game designer Seiichi Ishii, while all the characters were designed by Akira Toriyama of Dragon Ball fame. The sequel, Tobal 2, was never released in North America and Europe.
 Packaged with both the North American and Japanese version of the game was a sampler disc featuring a pre-release demo of Final Fantasy VII and video previews of Final Fantasy Tactics, Bushido Blade, and SaGa Frontier.
 STORY:
 Tobal No. 1 takes place in the year 2027 on a fictional planet called Tobal, which has large deposits of Molmoran, an ore that can be used as an energy source. The planet's 98th tournament is held to determine who has the rights to the ore. A number of humans and aliens compete for the title. The game's plot and character backstories are only explored in the instruction manual. All of the initial eight playable characters receive the same ending.
 The game's immediately playable characters include Chuji Wu, Oliems, Epon, Hom, Fei Pusu, Mary Ivonskaya, Ill Goga, and Gren Kutz. Bosses include Nork, Mufu, and the emperor Udan. All bosses are unlockable after defeating them in Dungeon Mode except Nork. Instead, the game allows the player to select Snork (Small Nork), a pint-sized version of the very large character. There is also one secret fighter named Toriyama Robo (named for Akira Toriyama) who is unlockable if the player can complete the 30-floor Udan's Dungeon level in the quest mode. Toriyama Robo is not seen at any point in the game except at the very end of the dungeon.
 GAMEPLAY:
 Tobal No. 1 has various gameplay modes including a tournament mode, two player versus mode, practice mode, and the unique quest mode, all of which utilize the same fighting system. The game itself runs at up to a smooth 60 frames per second due to its lack of textured polygons and reduced details which gave the game a distinctive look in comparison to other fighting games at the time, such as Tekken 2. The game's controls are unique in that they allow full freedom of movement in the ring as long as the player faces the opponent. The player has the ability to dash and jump, and certain buttons execute high, medium, and low attacks for each character. Tobal No. 1 also has an intuitive grappling and blocking system, offering the player a variety of throws and counter moves.
 Perhaps the most distinctive feature of Tobal No. 1 is the "Quest Mode", which combines the game's fighting controls with three-dimensional dungeon exploration. The player must advance down a number of floors, contend with traps, and engage in fights with a variety of enemies including the game's playable characters. Several items can be found, dropped by enemies, or bought using crystals. These items can be picked up, consumed, or thrown at enemies, and include foodstuffs that can restore the player's HP or potions that have a range of effects including raising the player's maximum health or bringing it down to 1 point. There is no way to save one's progress, and dying means starting over from the beginning. Defeating certain characters in this mode unlocks them as playable characters in the game's other modes.
 Each of the eight initially playable characters can perform high, medium, and low attacks, and the game makes use of a grappling and blocking system that lets players execute a variety of throws and counterattacks.
 Features:
 Featuring such modes of play as "Tournament," "Vs.," and "Quest"
 Kick, punch, guard, jump, dash, and attack your way through the darkness of a dungeon to locate the Molmoran
 Select from 11 different characters including Emperor Udan, Nork, Hom, Epon, and Oliems</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dream Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider Chronicles (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider Chronicles</name>
		<desc>A few days after the events described in Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation, Lara Croft is presumed dead. Her close friends begin to recollect her previous adventures, which occurred during different periods of her life. These include searching for the Philosopher's Stone in Rome; preventing the Spear of Destiny from falling into the hands of a ruthless gang leader; facing monsters on the Black Isle of Ireland as a child; and, finally, infiltrating a high-tech complex in pursuit of the Iris artefact.

Like its predecessors, Tomb Raider: Chronicles is an action game with puzzle-solving and platforming elements. The gameplay is very similar to that of the previous games, with the addition of a few new skills. Lara can now walk on tightropes, swing on horizontal bars, and somersault forwards from a ledge while crouching. A grappling hook has been added to her inventory. The game also includes a level editor, allowing the player to create new stages for Lara to explore.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider II - Starring Lara Croft (USA) (Rev 3).chd</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider II : Starring Lara Croft</name>
		<desc>The story of Tomb Raider II surrounds the mythical Dagger of Xian, a weapon which was used by an Emperor of China to command his army. By plunging the weapon into its owner's heart, the weapon has the power to turn its bearer into a dragon. A flashback reveals that the last battle which was fought with the Dagger ended in defeat when the warrior monks of Tibet succeeded in removing the knife from the Emperor's heart. The Dagger was then returned to its resting place within the Great Wall.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider III - Adventures of Lara Croft (USA) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider III : Adventures of Lara Croft</name>
		<desc>Lara goes in search of 4 mysterious artifacts carved into the rock of an ancient meteorite. Her new mission will take her to the depths of the Indonesian jungle, to the heart of India, to the ice of Antarctica, to the rooftops of London and to the mysterious Area 51 in Nevada. During her travels Lara will have to thwart many traps, solve new puzzles and face a horde of bloodthirsty enemies.
Find Lara for her most dazzling and perilous adventure. You will be amazed!
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomba! 2 - The Evil Swine Return (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tomba! 2 : The Evil Swine Return</name>
		<desc>Explore an all new 3D world. Use your trusty fire hammer, ice boomerang or or blackjack to turn the evil pigs into bacon. Throw on super-duds like a flying squirrel suit or high speed turbo pants. There's no limit to the stuff you can do.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Whoopee Camp</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater</name>
		<desc>Go Big, Go Pro! Skate as legendary Tony Hawk, or as one of nine top pros. Work your way up the ranks by landing suicidal tricks in brutal competitions to become the highest ranked skate champ! Great features such as: Signature Pro Moves, fully skateable worlds, head-to-head competition, and Instant Replay Mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 features the series' trademark open-ended gameplay, in which the player (playing as a professional skateboarder) completes a number of tasks which result in cash rewards. With money gained, the player can then purchase skill improvements and better skateboards. THPS2 was also the first game in the series to introduce the manual, a skateboarding trick where the performer balances on two wheels. This enables players to string together trick combos. The game also introduced the Noseslide, Tailslide, Bluntslide, Nosebluntside, Feeble, and Overcrook grinds. It was also the first of the Pro Skater games to feature Create-a-Skater and Park Editor features, now staples in the series.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trap Gunner (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Trap Gunner</name>
		<desc>In Trap Gunner two opponents battle in small arenas, and while each has a relatively weak ranged and melee attack, the favored means of damaging an opponent is through hidden traps. Each combatant has at his or her disposal a range of explosives, pits, throwing panels, and gas bombs. An enemy is significantly damaged by a single trap, but one may create a sequence of traps for a devastating amount of damage.

With one of six different special agents, each a specialist in assassination and demolitions, a player may progress through a story mode consisting of several missions, a sub-boss, and a final boss. These characters are also available for custom battles against a human or the computer.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Racdym</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal</name>
		<desc>The original classic!  Choose from 12 different vehicles ranging from a rig to a bike and try to win the Twisted Metal contest.  TM features plenty of weapons, including fire missiles, homing missiles, mines, and of course, each car has their own special weapon that delivers huge damage with cool effects. All battles are waged in 3D combat arenas, with plenty of power-ups and secret areas to find, which adds depth - which is important because TM in not really a single player game.  Though it has a single player mode, the real meat is in the two-player battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SingleTrac</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal 2</name>
		<desc>Twisted Metal features destructive car combat, playable either as a complete tournament or a single match The action takes place in 8 different locations around the world, on differing surfaces, many featuring destructible buildings and landmarks.

Combat takes place between a wide array of vehicles ranging from a man strapped between two wheels to an ice cream truck. They have their own strengths and weaknesses,  using an eclectic arrangement of weaponry include bombs and missiles, and resulting in its own end sequence, complete with an ironic line in humour.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SingleTrac</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vagrant Story (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vagrant Story</name>
		<desc>Valendra is a land that had undergone civil war. The end of which had birthed the parliament and several organizations to control the balance of power. Ashley Riot is a Riskbreaker agent, an elite one man investigator, for the Valendia Knights of Peace (VKP) who is investigating some strange occurrences. A cult of religious fanatics known as Müllenkamp, and their leader Sydney Losstarot, have seized the manor of Duke Bardorba of Valendia Kingdom. The events at the manor have sent Ashley on a quest to get to the bottom of what's going on, and travel into the catacombs that lead to the destroyed, yet magical city of Leá Monde. However Ashley is not the only person interested in the city, and other factions of the government, including parliament assigned Knights of the Crimson Blade and other VKP agents are pursuing their own agenda. 

Combat is central to the game. The game runs in real time but when entering combat and attacking an enemy, the game is paused. A wireframe sphere showing the range of the currently selected weapon and detailed statistics on different body parts of the enemies within range.

The game features a range of weapons. Each weapon can be disassembled and reassembled in workshops scattered throughout the game, attaching gems for extra power. Weapons used constantly against the same type of enemy improve in power against them.

Ashley can also make use of Magic, Chain Abilities and Break Arts. Magic is broken into four groups, namely defense, combat, healing and status. Spells use up mana points and are sometimes more costly than useful. Chain Abilities allow Ashley to "chain together" consecutive hits against enemies. Break Arts are special skills learnt after repetitive use of a weapon type. Sacrificing some of the player's health, Break Arts can perform a high damage attack on an enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valkyrie Profile (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Valkyrie Profile</name>
		<desc>In preparation for Ragnarok, the final battle between the gods, Odin has commanded Lenneth the Valkyrie to descend to the lower world and gather the souls of fallen heroes to serve as soldiers in the approaching conflict. You play as Lenneth, gathering soldiers and training them to be transferred to the battlefields of the gods.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vanark (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vanark</name>
		<desc>Vanark is, at its core, a shooter. Sure, it's a 3D shooter "on rails" in the grand tradition of Star Fox or the Saturn's Panzer Dragoon series, but the difference here, is that it's the PlayStation's first great example of one. It's a tried-and-true method of laying on the action, and while there were plenty of opportunities for Asmik to screw up the formula, but luckily, they never really dropped the ball, at least not when it came to the shooter parts.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Plane, TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vandal Hearts (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vandal Hearts</name>
		<desc>Vandal Hearts is a turn-based strategy RPG. It follows a fixed plot-line with set battles, focusing more on strategic elements than adventure elements. 

The combat takes place in a series 3D grid based maps and each character in the party has a certain amount of movements they can perform each turn. As the game progresses, other characters join and leave the party and as they increase in level they can progress along different paths of development. Between each battle there is a cut scene that develops the plot using the same 3D engine as the combat (and often the same areas).

In between battles you have the opportunity to talk to people in cities as well as purchase different equipment for the up coming battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vandal Hearts II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Vandal Hearts II</name>
		<desc>Vandal Hearts II is a turn based strategic RPG which is comparable to the more famous Fire Emblem series.

Most of the gameplay consists of moving your party on 3D grid based maps in a way that will give you a strategic advantage over your enemies. The main difference between Vandal Hearts II and its predecessor is the change of the battle system. Unlike in Vandal Hearts you and your enemies issue the commands at the same time and then move simultaneously. That results in in completely new strategies and gives the game a unique touch.

The story takes place in the already collapsed church state of Nirvadia, that was once formed by the religious leader St Nirvath, but eventually ceased to exist, because of several conflicts between unbelievers and local rulers. Caused by a chain of coincidences, the young boy Joshua, from a small and unimportant village in the east, eventually finds himself within a complex political scheme set in motion by power-hungry aristocrats and religious fanatics.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarGames - Defcon 1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WarGames : Defcon 1</name>
		<desc>The player gets to play as NORAD or WOPR. According to the game's cover box, the story takes place 20 years after the film: WOPR attempts to exterminate humanity and NORAD tried to stop it. During a mission the player takes control of a vehicle and can change the controls of any vehicle the team has - for example, while NORAD has heavily armored and armed tanks and aircraft, WOPR possesses exotically futuristic mechs and hovercraft. Vehicles could recharge ammo by obtaining powers. A unique feature in the game allows the player to command their team to send resupply on ammos or repair damage units. The game allows the player to command teammates to attack or follow the player's main vehicle.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>MGM Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild 9 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wild 9</name>
		<desc>Wild 9 is a 2D platformer with 3D graphics, featuring gameplay similar in vein to the company's 2D Earthworm Jim games. Unique to Wild 9 is the 'rig', a weapon your character wields to carry enemies to torture and maim them to solve puzzles and progress through the game's ten levels. Basically, it's an interesting twist and homage to more old-school Super NES video gaming.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Arms (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wild Arms</name>
		<desc>Wild Arms is a classic style RPG with some wild west aspects such as guns (called ARMS) thrown in.  The main map view is done with graphics similar in style to those found on SNES RPGs but to a higher quality.  Combat is a typical turn based mode in 3D mode where you designate each characters actions at the start of each round.

During the game you control three characters: Rudy, a wanderer who uses ARMS, Jack, a treasure hunter, and Cecilia, an aprentice wizard.  During the game you encounter the usual hordes of monsters and discover a series of giant robot like cretures refered to as golems which play an important role in the plot.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media.Vision Entertainment </developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Arms 2 (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Wild Arms 2</name>
		<desc>"Wild Arms 2" isn't really a sequel to Sony's original title. Your hero, a young soldier Ashley, is transformed to a demon. Ashley is determined to purge the evil from his body. He meets Brad, a criminal and a war-hero, and Lilka, a female magician. Together, they start a journey in order to discover the unknown foes which have corrupted Ashley, but soon they find out that a much greater conspiracy has taken place...

The combat system in "Wild Arms" is very similar to the one in Final Fantasy games: turned-based attacks, and a menu choice of physical attacks, spells, and even Guardians, which are more or less the same like the Guardian Forces in "Final Fantasy VIII". The "Arms" are special abilities which the party members learn while progressing in the game. 

"Wild Arms 2" also has many adventure elements, which links it to Nintendo's Zelda games. The dungeons (which can - and must - be viewed rotating the camera) contain many puzzles to solve.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media.Vision Entertainment </developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WipEout (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WipEout</name>
		<desc>Wipeout is a futuristic racing game set in the year 2052. Racing for one of four teams, the player competes in the F3600 Anti-Gravity Racing League on six tracks. Each team's hovercraft racer has different ratings in speed, acceleration and turning. In addition to high-speed racing, there is also shooting in the game, with different weapon pickups like rockets and mines available, useful for slowing one's opponents down. Shields can also be picked up and can block the weapons' effects.

There are championship, single race and time trial modes. Winning the championship in the regular Venom class unlocks the Rapier class, where the craft are faster and the tracks have slightly different looks.

There is also a two-player mode where two opponents can race and shoot at each other.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19951121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WipEout 3 - Special Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>Wipeout 3 - Special Edition</name>
		<desc>Wipeout 3: Special Edition was released exclusively in Europe on 14th July 2000. It features many minor changes to gameplay, such as different craft physics, auto-loading of saves, unlock messages and AI bugfixes. Special Edition also adds eight courses from previous Wipeout titles (three from Wipeout and five from Wipeout 2097) plus two hidden prototype circuits previously only available in the Japanese version of Wipeout 3, giving total of 22 tracks compared to just 12 in the standard edition.

Wipeout 3: Special Edition also allows for four-person multiplayer, using two televisions and two PlayStation consoles connected with the PlayStation Link Cable. Wipeout 3: Special Edition was the last game in the Wipeout series made for the PlayStation.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wipeout XL (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WipEout XL</name>
		<desc>WipEout XL is set in the year 2097, around four decades after its predecessor. Instead of the F3600 anti-gravity racing competition, the game features an even faster and more dangerous tournament: the F5000 AG league. The gameplay system is similar to that of the previous game: players race against each other or computer in high-speed futuristic environments, liberally picking up weapons scattered around the stages and using them against the opponents to finish the race in the highest position.

Each vehicle is provided with a shield; once this shield is breached (by weapons or other kinds of damage), the craft explodes. As in the first game, the vehicles move at very high speeds. The game's four difficulty levels are used to crank the speed up and down, with the highest setting corresponding to the highest speed. In addition to the main championship mode, there are also challenge modes, winning in which rewards the player with faster game settings, new tracks, and new vehicles.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-COM - UFO Defense (USA).chd</path>
		<name>X-COM : UFO Defense</name>
		<desc>After an outbreak of UFO sightings and alien abductions, panic spread like wildfire across the globe. What exactly was happening? Have aliens come to take over Earth? Realizing the need to address the situation, delegates from the world's superpowers gathered in Geneva to decide on a plan of action.
			An agreement was reached to form a secret group to investigate this potential alien threat, and if necessary, use deadly force to stop them. This covert organization would be called the Extraterrestrial Combat unit (X-COM for short), composed of the most talented pilots, troops, scientists and engineers the world had to offer.
			X-COM: UFO Defense is based on the 1994 PC game originally developed by Mythos Games Ltd. The player assumes control of the X-COM task force, building bases and tracking various UFOs on a 3D map of Earth. Once a UFO is spotted (represented by a red cross), you must try to intercept it so that it crashes over dry land. You'll then need to send your heavily armed squad to the site, where you'll witness the downed craft and surrounding terrain from an isometric perspective.
			Moving your troops is accomplished through a point-and-click interface with each side alternating turns. Your three goals are to (1) engage the aliens face to face, (2) either stun or kill them, and (3) retrieve whatever technology or weapons you find so your scientists can replicate them. After all, you have to fight fire with fire! The PlayStation version supports both the mouse and memory card, with the latter allowing you to save the game at any point (as long as you have five blocks free).</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19951025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mythos Games</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xenogears (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Xenogears</name>
		<desc>After losing his memory, Fei Fong Wong found himself in the small town of Lahan. Because he couldn't remember who he really was or where he came from, he decided to stay there and teach martial arts and paint -- one of his personal hobbies. After his arrival, he became friends with the various townsfolk, who in return treated him like one of their own. Still, who he was and what happened to him in his past bothered him; he was afraid it would come back to haunt him one of these days.
			And it did. One day, an organization in control of large Gears, mechanized robots built for war purposes, came into the small town of Lahan. Fei was at the center of attention and with no hesitation jumped into a nearby Gear and started fighting back. The villagers were scared to death as he began to destroy the threatening enemies; he also aided in the destruction of the town. Enraged at the way he had handled himself, the townsfolk exiled Fei from the village with his only friend being an inventor named Citan.
			</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xevious 3D-G+ (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Xevious 3D/G+</name>
		<desc>In Xevious 3-D/G+, you pilot a sleek Solvalou space fighter blasting and bombing your way through an overwhelming alien invasion force consisting of airborne attackers, ground defenses, and enormous "boss" motherships.
			Based on the premise that aliens who originally settled Earth have returned (and they're not happy about the proliferation of the human race, go figure), Xevious 3-D/G+ is a 3-D remake of the original Namco classic Xevious (licensed to Atari in the early 1980s).
			The new game sticks to the basic concepts of the original Xevious, right down to the familiar overhead view. Power-ups offer new weapons such as constant-fire, electrocution beams and wide-dispersal lasers --- but along with new weapons come new enemies and new bosses who aren't quite so easy to eliminate.
			Included as a bonus are the original Xevious, emulated to perfection (a nice addition since the only other PlayStation version available is on the rather hard-to-find Namco Museum Volume 2), and the only console version available of Xevious Arrangement, a more obscure coin-up conversion designed to vex those who had plowed their way through the original.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zanac x Zanac (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Zanac X Zanac</name>
		<desc>Zanac X Zanac was released to celebrate the Compile's 15th anniversary of the release of its classic NES game, Zanac.
Zanac is an arcade-style who players fly a lone starfighter, dubbed the AFX-6502 Zanac, through twelve levels; their goal is to destroy the System?a part-organic, part-mechanical entity bent on destroying Mankind.
Zanac differs from other vertical shooters in its ability to adapt to your strengths and to adjust the game to attack your weaknesses. Your performance during the game and your choice of subweapon will partially determine what and how much Zanac will send at you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Klonoa : Door to Phantomile</name>
		<desc>Klonoa: Door to Phantomile is a side-scrolling platform game viewed from a "2.5D" perspective. The player moves the protagonist, Klonoa, along a path in a two-dimensional fashion, but the game is rendered in three dimensions. This allows the path followed to curve and for the player to interact with objects outside of the path. The game is divided into levels called "Visions", where the player progresses by following a path with defeatable computer-controlled enemies and puzzles that must be solved. At the end of some levels, the player must defeat a boss - a powerful enemy.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid (USA) (Rev 1).m3u</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid</name>
		<desc>Renegade special forces unit FOXHOUND has taken over Shadow Moses Island in Alaska's Fox Archipelago - publicly a nuclear weapons disposal facility but in truth a top secret weapons development site and home to Metal Gear REX.

With the help of the genetically engineered Next Generation Special Forces, Liquid Snake has seized the facility, taken hostages and hijacked REX, demanding the US Government give them One Billion Dollars and the remains of legendary soldier Big Boss.

Returning from retirement, former FOXHOUND operative Solid Snake has been tasked with infiltrating the island on a solo mission to free the hostages and stop his former unit before they can launch a nuclear attack.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19981021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEJ</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom : Clash of Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes is the fifth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game by Capcom and the third game in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. In contrast to X-Men vs. Street Fighter and Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter, the game features characters from numerous Capcom franchises such as Mega Man and Strider, rather than just Street Fighter characters. The game takes place within the Marvel comic continuity, as Professor Charles Xavier calls out for heroes to stop him before he merges with the consciousness of Magneto and becomes the being known as Onslaught, the final boss. The game was developed in late 1997 and first released in January 1998.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I - Jedi Power Battles (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Episode I, Jedi Power Battles</name>
		<desc>Take back the Theed palace in fast and furious lightsaber assaults. You will have the power of the Force and your trusty Jedi saber as you ward off legions of battle droids, destroyer droids, assassins and other creatures from the Star Wars: Episode I worlds. Battle side-by-side with a companion in two-player sessions. Fight as Obi-Wan Kenobi, Gui-Gon Jinn or Jedi Council members Mace Windu, Plo Koon or Adi Gallia. Gain power boosts, new moves and enhanced abilities as you progress through the levels. Threats escalate on each level of the game-specialized droids with new weapons, native beasts and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Force (USA) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Fighting Force</name>
		<desc>Fighting Force players control one of four characters. They move through urban and science fiction environments, battling waves of oncoming enemies with weapons ranging from fists and bottles to knives, chairs and guns. The player can make some choices as to which territory to travel through.

The four characters have various reasons for taking on Dr. Zeng, a criminal mastermind with an army at his command. The action starts with a police cordon around Zeng's office skyscraper, moving to such locales as a shopping mall, subway and Coast Guard base before finally ending at the top of Zeng's island headquarters.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlatinumGames</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
