<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country Returns (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 1).wbfs</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country Returns</name>
		<desc>Under the influence of a group of evil Tikis, the animals of Donkey Kong Island have raided Donkey Kong's banana hoard and stolen his stash of bananas - and being an ape of large appetites he understandably wants them back. Good thing that you are along for the ride. With Donkey Kong Country Returns, Retro Studios brings Donkey Kong back to a banana and platforming hungry public in a new side-scrolling adventure with familiar characters and new levels that reignite the passion players had for the Super NES original and all things Donkey Kong.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20101121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Radiant Dawn (USA) (Rev 1).wbfs</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem : Radiant Dawn</name>
		<desc>The sequel to 2005 s Path of Radiance and the tenth game in the Fire Emblem series, Radiant Dawn takes place three years after the defeat of the Daein kingdom by Crimea.

Unlike other Wii games, the main method of control is either through the classic controller or GameCube controller, since the action is wholly turn-based tactical combat, largely the same as the previous nine games. The game consists of 44 chapters and uses the same engine as Path of Radiance. There are three new weapon and magic types: Knife, Dark Magic and Strike.

The player must lead a band of heroes against the Begnion Empire s oppression of the defeated Daein, along with help from many of the heroes from Path of Radiance. The members of the Dawn group are the main heroes of the game, with a major role for Sothe, who was a child thief from the previous Fire Emblem game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Tactical RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Epic Yarn (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Kirby's Epic Yarn</name>
		<desc>While walking through Dream Land, Kirby discovers a tomato and decides to eat it. Yin-Yarn, the evil sorceror who possessed the tomato (revealed to be a Metamato), appears and magically banishes Kirby into Patch Land, a world completely made of fabric, via the sock carried around his neck. In Patch Land, Kirby s body transforms into yarn, rendering his power to inhale useless. Instead, Kirby is granted the ability to transform by the magic of the Metamato, which he uses to rescue a boy being attacked by a monster. The boy, named Prince Fluff, explains that Yin-Yarn has separated Patch Land into pieces, which was tied together by magic yarn. Kirby decides to help Prince Fluff collect all seven pieces of the yarn and restore Patch Land.

Meanwhile, Yin-Yarn captures King Dedede and Meta Knight and places them under his control. Kirby is forced to fight Dedede and Meta Knight after they ambush him in Patch Land. When Kirby and Prince Fluff finally collect all the Magic Yarn, Meta Knight, no longer under the sorceror s influence, informs Kirby that Yin-Yarn is turning Dream Land into fabric. Prince Fluff produces the second sock, its magic fully restored, and uses it to transport Kirby and himself to Dream Land; now completely made of yarn. Kirby confronts and defeats Yin-Yarn, breaking the spell and returning Dream Land and himself back to normal. Prince Fluff parts with Kirby, stating that he can visit Patch Land anytime via Yin-Yarn s magic sock.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Return to Dream Land (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Kirby's Return to Dream Land</name>
		<desc>Kirby and his friends are back in an adventure designed to satisfy longtime Kirby fans and beginners alike. When an alien spaceship crashes in the otherwise peaceful realm of Pop Star, its pieces are scattered throughout the land. Players must guide Kirby as he retrieves the ship's parts and helps the aliens return to their home planet. This time, however, he's not alone. At any time, up to three more players can join in the fun and play as Meta Knight, King Dedede and Waddle Dee to help Kirby in his quest.Kirby's powerful Copy Ability returns, allowing him to inhale, spit and transform as he encounters enemies.The game also introduces new Super Abilities, which are activated when Kirby inhales special enemy characters. For example, the "Super Sword" Super Ability allows Kirby to swing a giant sword and wipe out an entire screen's worth of foes.Up to four players can enjoy the action together. They play cooperatively to progress through the game and collect Point Stars and Ability Stars. Players can join and leave the game at any time.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20111024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Skyward Sword (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2).wbfs</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Skyward Sword</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword once again places the player in control of Link, a Hylian boy who this time around lives in the floating nation of Skyloft. Link is in love with a local girl called Zelda but one day while flying on their bird mounts, a tornado shows up out of nothing and takes Zelda away from Link. After that Link teams up with Fi, a spirit living within a sword and he descends to the long-forgotten surface to search for Zelda.

The game is structured very similar to previous Zelda games: you travel through an overworld in search of temples to visit and once in you solve a series of puzzles before fighting a boss at the end and receive the next bit of plot. The biggest change is that the overworld is more focused on puzzles this time around with only a handful of action. Also new is the implementation of the Wii Motion Plus which allows full 1:1 controls and new puzzle possibilities. </desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20111120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Twilight Princess (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2).wbfs</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Twilight Princess</name>
		<desc>When an evil darkness enshrouds the land of Hyrule, a young farm boy named Link must awaken the hero – and the animal – within. When Link travels to the Twilight Realm, he transforms into a wolf and must scour the land with the help of a mysterious girl named Midna. Besides his trusty sword and shield, Link will use his bow and arrows by aiming with the Wii Remote controller, fight while on horseback and use a wealth of other items, both new and old.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart Wii (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Mario Kart Wii</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart Wii is an installment of the long-running Mario Kart series, but here for the Nintendo Wii, where you take control of various Nintendo characters to race through different tracks and win the Grand Prix, using a variety of vehicles and items spread through the track to help you.

There are various additions to the series. Players can now also play with motorbikes, which can do wheelies but are lighter and can't super boost, in contrast with karts. There's 6 varieties of each for each character class to choose from, and 4 new characters have been added as well as being able to drive with your Mii. Finally, there's 16 new tracks as well as 16 returning from previous games.

Gameplay has also been modified. Drifting has been tweaked so that it's easier to use and players only get a turbo boost based on how well they perform the drift. It can be set to Manual, where players press a button to drift, or Automatic, where it's automatically triggered on curves but provides no turbo boost. Stunts can also be performed in the air to gain turbo boosts. Races have also been bolstered to support up to 12 players now.

There's 4 modes of play to choose from: Grand Prix, where you race through series of tracks in the 50cc (karts only), 100cc (bikes only) and 150cc (karts and bikes) cups; Time Trial, where you take on ghost replays and try to finish in the least time; Versus, where you race against opponents on a single track; and Battle, where you can compete against your foes in either hitting them with weapons or collecting coins.

Multiplayer is also supported, allowing up to 4 players in hotseat and 12 online on Nintendo Wi-Fi, where you can take on strangers and friends (with Friend Codes) in any game mode, play in competitions, beat other's ghost replays or check online rankings. The game can be played using a Wii Wheel (included), Wii Remote, Nunchuck, Classic Controller, or Gamecube Controller.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-12</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime Trilogy (USA).wbfs</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime: Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Metroid Prime 3: Corruption set a new standard for first-person motion controls in video games. Now it's bringing those controls to the rest of the celebrated series, allowing players to experience the entire Metroid Prime story arc with the peerless precision of the Wii Remote. Nintendo announces Metroid Prime Trilogy, a new premium three-game collection for the Wii console that bundles all three landmark Metroid Prime games onto one disc and revamps the first two installments with intuitive Wii Remote controls, wide-screen presentation and other enhancements. Each game maintains its original storyline and settings, but now Metroid Prime and Metroid Prime 2: Echoes lets you use your Wii Remote to aim with precision as heroine Samus Aran. Based on the breakthrough control system that debuted in Metroid Prime 3: Corruption, these new Wii controls bring an entirely new level of immersion and freedom to these milestone games.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20090824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Galaxy (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Super Mario Galaxy</name>
		<desc>Mario takes to the skies and beyond in another outing to save the Princess. As the Mushroom Kingdom prepares to celebrate the arrival of a comet that appears in the skies every hundred years, Princess Peach sends Mario an invitation to attend. As Mario arrives, Bowser and minions attack the Kingdom and once again kidnap the Princess... and her entire castle. Mario gives chase but is lost as the ship leaves the atmosphere and ends up on a space station built on the visiting comet overseen by the mysterious Rosalina. It's up to Mario to brave new galaxies, find the elusive Power Stars, and bring his friends home.

Super Mario Galaxy plays similarly to Super Mario 64, as Mario explores his latest 3D world defying gravity, crossing various terrains, and even running upside down across the planet surfaces. Bouncing from planet to planet, Mario must collect Star Bits and coins, using his usual jump attacks and spins (now controlled with movement from the Wii Remote). The Wii Remote is also used to collect out of reach Star Bits and also can be controlled by a second player.

In addition, Mario can find new suits (similar to Super Mario Bros. 3) that give him the ability to turn into the ghostly Boo Mario, the high-flying Bee Mario, launch fireballs as Fire Mario and skate across frozen lakes as Ice Mario. New challenges also await Mario including ray surfing, balancing on a high-speed ball, floating inside bubbles, and other challenges in his quest to get all 120 stars. Even Luigi lends a hand in the search, making valuable contributions to the adventure.

Players can also take a snapshot of the worlds they've completed along with their best record times and send them to their friends via Wi-Fi.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Galaxy 2 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Super Mario Galaxy 2</name>
		<desc>Mario returns to the stars as the everlasting villain Bowser has kidnapped Princess Peach once more. This time while she was baking a cake...
Once again Mario is determined to fight Bowser and free Princess Peach. 

The basic goal of each level is to collect the golden star. The environment is still a mixture of standard Mario stages and miniature planetoids with their own orbital gravity. Throughout the game the perspective is changed at some stages, switching from 3D to 2D. The 2D part is similar to New Super Mario Bros. Wii.

Super Mario Galaxy 2 features a further improved experience over its predecessor, with two new suits for Mario and the return of Yoshi. Mario's first new suit is the Cloud Suit, which allows him to create three safe but temporary platforms. The second new suite is the Rock Suit. While wearing it, Mario can roll up into a ball which will be necessary to complete some challenges.
For the first time in the franchise Yoshi will be able to wear a suit as well. By finding it, he will become "Light Yoshi" that allows him to see certain platforms that are otherwise invisible.

Like in the original Super Mario Galaxy a second player can join the experience by pointing the Wii Remote on the screen to collect coins. What is new to the game however, is that the second player now also can collect items that are out of the reach of Mario.

To aid the entry for people new to the franchise, the game features an introduction to the game play and controls of the game.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20100523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Paper Mario (USA) (Rev 2).wbfs</path>
		<name>Super Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>In this action-platformer, Bowser and Peach find themselves at the wedding altar, forced into marriage by the evil Count Bleck. With this union, a void will engulf the entire universe as foretold by the book, the Dark Prognosticus. Before Luigi can stop Count Bleck, the villain escapes with an item known as the Chaos Heart. However, there is another book, called the Light Prognosticus, which can counteract the Dark Prognosticus. The Light Prognosticus foretells of a hero dressed in overalls. This hero is believed to possess the power to stop certain destruction of the universe.

Mario, joined by Peach, Bowser, and a new group of friends, must travel through eight worlds in search of Pure Hearts. Each character has a special ability, which can help the player solve the game's many puzzles. Mario can flip between the second and third dimensions in order to find items, secret pathways, and pound enemies. Peach can use her parasol to float long distances and to defend against enemy attacks. Bowser uses his fire breath to light things and to fry enemies.

Super Paper Mario does not fully depart from its RPG roots. For instance Mario and friends receive points from baddies. These points allow Mario and company to level up. Items can also be used to attack enemies or gain lives. Players collect coins to pay for more items.

Players can shake the Wii remote after jumping on bad guys but before hitting the ground to gain extra experience points. Players use Tippi, a Pixl, allowing them to point the remote at the screen to find secrets. Other Pixls, who help in other ways, can be found along the way. Pixls besides Tippi can be used by pressing the 1 button.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. Brawl (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).wbfs</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros. Brawl</name>
		<desc>Welcome to a brawl for the ages, where anything can happen, anyone can show up and all bets are off.Game storyline: In multiplayer games, characters from all Nintendo universes meet up in Nintendo locales to duke it out. In the solo mode called "The Subspace Emissary," the world of Smash Bros. is invaded by an entity called the Ancient Minister and his army of creatures, called "The Primid." Normally, characters come alive in the world of Smash Bros. to do battle, then turn back into trophies when defeated. However, the Ancient Minister starts turning characters into trophies to harness their power, then detonates bombs that suck pieces of the world back into his realm of Subspace. Eventually, all the characters must work together to defeat the invading creatures from Subspace - this is accomplished by playing through side-scrolling levels.How to progress through the game: For multiplayer games, players pick characters, set rules and locations for where they want to play and then duke it out. In Solo Mode, characters play through a long, side-scrolling adventure, beating up enemies along the way as they watch short cinematics starring their favorite characters.Characters: Mario, Samus, Bowser, Donkey Kong, Solid Snake, Meta Knight, Kirby, Pikachu, Zero Suit Samus, Link, Zelda, Pit and Wario, to name just a few. Anyone and anything from a Nintendo universe could appear in this game in one form or another.Special powers/weapons/moves/features: Anything from a Nintendo game could conceivably be in this game, whether it's a musical score, an obscure item or a character that shows up to help the fighters. Super Smash Bros. Brawl is eminently customizable, so players can choose the frequency of items appearing, adjust musical scores and basically play the game however they'd like. Items range from baseball bats to proximity mines to Poké Balls to Assist Trophies, which spawn characters like Hammer Bros. and Sim City's Dr. Wright to attack others.Super Smash Brawl Tournament WinnersLA Region Winner - David SegalSF Region Winner - Jason CaroMA Region Winner - Daniel JungNY Region Winner - Jensen SantiagoTournament National ChampionDaniel Jung * This action-packed fighting game features a ridiculous number of characters that have appeared on Nintendo platforms, from Mario to Link to Pikachu ... to Solid Snake! As they square off in famous locales drawn from the rich history of Nintendo, literally anything can happen - and usually does. With limitless customizing options, items and weapons that boggle the mind and a wealth of modes, this game has truly infinite replayability. * Super Smash Bros. Brawl features a sprawling adventure mode called "The Subspace Emissary" that's a full game in and of itself. Players jump and brawl their way through enemy-packed side-scrolling levels, meeting up with other characters, watching incredible cinematics and taking on massive bosses. * For the first time, this celebrated series is going Wi-Fi, allowing up to four players to brawl, no matter where they may be.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20080309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wii Sports + Wii Sports Resort (USA) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Wii Sports + Wii Sports Resort</name>
		<desc>A bundle containing Wii Sports and Wii Sports Resort on a single game disc that was bundled with some Wii consoles.

Wii Sports is a compilation of small sports games designed to be a showcase for the Wii's motion sensitive controller. Each game has several practice modes, and there is a Fitness Age feature to measure your daily improvement at all games.

Explore the Wuhu Islands with Wii Sports Resort, the sequel to the Wii launch title, Wii Sports. Wii Sports Resort includes and takes advantage of a peripheral called Wii MotionPlus, which enhances the player's motion control in the assorted sports. Available in this game are:</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xenoblade Chronicles (USA, Asia) (En,Fr,Es).wbfs</path>
		<name>Xenoblade Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Join the battle for Bionis to repel the invasion of a terrifying mechanical army and uncover the secrets of a mystical sword called the Monado in Xenoblade.Xenoblade Chronicles is an epic role-playing game which takes place on an immense game world on the remains of two giant titans, and features fast-paced real-time battling. The game heavily focuses on exploring vast landscapes and immerses you into the game with cinematic cut scenes.The story focuses on Shulk and the Monado, a mystical sword that gives his bearer great powers, and a war between humans and robots.The game?s real-time battles has an action oriented approach, giving you the chance to unleash special attacks and strategies by selecting them from a command gauge; the battling also is interlinked with the affinity between characters.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20120406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
