<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Alienfront Online (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Alien Front Online</name>
		<desc>Alien Front Online is a tank driving shoot-'em up that focuses on online play. The premise is a classic alien invasion of earth. Non-friendly aliens descend to the earth and put up strongholds around globe. You can choose to fight the resulting battles from the side of the army or the side of the aliens.

In online mode, this game supports 4 player vs. 4 player battles. 

In single player mode, there are 30 missions for each side. You move from mission to mission in a branching storyline with multiple endings.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Armada (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Armada</name>
		<desc>Ten millennia after the initial wave of colonization of the universe, humans have developed into distinct races adapting to their newfound homes. While there is peace between the races, there is no sense of unity. This all changes when, without warning, a bio-mechanical Armada wages war on the whole of humanity. Now as a starship captain representing one of the six main races of humanity, your charge is to take the fight to the Armada and save humanity.

Gameplay consists of commanding a starship as you explore the universe, taking out Armada opposition where you see it. Along the way you can take missions and answer calls for help which will provide you with valuable experience and credits to upgrade your ship. In this way, you can build your strength until you are ready to take on the Armada full force in an attempt to end the threat once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Metro 3D</developer>
		<publisher>Metro 3D</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bangai-O (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bangai-O</name>
		<desc>Ever wanted to just unleash the ultimate weapon? Blow up 500 enemies at once? Cause the ultimate amount of mayhem ever? In true Treasure fashion...you just got that power!

As the pilots of the Bangaioh mech, you've got to stop a mad group from taking over the world by giving them a little dose of insane destruction. Wanna just be crazy and let them kill you? Go ahead...just hit that trigger before it happens...

The Nintendo 64 version was only released in Japan. The Dreamcast version exists in the U.S. and Europe.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Entertainment Software Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Stinger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Blue Stinger</name>
		<desc>After an object from outerspace hits Dinosaur Island and surrounds it in a protective cocoon, you are left stranded to uncover the secret that could end life on Earth as we know it.
You play sea rescue expert Eliot Ballade, or weapons specialist Dogs Bower. Explore the island, solve puzzles and avoid hazards in seven areas and 230 locations. You can swim, drive, climb and fight, hand-to-hand or with the arsenal at hand.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannon Spike (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cannon Spike</name>
		<desc>Originally an arcade game, this shooter was converted and is now found on the Dreamcast. Somewhat similar in style to Smash T.V. in gameplay, you do battle in ten levels, containing two to four areas each.
Players can choose from a variety of characters including Mega man (or Rockman) from the Mega man series, Knight Arthur from Ghost 'N' Goblins series, Charlie and Cammy, both from Street Fighter series and B. B. Hood from Darkstalkers as well as two original characters: Shiba and Simone.
The different characters use slightly different attacks but each share the setup of one regular ranged attack and one powerful ditto as well as one regular and one powerful mêlee attack.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ChuChu Rocket! (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>ChuChu Rocket!</name>
		<desc>ChuChu Rocket is an action puzzler, designed predominantly as a multi-player game. You have indirect control over mice, and must guide them to the safety of a rocket, and away from a cat. You do this by placing arrows on the ground, which they will follow. The multi-player game is a frantic all-against-all duel, in which each player's mice will only follow instructions of their own colour. You can play this mode on your own against CPU opponents, or take on a series of predefined puzzles</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Smash (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Smash</name>
		<desc>You have embarked on a succession of stages. The scenery is set: your character, a wall as well as fixed or moving geometric shapes. You must, with the help of the perfect equipment of cyber tennis player, knock out these geometric shapes. Once the work is done, you can move on to the next stage. Very nice, this program also takes time into account. Indeed, this one must never completely pass, otherwise, it is a nasty Game Over which will occupy most of your screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega rosso</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi</name>
		<desc>Get behind the wheel of one of the 4 taxis and become one of the craziest drivers by picking up your passengers and getting them back to their destination as quickly as possible. Choose the shortest routes in these bustling cities and master your driving to earn maximum dollars. For even more fun, a very rhythmic soundtrack adorns these crazy road adventures!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the smash hit Crazy Taxi puts you in the driver's seat once again with 4 new drivers to choose from, and a brand new city to wreak havoc in based on New York City.

In Crazy Taxi, you crashed your taxi through the streets as fast as possible, making money by performing stunts and picking bringing passengers to certain destinations. For Crazy Taxi 2, you can pick up more than one passenger at a time, meaning more money faster, new stunts including the 'hop', which allows you to hop over buildings and take the quick route past the traffic, and plenty of mini games, such as Crazy Golf.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyber Troopers - Virtual-On - Oratorio Tangram (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cyber Troopers Virtual-On : Oratorio Tangram</name>
		<desc>Virtual-On: Oratorio Tangram on Dreamcast is a fighting game in which you can see colossus of steel face off against each other. Choose your mecha-robot (big robot) and activate the machine. Whether it's with a cyber sword or your rockets, smash your opponents into a junkyard before they cut your batteries.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./D2 (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>D-2</name>
		<desc>D2 on Dreamcast is a game combining survival-horror, shooting game and role-playing game. You play Laura, lost in the Tundra after a plane crash and suffering from amnesia. Your progress in the game will reveal clues allowing the heroine to gradually regain her memory.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WARP</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daytona USA (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Daytona USA</name>
		<desc>Just like the arcade version, pick one of three tracks (beginner, advanced, or expert) and either automatic or standard transmission. A pounding music soundtrack kicks in as you are slapped into your car to await the green light. The game offers both a traditional arcade mode with checkpoint time splits and a special PC mode that pits you against the other cars over different race distances. The PC mode also offers more car choices, with a variety of speed, acceleration, and grip characteristics. It even rewards successful players (meaning those finishing first, second, or third in the difficult setting) by offering up to ten more upgraded cars to drive. Once underway, the goal is to work from last to first as smoothly and quickly as possible
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead or Alive 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive 2</name>
		<desc>The arcade conversion adds an improved tag feature, with new stadiums to fight in, new character moves to play with, and plenty of windows, walls and ledges to fall over and crash through. Unlike Tekken Tag Tournament, however, DOA2 also includes a single player mode, a dodge button (allowing you to move left and right away from attacks), and multi-level arenas.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20250508T154042</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecco the Dolphin - Defender of the Future (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Ecco the Dolphin : Defender of the Future</name>
		<desc>Hundreds of years in the future, mankind and dolphins live peacefully together and share the earth. Dolphins, who are much more intelligent than they seem, act as the earth's caretakers, while dolphins and humans explore the galaxy. An alien force, known as the Foe, seeks to end this happy existence. The Foe damages the Earth's defense system, and alters history for the worse. One extraordinary dolphin, Ecco, must travel through time to set things right. Ecco is a 3d underwater adventure game. There are more than 25 aquatic environments to explore. Ecco must communicate with other ocean creatures and learn to manipulate his environment if he is to succeed in defeating the Foe.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elemental Gimmick Gear (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Elemental Gimmick Gear</name>
		<desc>A mysterious planet Fogna... you awaken one day after a prolonged sleep, look around and realise you have been asleep for quite a while - thousands of years... The people who saw you during your sleep named you the Sleeper. You were discovered by an archaeological team, and an ancient machine, which was dubbed "Elemental Gimmick Gear" by the archaeologists, was found near you. You are a young man, but in fact you are several thousand years old. Now you must discover your past, the past of the planet, and the purpose of the mysterious Elemental Gear. This game is an action RPG. The player can move around the battlefield, using various physical attacks, such as punch, spin, etc., and also elemental (magic-like) spells. The game is mostly 2D, except the boss battles, which are in full 3D. There are also many puzzle-solving areas and mini-games included within the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evolution - The World of Sacred Device (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Evolution : The World of Sacred Device</name>
		<desc>Evolution is a dungeon crawling game that follows the adventures of Mag Launcher. Mag Launcher and his companions use Cyframes, technology discovered in ancient ruins. These Cyframes are sought after by adventurers who explore caverns to find them.
Combat in Evolution is non-random and occurs whenever the character touches an enemy. The battle system uses 3D graphics and is turn-based, with each individual combatant having their own turn.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evolution 2 - Far Off Promise (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Evolution 2 : Far Off Promise</name>
		<desc>The events narrated in Evolution 2 on Dreamcast begin six months after those of the previous installment. You control the same team as in the first episode namely Mag, Linear Canon, Gre Naid, as well as adventurers Chain and Pepper. It's always about exploring dark dungeons in search of hidden artifacts.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Swing! Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa (USA).chd</path>
		<name>F355 Challenge : Passione Rossa</name>
		<desc>F355 Challenge on Dreamcast allows the player to tame the brand's racing car on the prancing horse. An Arcade mode and a Championship mode are offered. You will have the choice between 6 official circuits (Suzuka, Monza, Sugo, Motegi, Lang Beach) and several colors for your Ferrari.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Pro Wrestling D (Japan) [T-En by Irvgotti452].chd</path>
		<name>Fire Pro Wrestling D</name>
		<desc>Choose from 200 fighters, most of them from official American and Japanese competitions. The game offers, among other things, the possibility of replaying old legendary matches and trying to change the outcome.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>S-Neo</developer>
		<publisher>Spike Co</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Wrestling</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fur Fighters (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es) (Rev B).chd</path>
		<name>Fur Fighters</name>
		<desc>A group of baby stuffed animals are kidnapped from their families by the Stupid Bears (an evil gang of stuffed teddy bears, of all things!), and it is up to the Fur Fighters to save the young ones. The group that you control ranges from Kangaroos and Penguins to Cats and Dogs, all with their unique abilities and styles of fighting, which you must use to not only defeat the Stupid Bears, but complete puzzles and specific objectives along the way. You can control only one character at a time, but there are teleport areas so that you can change your character to one that can complete the tasks at hand.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / TPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GigaWing (USA).chd</path>
		<name>GigaWing</name>
		<desc>Gigawing on Dreamcast is a shoot'em up split into 5 levels, to which is added a boss at the end of the game. Destroy anything in your way while protecting yourself from attacks thanks to reflect score, a magnetic bullet-proof barrier . The player has the choice between 4 ships, each with its own weapons and a different pilot.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GigaWing 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>GigaWing 2</name>
		<desc>The third game in the Takumi/Capcom arcade shooter trilogy, Giga Wing 2 was originally designed for the Naomi arcade system and later ported to the Dreamcast. It is a top-down, vertical-scrolling shoot-em-up featuring four-player simultaneous action, high-res 3D graphics, and an orchestral score. There are four characters to choose from, each with his own storyline and fighter/spaceship. Each ship has its own weapon type and speed. Like the previous Giga Wing and Mars Matrix games, gameplay is designed around bullet absorption/reflection mechanics, large numbers of enemies, and giant boss fights. Giga Wing 2 adds the ability to choose from two different bullet reflection powers: reflect force and reflect laser. The reflect force repulses enemy shots, while the reflect laser uses them to charge up a beam weapon.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Grandia II</name>
		<desc>Ryudo has been hired to protect a young priestess who must participate in a ceremony to halt the encroaching rebirth of Valmar, the God of Darkness. Embroiled between the forces of good and evil, Ryudo must follow his destiny and save the people he detests so much.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunbird 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Gunbird 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the arcade sleeper Gunbird blasts its way onto Sega's Dreamcast! Take flight as one of seven crazy characters as you battle the Queen Pirates in search of the world's biggest treasure hoard! This Dreamcast version features a guest appearance by Capcom's Morrigan Aenslaed as a playable character, who never appeared in the arcade version.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Headhunter (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).m3u</path>
		<name>Headhunter</name>
		<desc>After awakening from a coma in a sterile hospital room, Jack Wade realizes that his memories, his identity, and even his mind have all been stolen. In order to regain what he has mysteriously lost, Jack must embark on a shadowy quest that puts his headhunting skills to the test. As Jack or his accomplice Angela Stern, you must use stealth tactics or your arsenal of weapons to fight through seedy biker hangouts, gas-filled shopping malls, and futuristic laboratories.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amuze AB</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hydro Thunder (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Hydro Thunder</name>
		<desc>Port of Midway's arcade boat-racer. The premise is non-existent, you simply rev up the engines and go on 13 water courses set in Antarctica, the far east, the Greek isles, etc. on different types of futuristic boats. Races use the usual arcade checkpoint system and scattered across the courses you'll find an assortment of power-ups and upgrades like nitro boosters. 

Graphics are entirely 3D with reflective water effects and realistic bouncing and bucking in the boats. Multiplayer competitions are supported for 2 players on the PlayStation version.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikaruga (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ikaruga</name>
		<desc>Vertical shoot-em-up ported from the Naomi Arcade version. Ikaruga is more or less a sequel to Radiant Silvergun by Treasure, on the Sega Saturn.
Based on a two-colors system, the player has to switch between the black &amp; white sides of his ship during gameplay.
The black side is immune to black enemy bullets which it consider as bonus, and dies on impact with a white enemy bullets. Your own black bullets damages white enemies twice as more as white bullets. And vice-versa for the white side. Those properties makes a balance between protecting yourself well and killing enemies fast.
This aspect, combined with specific enemy patterns and a combo system makes Ikaruga an original shoot-em-up with a dose of strategy.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Illbleed (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Illbleed</name>
		<desc>Illbleed on Dreamcast is a survival horror. You play as a teenage horror movie fan who has received an invitation to experience a horror-themed amusement park. Unfortunately, you lost sight of your three friends who were with you and you are now alone ...</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crazy Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Grind Radio (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jet Grind Radio</name>
		<desc>The government is trying to curb the activities of young people in Tokyo-To ...
Equipped with super fast rollerblades, it is not easy to get your hands on them! The music of Professor K, DJ of the pirate radio station Jet Set Radio, brings these young people together and inspires them to fight for their freedom of expression: so now it's up to you to grab your spray paint and cover the walls of the room. city of tags! But beware of your rivals who also want to tag the walls of your neighborhood. You will therefore have to associate yourself with cool characters who will help you in your projects. And do not forget that the police are on your tail: you will have to be quick to escape them. Jet Set Radio is 100% speed, fun and above all super funky!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./JoJo's Bizarre Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>JoJo's Bizarre Adventure</name>
		<desc>Based on the Japanese manga/anime of the same name, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure is a 2D fighter from Capcom. Take on the role of one of 18 characters and battle your friends in Arcade Mode, or take on the role of Jotaro "JoJo" Kujo and his friends in Super Story Mode as they battle their way to the evil vampire, Dio Brando, in order to save the world!

A Dreamcast version also exists, but without the Super Story Mode and a couple of missing characters. Both games were ports of Capcom's arcade fighter, JoJo's Venture and its update, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain : Soul Reaver</name>
		<desc>You play as Raziel, once a vampire in the service of Kain, then fallen because having the potential to take the place of his master. You must help him achieve his revenge by ridding the game levels of any bloodsuckers that cross your path.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mars Matrix (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mars Matrix</name>
		<desc>Mars Matrix: Hyper Solid Shooting on Dreamcast is a very popular shoot'em up genre on the SEGA console. The game is based on a system of absorbing the shots of your opponents when you keep the fire button pressed, you can then return the energy gathered in the form of more powerful shots.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom 2</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom 2: New Age of Heroes is the sequel to the 2D fighting game Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes. 
The game allows you to tag in all three players (instead of two, while the third is only used for special attacks, in the predecessor).
There are now up to 56 characters to use (most you have to unlock), including new characters like Jill Valentine from Resident Evil and Tron Bonne from Mega Man Legends.
Another new gameplay feature allows your team mates to come in during battle and give you a little health boost. This helps in lasting the distance in Survival mode, but they can also be hit by on coming attacks from the enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MDK2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>MDK 2</name>
		<desc>MDK with enhanced graphics, new weapons and gadgets, new playable characters, deeper storyline, focuses on different types of gameplay (i.e. puzzle solving, shoot 'em up, sneaking around). You progress through the game as a team of three characters playing each one at a time: Kurt Hectic - janitor with a sleek coil suit (good for sniping and long distance fighting), The Doctor- a scientist, inventor, and Kurt's employer, and Max- the lovable six legged robotic dog built by the Doc. As the Doc you have to find different parts and put them together to make weapons to defeat your enemies, and as Max it's an all out gun battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BioWare</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MSR - Metropolis Street Racer (USA) (Rev A).chd</path>
		<name>Metropolis Street Racer</name>
		<desc>Enter a new age of driving, a new form of thinking and feeling, and totally immerse yourself in the most advanced driving game ever created. Your 'Kudos' is the only path to success, since this is a unique test of skill, style and precision, which spans the streets of London, Tokyo and San Francisco. Be astounded by the realism, push your limits round 250+ different circuits, in hundreds of challenging events. Indulge up to 8 people in a unique multiplayer experience, and prepare yourself for the ultimate internet Kudos Challenge. From established racing game developers, Bizarre Creations, and featuring music from the renowned Richard Jacques, this game will change the way you think about driving forever.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Napple Tale - Arsia in Daydream (Japan) [T-En by Cargodin v1.0].chd</path>
		<name>Napple Tale - Arsia in Daydream</name>
		<desc>The player controls Arsia, a young girl, wandering the town of Napple, and to restore peace, Arsia and her familiar creatures will need to collect six petals.
Although the game is primarily a platform game, there are a lot of people to talk to. Exploration parts are mostly in Napple with a 3rd person view, while platform levels are 2D side scrolling. In these levels, Arsia usually has to complete them and fight a boss.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chime Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ooga Booga (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ooga Booga</name>
		<desc>Ooga Booga is a party-game on Dreamcast. The action takes place on a tropical island that emerges from the waters with each full moon, it is then the opportunity for the four tribes to compete in many games aimed at harvesting magic, thus preventing the explosion of the volcano present on the island.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20010911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outtrigger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Outtrigger</name>
		<desc>You might be good enough to join Interforce, a private enterprise formed to fight terrorism, but to lead the team, you'll have to prove you're better than the other members. Outtrigger is a combat game that features both first- and third-person perspectives, and while it comes with a batch of single-player scenario missions, the game favors multiplayer mayhem. A split-screen mode for up to four players allows friends to compete in-house, and online cooperative play lets you form teams over the Internet. Settings include castle ruins, an observatory, abandoned train stations, and more. The game's cache of weapons includes flamethrowers, photon torpedoes, and rocket launchers, to name a few.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA AM2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star Online Ver. 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star Online Ver. 2</name>
		<desc>The world's first online console RPG gets an update with PSO Ver. 2. New items and weapons, new online games and play modes, a Dressing Room, new areas to explore, and the Ultimate Difficulty mode have been added. You can also bring in your PSO characters, modify them in the Dressing Room, and attempt Ultimate Mode and strive to reach Level 200!

PSO Ver. 2 functions as a stand-alone game, as well as an add-on. You don't need to have owned PSO in order to play.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>MMORPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone</name>
		<desc>The creators of Street Fighter add a new dimension to 3D fighting. In Power Stone, 2 fighters take to multi-level arenas with Power Stones and other weapons lying around for use.

Each game contains Power Stones. When you have enough stones (between three to five), your character transforms into an almost unbeatable warrior, with an all-new range of moves (although this does not last for long).</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20250508T154233</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone 2</name>
		<desc>The world's most revolutionary fighting game does it again! Power Stone 2 takes go-anywhere, grab-anything combat, and introduces awesome new innovations to the hit arcade fighting series. Now, up to four players wage insane battles in fully interactive, multi-level stages. Master over 120 different items used in battle - weapons, vehicles traps, power-upsand more! As if chaotic swashbuckling battles weren't enough, combine forces with other players to battle monstrous bosses to win the game!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Justice (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Project Justice</name>
		<desc>Project Justice is the sequel to Shiritsu Justice Gakuen: Nekketsu Seishun Nikki 2. It once more thrusts you into the shoes of a team of students, trying to find out what is causing all the bizarre events.

Players pick a school to fight for and smash their way through the other schools, questioning them until you find out what is happening. The gameplay is very similar in style to the original Rival Schools, featuring bombastic special moves and team-up attacks, along with the same, highly caricatured students.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake III - Arena (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Quake III Arena</name>
		<desc>Quake III Arena on Dreamcast is a multiplayer oriented first person shooter. A varied and complete arsenal is at your disposal to organize a happy butchery alone or in teams. The classic modes of the genre are all there (Capture The Flag, Possession, Deathmatch ...). The major advantage of this episode on console is the possibility of online play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>No Cliché</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2 - The Great Escape (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>Rayman 2 : The Great Escape</name>
		<desc>A gang of pirates have invaded Rayman's world to seize its unique creatures and sell them to an intergalactic circus. Our mighty hero, Rayman, has been captured and stripped of his powers. He flees captivity and embarks on a dangerous mission to return to his conquered world where he must liberate all of his imprisoned friends from the pirates.

Just like Bugs Bunny: Lost in Time, the game is rendered in full 3D and contains action, adventure and mind twisting puzzles!
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Code : Veronica</name>
		<desc>The action of Resident Evil: Code: Veronica on Dreamcast originates two months after the events of Resident Evil 2 and 3. Claire Redfield still in search of her brother Chris, infiltrates Umbrella, but is unmasked, then imprisoned on an island. Once released, she must face the creatures, once again victims of the T-virus.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rez (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>Rez</name>
		<desc>Rez is a fast-action shooter that takes you deep into the world’s computer network. The “Project K” Network has recently been upgraded to handle the rapid expansion of the information age and the core, known as “Eden,” holds the most advanced artificial intelligence the world has ever seen. Unfortunately, Eden cannot handle the ability to create her own thoughts and buckles under the pressure in an existential breakdown. She is lost deep inside the system, and you’re the only one that can bring her back online, saving the world from utter chaos.

You must blast complex viruses, unlock passwords, and destroy firewall bosses as you search for Eden. Each stage is in a constant state of flux dependent on your shooting techniques, which ultimately control the music and colors of your environment. The deeper you get into the dreamlike cyber world of Rez, your form will evolve or devolve depending on your progress.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>United Game Artists</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samba de Amigo (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Samba de Amigo</name>
		<desc>Samba De Amigo is a highly unique game:  a maracas simulation.  Game play is based around a special maracas controller that you use to interact with the music.  The controller senses which region in space out of a possible 6 that the maracas are in.  It also senses when the player shakes the maracas.  As the music plays, the player must shake the maracas in the appropriate region with proper timing to progress.  A standard controller can also be used if you do not have the maracas controller, which is sold separately.

The music in the game comes from a wide variety of sources.  Some of the songs are traditional samba music, while others are recognizable pop tunes, like "Macarena" and "Tequila."</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Rhythm</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seaman (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Seaman</name>
		<desc>Ever want to raise your own pet, starting with nothing but a tiny egg? How about raise him to be a smart-mouthed, viper-tongued companion who listens to you and gives you a dose of smart-ass advice? Look no further than the lab of Dr. Jean Paul Gassé, who left you a few eggs from the mysterious creature known as the Seaman. Now you've got the chance to raise your very own Seaman. Talk to him, tickle him, feed him...just don't rub him the wrong way, or you'll end up with an angry pet and a big headache.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivarium</developer>
		<publisher>Vivarium</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Bass Fishing (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Bass Fishing</name>
		<desc>Explore the exciting sport of bass fishing! Based on the arcade hit, explore eight fishing locations as you try to catch the biggest fish possible! You can choose between fourteen different lures, and compete in four tournaments, starting with you as an amateur, up to a Masters Classic tournament!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sims</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fishing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Rally 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Rally 2</name>
		<desc>Sega Rally 2 is the sequel to Sega's hit arcade game, Sega Rally. This game, like it's predecessor, is based on Rally racing. Rally racing is unique in that races take place on both race tracks and off-road courses. The courses in this game reflect this nicely. Some take place in the desert or forest, others take place in cities.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Smash Pack - Volume 1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Smash Pack : Volume 1</name>
		<desc>Sega Smash Pack: Volume One was the first, and ultimately the only collection of classic Sega games released for the Dreamcast.  It contains only some games in common with the PC Sega Smash Pack and Smash Pack 2 so is an iteration of the concept rather than a port of that collection.

This collections features ten emulated Genesis/Mega Drive titles. These games are Altered Beast, Columns, Golden Axe, Phantasy Star II, Shining Force, Vectorman, Revenge of Shinobi, Sonic the Hedgehog, Streets of Rage 2 and Wrestle War. This was the first American release of Wrestle War.

It also included two games that had been previous released for Dreamcast: Sega Swirl, which had been given away on various discs and Virtua Cop 2, which had been previously available for Dreamcast only in Japan.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>Witness to the murder of his father by the mysterious Lan Di, the young Ryo Hazuki swears to find him to avenge his father. This is the starting point of this extraordinary adventure that is Shenmue on Dreamcast, a game at the crossroads of a multitude of genres that includes its share of action and confrontations inspired by martial arts.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA AM2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue II (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).m3u</path>
		<name>Shenmue 2</name>
		<desc>After crossing the sea, he will arrive from the East, from a distant land... the epic of Shenmue is reborn. In this second part, Ryo Hazuki arrives in Hong Kong to pursue his mission: to try to avenge the death of his father and discover the mystery of the Phoenix Mirror. Shenmue II is a universe at least three times larger than the first one: more characters to communicate with, more knowledge to acquire, more new experiences. But beware, you can't trust everyone!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA AM2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skies of Arcadia (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Skies of Arcadia</name>
		<desc>Arcadia is a world where continents float high above, and people travel by airships. Among the countries of this world, the most powerful one is the Empire of Valua. Guided by its greedy admirals, Valua strives to possess all the power in Arcadia. The boy Vyse and the girl Aika are members of the Blue Rogues - noble pirates who attack only Valuan war ships. During one of their confrontations with a battle ship, they encounter a girl named Fina, who is on an important mission whose secret she cannot tell yet. Involved in the conflict with the Empire of Valua, the trio of the heroes must explore the whole world of Arcadia in order to defeat the admirals.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Overworks</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es) (Rev A).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure</name>
		<desc>Yet again Sonic and friends find themselves wrapped up in the schemes of Dr. Robotnik. This time he plans to exploit the power of Chaos, a malevolent being that feeds upon the power of the Chaos Emeralds. In their own ways five heroes will do what they can to save Station Square and, perhaps, the entire world.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic has returned! This time, his nemesis Dr. Eggman has teamed up with Shadow, a dark hedgehog with a mysterious past, and is aiming once again (like he doesn't) to rule the entire world with the power of the Chaos Emeralds! It's up to Sonic and his friends to stop Eggman and put him out of business for good!

With new features such as a story line told from the view of both the good guys and the villains, greater speed, and an improved A-Life system, Sonic Adventure 2 is poised to be Sonic's greatest and most dangerous mission yet!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20010619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soulcalibur (USA).chd</path>
		<name>SoulCalibur</name>
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games.  A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends.  

All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.  In addition to high, mid, and low attacks, characters can hold/throw, block, and perform special attacks -- one or more of which is deemed "un-blockable" and must be avoided by ducking, jumping, or rotating around your attacker. 

In addition to several locales in which to fight and alternate models/costumes per character, the Dreamcast conversion of Soul Calibur contains many additional features over the arcade coin-op, including hidden characters and locales, a campaign mode, and tournament mode.  There is also a "museum" where you can view character profiles and view motion-captured martial arts demonstrations.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Channel 5 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Space Channel 5</name>
		<desc>Hey there, Space Cats! Some pesky little aliens called Morolians are trying to take over Earth, and they're forcing the population to dance endlessly! Space Channel 5, the planet's news channel, has sent the grooviest reporter they have, Ulala, out to cover the latest happenings, but those little Morolians also have to be taught a lesson! So it's now up to Ulala to dance and groove with the aliens to beat them at their own game and free the population of Earth! Get dancin', Space Cats, 'cuz we're gonna give those aliens a little taste of their own groove!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dancing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I - Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Episode I Racer</name>
		<desc>Based upon the Pod Racing scenes of Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, your mission as young Anakin Skywalker or as one of a collection of strange characters from around the Galaxy is to compete, survive and win in the high speed challenge of Pod Racing.

Each character has a unique Pod that can be upgraded with the credits you win after each race. Finish first to gain the most prestige and compete in greater and more challenging tracks, including the now famous race along the sand dunes of Tatooine that determined the destiny of many lives.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./StarLancer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>StarLancer</name>
		<desc>It's 2160, and the Eastern Alliance has launched a surprise attack on the Western Coalition's fleet and decimated it. The call has gone out for volunteers to become Alliance fighter pilots, and you have signed up with the 45th Volunteer Squadron.

Designed by Chris and Erin Roberts, the creative force behind the Wing Commander/Privateer megaseries, this space fighting simulation features the genre's standard mission types: escort, fighter sweep, interception, attacking space stations, fighting in asteroid fields, etc.

12 pilotable fighters (you can choose which you fly as well as missile loadout, but not all are available in the early missions), 9 enemy fighter types.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Anvil</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III : 3rd Strike</name>
		<desc>3rd update to Street Fighter 3, Capcom's classic 2D fighter. The new version includes new music and artwork, more super arts for each character, a grading system, a manual throw system, path selection and new characters including (YES!) Chun-Li. The Dreamcast port also offers a training record option were you can record a certain move or combo and have it play against you over and over to see how you can parry it, plus a "system direction" option which allows you to modify practically every aspect of the game (air-blocking, combo limits, etc.) to customize it to your liking.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stupid Invaders (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Stupid Invaders : The Epic Adventure of Five Incredibly Stupid Aliens</name>
		<desc>Five aliens crashland on Earth, and hide out in an abandoned house while they repair their spaceship. In the meantime, Dr Sakarin, an evil alien-collecting scientist has found out about them, and sends out his evil henchman Bolok to capture them. You play as each of the five aliens, and must help them escape.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titanium</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Magnetic Neo (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Super Magnetic Neo</name>
		<desc>In Super Magnetic Neo, a gang lead by evil, foul-mouthed baby Pinki has taken over Pao Pao Park.  The professor must stop her, so her sends Super Magnetic Neo, a little boy robot with a powerful electromagnet on his head.

The game has some resemblance to the Crash Bandicoot series in that some levels have you running toward the camera, have a side-view, or have you riding an animal.  It contains some running, jumping and switch-flipping much like any 3D platformer.  However, it does have a unique magnetism aspect.  Positive and Negative charges are represented by red and blue.  Neo's head can act as a positive or negative pole.  This is called his magnogimmick.  Using the principle of opposites charges attract and similar charges repel, Neo can pull himself toward platforms, then launch off them, or navigate many related environmental puzzles such as pulling himself into teleporters or swinging on magnetic pendulums.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of the Berserk - Guts' Rage (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sword of the Berserk : Guts' Rage</name>
		<desc>Taken from Kentarou Miura Kenpuu Denki Berserk's work, Sword of the Berserk: Guts' Rage is considered by some to be a spin-off of the manga.
Indeed, the story takes place as Guts crosses the devastated lands of Midland with Puck and his beloved Casca (in post-traumatic amnesia) in search of? Griffith.
However, by crossing a caravan with people of the spectacle, our hero will discover in a village with people infected by parasitic plants, the Mandragora. This is when our hero is going to cut mandrake.
Directed by Yuke's, Sword of the Berserk necessarily presents itself as a hack 'n slash type action game. To decide, to slay this will be the player's mission throughout the game, however, it will be necessary to pay attention to the "QTE" sequences in certain passages. Success, Gattsu continues on his way. Failure ? Well, we'll have to slaughter the beast.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tech Romancer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tech Romancer</name>
		<desc>Tech Romancer is a 3D beat-em-up with a difference; the difference being that, rather than controlling one of a set of martial artists, you control one of a set of huge robots (or mecha). Ranging from the absurd (A huge, spherical mech with a boat and bus for feet, a house for a head, train for one arm and office building with wrecking ball for another) to the "typical" anime styled mecha (Beam-firing chest gem, detatchable rocket-powered fists) to a more westernised idea of a mech (Huge, sluggish, equipped with heavy cannon, rockets, missiles and land-mines), you're bound to find at least one which suits you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Test Drive Le Mans (USA) (En,Fr,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Test Drive Le Mans</name>
		<desc>Take on the LeMans endurance racing challenge! Join one of the 25 factory teams take one of the over 50 vehicles (designed with assistance of actual teams) on the eight different LeMans circuits. The actual wear and tear are simulated. Tire wear, oil and fuel consumptions...  Day and night and back to day driving...
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Test Drive V-Rally (USA) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
		<name>Test Drive V-Rally</name>
		<desc>Test Drive V-Rally on Dreamcast is a racing game featuring 16 official World Rally Championship cars and 10 unlockable bonus cars, playable in over 80 stages in 12 different countries. Alone or up to 4 on the same screen, the software has four distinct modes, completed by an editor and a channel generator.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eden</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Commander (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Toy Commander</name>
		<desc>Toy Commander on Dreamcast is an action game simulating a toy war. Slip aboard one of the 30 miniaturized vehicles (tank, plane, helicopter, car ...) and complete the 50 missions proposed to claim the honorary title of "Toy Commander". The game also gives rise to multiplayer clashes (1 to 4 participants in versus or cooperation mode).</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>No Cliché</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unreal Tournament (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
		<name>Unreal Tournament</name>
		<desc>In Unreal Tournament on Dreamcast, step into the arena and take part in the biggest sporting event in the universe. This FPS composed of four game modes (Deathmatch alone or in a team, Domination, Capture the flag) offers multiplayer games in arenas where the main rule is to survive while taking care not to give your opponents the slightest respite.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic Games</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Fighter 3tb (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 3tb</name>
		<desc>Virtua Fighter 3tb (Team Battle) is a port of the arcade game Virtua Fighter 3 to the Dreamcast. The "tb" adds a team battle mode which was not present in the coin-op. For those that do not know, the Virtua Fighter series is your classic beat-em-up, with a bunch of characters all trying to kick, punch, throw and body slam the bejesus out of each other. Each of the characters has over a hundred possible moves and the game plays very faithfully to the original. The game features interesting arena to fight in which are more like real locations in they are not flat and some parts can be broken away during the match.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis</name>
		<desc>Imagine how a tennis player feels when he enters the arena, the crowd is cheering, the atmosphere electric, the adrenalin rushes... Well now you can with Virtua tennis, the most lifelike and playable tennis game ever! Play as one of eight licensed players and uncover the secret stars. As well as the traditional arcade mode you can play in the exhibition mode, with 4 player action via doubles play.

Once you've mastered those modes take on the world in the world circuit mode, with unique training games, diffrent challenges and shops to buy clothing, equipment, stages and playing partners. 
Virtua Tennis, so realistic you can almost taste the strawberries and cream.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20000711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Tennis 2K2</name>
		<desc>Sequel to the original game which was released two years prior. The games graphics have been improved, and there is a greater roster of players to choose from. The most noteworthy addition is that of female players, such as Monica Seles and Venus and Serena Williams. You cannot however play as a male against a female.
The gameplay is a lot faster than the original. The players you control move a lot faster, as do the AI computer players. Less diving, but more getting at shots that go behind you and over the shoulder shots.

The game modes from the original are the same, featuring tournament mode, where you play against the pros; exhibition mode for a one-on-one, best-out-of-three game; and world tour mode which now features the option of creating and customizing your own player. Build you player up, buy equipment and hire pros to play in doubles matches with you.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20011023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wetrix+ (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wetrix+</name>
		<desc>The idea for this game is that you must build barriers on the arena to stop the water from leaking out. As you go along, rain starts to fall onto the arena, so you better keep the walls as high as possible. Too much on the screen, though, will start and earthquake. Ice blocks fall to freeze the water. Bombs drop, leaving holes in your walls and fireballs dry up the water. Simply go as long as possible to get as high a score as you can. There is a practice mode available, and you can play against a friend.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zed Two</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Metal (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt).chd</path>
		<name>Wild Metal</name>
		<desc>Wild Metal on Dreamcast is a tank battle game featuring 5 playable armored assault vehicles and 17 mechanical opponents. The objective is to locate and capture 8 sources of energy spread over three original planetary systems: the tundra, the Aztec desert and the red planet.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20000201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Revenge (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Zombie Revenge</name>
		<desc>A top-secret government plan to use undead soldiers has gone horribly wrong. Experience this nightmare intensely in Zombie Revenge on Dreamcast.
Alone or in a network, command one of the 3 special agents of your choice and rid the city of zombie scum using the many weapons scattered on the course.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
