<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Days of Ruin (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Advance Wars : Days of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Days of Ruin takes place in an entirely new world where a large-scale meteor shower triggered massive global destruction that eradicated 90 percent of the population. After the catastrophe, the survivors have formed together into militaristic bands that are warring over the last remaining scraps of civilization. You'll take control of Will, a young military cadet (whose hair is admittedly just a little spiky) who quickly becomes embroiled in the conflict at the outset of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA, Australia).zip</path>
		<name>Advance Wars - Dual Strike</name>
		<desc>The first entry of the long running Wars series for the Nintendo DS. This turn-based strategy game has you commanding an Allied Nations army against the vile Black Hole.Choose from a handful of COs (commanding officers), each with his own unique CO power </desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).zip</path>
		<name>Aliens - Infestation</name>
		<desc>GAME OVER, MAN!  The Xenomorph, the ultimate killing machine, returns.  Only the Universe's toughest, the Colonial Marines, can exterminate the galaxy's most feared species.  Can you fight off the terror of the alien infestation?

-Choose you squad and watch the dynamic story system adapt
-Pick up where the Aliens crew left off and fight through the U.S.S. Sulaco, planet LV-426, and more!
-Load up with iconic weapons from the film, including pulse rifles, smart guns, and flamethrowers.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Wayforward</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animal Crossing - Wild World (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing : Wild World</name>
		<desc>Animal Crossing: Wild World is a 2005 social simulation video game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld game console, and is the second game in the Animal Crossing series.
Wild World focuses on living in a remote village populated with anthropomorphic animals, where the player is encouraged to perform any number of tasks, such as collecting and planting. Like all Animal Crossing titles, the game is synced to the console's clock and calendar, allowing the game to be played in real-time, which affects the occurrence of in-game events based on the current time of day or season. Wild World also utilizes Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, which notably allows players to travel and visit the villages of other players via online play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avalon Code (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Avalon Code</name>
		<desc>Avalon Code is a hack and slash Action-RPG that takes place in a world about to end.  Choosing between a male or female avatar, the player is given the Book of Prophecy from which the world will be remade.  Everything in the world can be scanned and recorded into the Book of Prophecy, and players can further redefine an entry's properties by mixing and matching pieces of code.  

Codes in Avalon Code are Tetris-like chunks which fit into each book entry's grid of available code space.  Think of these codes like genes in a DNA sequence that you can grab and move with the stylus.  For example, elemental properties (such as fire) can be incorporated into a weapon, allowing you to melt ice.  Removing codes from enemies allows you to weaken them, making them easier to dispatch.

Players string together light combos and can perform charged special moves.  Additionally, the player can begin a Judgment Link which juggles the enemy higher and higher (with proper timing) which yields precious HP, MP and Gem bonuses.  Dungeons are somewhat unique in that each room is a timed challenge, with requirements such as hitting all switches, defeating all enemies, Judgment Linking xN, and/or various combinations of these.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bangai-O Spirits (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bangai-O Spirits</name>
		<desc>Bangai-O Spirits is a handheld remake of the original, this version has the player take the role of two Bangai-O pilots, Riki and Mami, as they fly in an omni-directional path across environments, blasting away bad guys.  The game is a mix of action, shooter and strategy, as the player can use ten different weapons (Napalm Missiles, Homing Missiles, Bounce Missiles, Break Missiles, Direct Missiles, Freeze, Reflect, Sword, Bat and Shield) with the ability to choose from two different Bangai-O suit classes, each with their own strengths and weakness.

The main game is at the bottom of the dual-screen while the top is used for a map, so the player can track their place in the game.  Players can also pick up power ups along the way while avoiding vast amount's of bad guys and avoiding special themed traps for each level.  There are over 160 levels to play as well as a level editor that the player can use any of the other levels as a template.

Players can also play 4-way co-op using Wi-Fi and players can also share data, scores, levels among others using Sound Load technology, where the info is converted into a sound file that is recognized and decoded by other DS' using its microphone and uploaded on the internet where the player can download information through audio devices and played to their own DS' microphone to download the information.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080812T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The team that developed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow returns to bring the sequel, CastleVania: Dawn of Sorrow, to the Nintendo DS. This time, you must infiltrate a castle belonging to a cult that is planning to resurrect Lord Dracula. Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow lets you defeat evil spirits using the "Magic Seal" system which utilizes the Nintendo DS touch screen. You can trade captured souls with other players using the wireless system as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<desc>Set in the early 19th century, this installment of the long running Castlevania series takes a slight departure from the typical series storyline. A secret monastic organization, Order of Ecclesia, is charged with finding alternative ways of combating the hordes of undead summoned by the ever-returning evil lord Dracula, as the Belmont clan has apparently gone into hiding. Shanoa, a young acolyte of the Order, is chosen for her extraordinary magical abilities to wield Dominus: the ultimate spell against evil. As she is about to complete the ritual to absorb Dominus a rogue acolyte named Albus steals the three tomes containing the spell. Shanoa is then dispatched to track down Albus and return him and the spell back to the Order.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Portrait of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Take control of two heroes, Jonathan Morris, a vampire killer and his close friend Charlotte Orlean, a girl with tremendous magical ability. Amidst the chaos of World War II, two mysterious sisters emerge, working to resurrect Dracula and David and Charlotte are all that stand in their way.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger (USA) (En,Fr).zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>What begins as a carefree day at the Millennial Fair for a young man named Crono turns into a huge adventure. He will be thrusted into the ultimate trip through time and space, encountering new friends, defeating the forces of evil, and encountering the one who would destroy the flow of time.
Chrono Trigger is a role-playing game, with the usual game mechanics fare. As the characters grow in power, not only their ability scores increase, but they also learn new "Techs".
The game utilizes the ATB (active time battle) combat system from Final Fantasy game. Apart from normal Techs, it is possible to use Double and Triple Techniques.There are no random battles in the game, as all the enemies are visible on screen, and it's even possible to just pass by them entirely.
The game allows you to face your ultimate adversary at different points of time, which leads to several different endings.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20081125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra 4 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Contra 4</name>
		<desc>Contra 4 for the Nintendo DS is a direct sequel to 1994 SNES Contra III: Alien Wars. Two years after the defeat of Red Falcon - the first wave of the alien colonization fleet, the main invading force Black Viper approaches Earth. The heroes of the original Contra series - Billy Rizer and Lance Bean as well as two newcomers - Mad Dog and Scorpion are now humanity's last line of defense against total annihilation.

This installment of the long-running series adds dual screen gameplay, enabling the player a wider view, and a 2-player co-op mode via local Wi-Fi connection. Each player is now given two weapon slots which can be filled with any one of the game's many weapon power-ups and switched at will with a press of a shoulder button. The game features nine levels set in such classic Contra locations as Jungle, Waterfall and a pseudo-3D Base.
As a bonus, the cartridge contains an illustrated history of Contra, as well as the Contra and Super C original NES games.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dig Dug - Digging Strike (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dig Dug - Digging Strike</name>
		<desc>Dig Dug: Digging Strike, utilizes the original Dig Dug game and its predecessor, Dig Dug II, placing both elements in the game with the dual-screen technology, placing the original Dig Dug on the bottom screen and the overhead view of Dig Dug II on the to</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullets</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Heroes : Rocket Slime</name>
		<desc>The peaceful land of Slimenia has been suddenly invaded by a mysterious cartel called "the Plob" who then proceed to kidnap all the slimes in the capital city of Boingburg. Our protagonist Rocket is the only slime left behind and must embark on a journey throughout Slimenia to save his friends and uncover the Plob's nefarious plot!Part of a series of Slime Mori Mori games in Japan Dragon Quest Heroes is full of adventure stages that take advantage of our hero's bouncing and stretching abilities as he works to solve the challenges of each area in the game and rescue his captured slime friends. Each adventure stage culminates in Rocket hopping aboard a colossal slime-shaped player-customizable war machines. Pit tanks against a friend's in exciting player-vs-player action using the Nintendo DS wireless multiplayer game feature!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IV : Chapters of the Chosen</name>
		<desc>The Legends of Zenithia starts here!

A prestigious army captain, an adventurous princess, a humble merchant, two sisters, and you, the hero. Dive into this unique adventure, and discover the grand tale told through the experiences and emotions of characters from all walks of life.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies</name>
		<desc>In Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies, players begin their adventure as a city guardian who is sent to retrieve a sacred trees fruits, which have the power to grant wishes. Players travel the world, conquer fearsome monsters and unravel an epic storyline. During their journey, players will encounter mighty opponents in fast-paced battles, and also interact with a colorful cast of characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker</name>
		<desc>DQM : Joker, you play an aspiring monster tournament competitor. The goal is to recruit and train a team of monsters powerful enough to win the Monster Tournament of the Granpool Archipelago.

The game uses the same combat engine as Dragon Quest VIII, turn-based where commands are issued, and then the game shows the results in 3D.

There are many monsters spread over 8 families so it is up to the player to find a combination that takes into account the strengths and weaknesses of the monsters. The player's character also doesn't fight directly in the battles, but aids the monster team with potions and other power ups.

Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection is also used to fight a battle vs AI opponents ranked similar to the players monsters, however this can only be done once per day so the daily rewards aren't over collected.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2</name>
		<desc>Dragon Quest Monsters: Joker 2 gameplay follows closely to its predecessor. Players explore areas and tame wild monsters into their party. Monsters fight in turn-based combat and grow stronger. The battle system itself is very similar to previous Dragon Quest Monsters games. The player controls up to three monsters that make up the party, and can issue them direct orders or set them to one of 4 AI settings. This game features two new monster sizes: large monsters, which use up two spaces on one of the player's two benches, and gargantuan monsters, who take up an entire bench on their own. The main character, who is henceforth referred to as the Hero, does not directly participate in battles except for when the player uses items. He can, however, use any item in his possession and not just the ones 'in hand'. 311 monsters from the Dragon Quest games appear in Joker 2, with a few new species, many from the original "Dragon Warrior Monsters" games. This is the second game in the series to feature Wi-Fi support, after the first Joker game, and the first to support direct battling between players.
Square Enix released Joker 2 Professional, an expanded version of the game, on March 31, 2011. Professional features over 100 new monsters, as well as new regions and abilities, but the same story. Players are able to import their old monsters from the original game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest V: Hand of the Heavenly Bride</name>
		<desc>The legend of Zenithia continues!

What begins as an innocent voyage of a boy traveling alongside his father develops into an eye-opening adventure that transcends generations. You - a hero in the making - determine your own path, choose your own wife and befriend a wagonload of quirky monsters along the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VI : Realms of Revelation</name>
		<desc>Coming to North America for the first time, Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation for Nintendo DS brings the classic console title into the handheld scene. Explore two parallel worlds while distinguishing reality from illusion and seeking to discover the true meaning of your very existence.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elite Beat Agents (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Elite Beat Agents</name>
		<desc>Elite Beat Agents is the spiritual sequel to Osu! Tatakae! Ouendan!  In this rhythm-based music game, the Elite Beat Agents are a special task force dedicated to helping people in need and righting wrongs through the power of song. 

The game is played entirely through use of the stylus.  Timing is required to line up the rings that close in on the circles to ensure the proper beat for the song.  Beats can also be scored by dragging a glowing ball through a set line area until the end of a beat.  Finally, players will be required to turn a spinner as quickly as possible during a music break.

The level stories are mostly comedic, where the Agents will help a girl and her jock boyfriend go steady, help a speeding taxi driver deliver a baby, and even help a weather reporter chase away rain clouds to go on a picnic with her son.  Each level is accompanied by popular songs such as Madonna's "Material Girl", Chicago's "You're the Inspiration", or Jamiroquai's "Canned Heat", among others, for 19 music tracks total.

Multiplayer allows gamers to compete against each other via single-card or multi-card play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>iNiS</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dancing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy III (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>In 2006, Final Fantasy III reached North American shores in an official update/remake for the Nintendo DS, finally bringing all of the main Final Fantasy entries to the United States for the first time.

Raised as an orphan by Nina and Elder Topapa in the village of Ur, Luneth, his shy friend Arc, the rebellious Refia and the brave soldier Ingus are chosen as the Four Warriors of Light to send to restore balance to the crystals, and save the world from imminent destruction.

Taking the original game which debuted on the NES, Square-Enix had updated the title with a new cinematic intro, improved graphics and a touch-screen interface to move characters and utilize selection menus. There is also Moogle Mail, a Wi-Fi feature that allows players to send messages to each other via their DS systems. The game has also some revised story elements, detailing the adventures of four friends who find each other, each with new backstories.

Final Fantasy III is a traditional turn-based RPG, which were popular back in the '80s and '90s, but introduced refinements to the genre, such as smarter battle AI. Final Fantasy III is also known for two major milestones in the history of the series: Its introduction of the cheerful Moogles, as well as the introduction of the job system, allowing characters to switch professions throughout the game for new abilities.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy IV is a full remake of the classic RPG originally released for SNES, known as Final Fantasy II in the West. This version features real-time 3D graphics, "super-deformed" character designs, and voice acting in cut-scenes. It introduces new gameplay elements, including increased difficulty, a menu option for reading party conversations, and the addition of "augments" which provide characters with extra abilities and spells. Other updates include bonus items for completing map exploration, a customizable new summon for Rydia, and a new quest involving the "naming" moogle.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics A2 : Grimoire of the Rift</name>
		<desc>Embark on a journey through the vibrant world of Ivalice this summer with FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift. As the third entry in the Ivalice Alliance series, this follow-up to the 2003 Game Boy Advance release brings the popular tactical franchise to the Nintendo DS for the first time. FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift will introduce newcomers to an engaging turn-based, grid-oriented battle system as they make new discoveries alongside the hero in this lighthearted adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20080624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Tactical RPG</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem : Shadow Dragon</name>
		<desc>Prince Marth and his band of loyal followers are the last hope in freeing Archanea. Alternate turns with the enemy, and shape up your army to suit your strategy by selecting from dozens of units with unique spells, abilities, and weapons. Each unit has its own strategic benefits, so guide them wisely or risk losing them on the battlefield.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Tactical RPG</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost Trick - Phantom Detective (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Ghost Trick : Phantom Detective</name>
		<desc>Ghost Trick: Phantom Detective, known in Japan as simply Ghost Trick, is an adventure game developed by Capcom for the Nintendo DS. 
Ghost Trick's story centers on the recently deceased protagonist Sissel, and his ghost's struggle to discover who he was when he was alive and who killed him. The player assumes the role of this ghost, who has the ability to perform various Ghost Tricks to solve puzzles and navigate the world around him.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20110111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - Dark Dawn (USA, Australia) (En,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun : Dark Dawn</name>
		<desc>After going dark six years ago, 2010 will see a new dawn. Golden Sun DS updates the popular portable Golden Sun role-playing series with an impressive graphical style. This installment follows the story of the previous heroes' descendants and immerses players into the magic of its adventure by pushing the boundaries of intuitive touch-screen controls.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: Chinatown Wars is an entirely original entry into the critically acclaimed Grand Theft Auto series, and brings a new level of interactivity to its sprawling open environments. With the use of the DS touch screen, players navigate their way through the streets as they uncover the truth behind an epic tale of crime and corruption within the Triad crime syndicate, delivering the unprecedented amount of depth that has become a true trademark of the franchise.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hotel Dusk - Room 215 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Hotel Dusk: Room 215</name>
		<desc>Los Angeles, 1979. You are Kyle Hyde, an ex-cop turned salesman trying to track down a missing friend. Clues lead you to an eerie, old hotel rumored to have one very strange room - a room where wishes are granted. It's up to you to unravel the mystery in Hotel Dusk: Room 215, a gritty new graphic adventure for Nintendo DS. Players hold their DS like a book and use the touch screen to grill characters, search for clues and solve mystifying puzzles. Players follow the plot twists and turns as they hunt for their missing friend and investigate the mysteries of Hotel Dusk.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cing</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (USA) (En,Fr).zip</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts : 358/2 Days</name>
		<desc>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days revolves around Roxas, the "other" hero from
Kingdom Hearts II. Players follow Roxas through his days among Organization XIII's ranks, unraveling the events that took place during the year that Sora was asleep, and ultimately revealing one of the Kingdom Hearts saga's most shocking secrets. Players and their friends will join Roxas, his friend Axel and the mysterious fourteenth member of Organization XIII on a journey across charming, vibrant worlds full of Square Enix's and Disney's beloved characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>H.A.N.D</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Canvas Curse (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby : Canvas Curse</name>
		<desc>Your DS stylus has been infused with the power to paint! When Kirby gets turned into a ball by an evil witch, your hand-drawn rainbow paths become the only way he can find power-ups and reach the gates of each world. Draw loops to make him speed up, make ramps to jump danger, and draw walls to block laser beams and cannon blasts as you explore seven worlds packed with adventure! Get in touch: Stun enemies, break blocks, and much more - all with a touch of the stylus! Be a copycat: Tap Kirby to dash into enemies and copy their abilities. Eleven abilities in all! So many modes: Try timed challenges, take on bosses, or play simple but fun mini-games!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Squeak Squad (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby : Squeak Squad</name>
		<desc>Kirby - Squeak Squad is a platform game for Nintendo DS. You play the famous and adorable Kirby, who can breathe in air to inflate like a balloon and thus cross the many levels of the game while gliding. The small creature is also able to swallow its enemies and take their strength, and must stop the "Squeak Squad", a group of malicious rodents.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Mass Attack (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby Mass Attack</name>
		<desc>Kirby: Mass Attack is a single player Side-Scrolling, Real-Time Strategy game for Nintendo DS that features both new adventure, and a new gameplay mechanic uniquely suited to the Nintendo DS. Gameplay includes the ability and necessity of controlling multiple versions of Kirby simultaneously in order to defeat enemies, solve puzzles and complete challenges.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star Ultra</name>
		<desc>Kirby's back with a bunch of fun adventures!  Explore Dream Land and defeat King Dedede, tame the ferocious Dynablade, explore a huge cave, take part in a gluttonous race, vandalize Meta Knight's ship, the Halberd, explore the entire galaxy, and more!

Kirby Super Star Ultra is an updated remake of Kirby Super Star, a popular SNES game which is broken up into seven main games.  In addition to those previous games, Ultra includes five new games and three new sub-games.  Listed are just some of the new ones:

Revenge of the King: King Dedede wants a rematch!  This game is a toughened up version of Spring Breeze, the opening game.

The Arena: Every boss that Kirby has met throughout the game, one after the other!  Try to beat them all!

Meta Knightmare Ultra: Play through the first five games as Meta Knight, with his own special abilities and powers!  Speed is the key!

Kirby Card Swipe: Watch the top screen, and quickly pick the correct card.  Be the first to do it thrice!

Kirby on the Draw: Enemy targets pop up, tap them as they appear.  Don't tap the bombs!

Snack Tracks: Eat all the food on your tracks.  Don't eat the bugs, bombs or rocks!

As with the original, Ultra features a heavily featured multiplayer mode.  All games can be played either co-operatively or competitively.  Spring Breeze can even be played co-operatively if your friend doesn't have a copy of the game!</desc>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Window - The Secret of Cape West (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Last Window : The Secret of Cape West</name>
		<desc>Los Angeles, 1955: A man has broken into a safe. A mysterious figure then enters the room, aims a gun at him, and fires. The victim collapses, dead. He drops a diamond which he removed from the safe, and a photograph of a man and a young boy lies next to it. 
1967: A woman is slouched over a table, apparently dead, in a room in the Hotel Cape West. A man is seen leaving the room. 
1980: Kyle Hyde wakes up in his car and speaks on the phone with Ed Vincent, his boss at Red Crown; Vincent fires Hyde for his negligence. He travels to the Cape West Apartments, where he lives. Just before he enters the building, he notices a mysterious woman wearing a hat and sunglasses. Soon afterwards, he discovers that the Cape West Apartments are to be demolished at the end of the month, and all the tenants are vacating. As he opens his apartment door, he notices a letter that tells him to find out what secrets the apartments hold, and an object known as the "Scarlet Star." Thus begins Last Window: The Secret of Cape West.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cing</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Phantom Hourglass (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Phantom Hourglass</name>
		<desc>Continue the Wind Waker adventure in Link's first DS game.

The epic story of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker continues as Link finds himself lost and alone in unknown seas in a new adventure. Featuring intuitive touch-screen controls and innovative puzzles, The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass offers new challenges for fans of the series and an easy-to-grasp introduction for gamers new to The Legend of Zelda. But time grows short, and only the Phantom Hourglass can buy Link the minutes he'll need to survive.

Many months have passed since the events of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker, and Link, Tetra and Tetra's band of pirates have set sail in search of new lands. They come across a patch of ocean covered in a dense fog, in which they discover an abandoned ship. Tetra falls into danger when she explores the ship alone, and Link falls into the ocean when he attempts to rescue her. When he washes up unconscious on the shores of a mysterious island, he is awakened by the sound of a fairy's voice. With the aid of this fairy, he sets off to find Tetra and his way back to the seas he once knew.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Spirit Tracks</name>
		<desc>All aboard for adventure as Link sets off on a quest to restore the spirit tracks and keep an ancient demon locked away.

Take control of your own train as you explore the vast land by rail. As the conductor you plan the route, set the speed and watch out for enemies and obstacles, clearing the path with the powerful built-in cannon.

Link has a valuable new companion. While navigating dungeons, he's accompanied by a Phantom, a hulking suit of armour that responds to his commands. Tap the Phantom to take command of him, then draw a line on the touch screen to direct him where to go. The stout Phantom can walk through fire or lava, be used as a platform to carry Link above dangers, or even run interference to block Link from harm.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi : Bowser's Inside Story</name>
		<desc>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story is the third game in the Mario &amp; Luigi series of games. Players control Mario and Luigi simultaneously in the side-scrolling platform environment of Bowser's body, while also controlling the Koopa King himself in the top-down world of the Mushroom Kingdom. Similar to games like Earthbound, enemy encounters are seen as actual enemies that players can avoid or attempt to strike early. The actual battles are a combination of turn-based menu attacks, and timed reactions to enemies during battle. By watching the way an enemy reacts, you can anticipate their attack and avoid it or counterattack.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Dream</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi : Partners in Time</name>
		<desc>The famous Mario Brothers return in this sequel to the humorous Superstar Saga. In this adventure, Princess Peach takes a trip in a time machine, but when it returns, there's only a monster inside! The heroic brothers travel back in time only to discover that evil alien life forms known as the Shroobs have taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and no-one is safe! They soon meet up with their younger selves, and set out to stop the alien menace, not to mention rescue the Princess!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart DS (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Kart DS</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart DS is the continuation of the long running racing game series that began on the Super Nintendo. It features 16 new tracks as well as 16 tracks from the previous 4 games, with each set split up into the Nitro and Retro Grand Prix respectively. Eight racers are initially available, each with two go-karts to choose from. A number of characters and additional karts are also available to unlock. New items have been added to the arsenal, including a Blooper squid that squirts ink onto the screens of other players and a Bullet Bill power up that transforms the player into a giant, fast-travelling bullet on autopilot.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem! (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong: Mini-Land Mayhem!</name>
		<desc>At the grand opening of Mario's third theme park, the first 100 guests receive a new Mini Pauline toy. Donkey Kong arrives as the 101st guest and finds himself out of luck. He grabs Pauline and heads into the park with Mario and his Mini Marios in hot pursuit. The fourth game in the series adds new challenges and new opportunities for users to share what they have created.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2 - March of the Minis (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2 : March of the Minis</name>
		<desc>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2: March of the Minis is an action/puzzle game where the object is to bring as many Mini-Marios to the exit door as possible by solving the puzzle. All the puzzles are fairly small and take up anywhere from one screen to four screens (2x2) in size. All the Mini-Marios that are collected in each room are then used in the Donkey Kong boss battle at the end of the world. All of the control is done with the stylus; no buttons are used at all.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Meteos (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Meteos</name>
		<desc>Designed by Masahiro Sakurai and produced by Tetsuya Mizuguchi, Meteos was the DS's second big-name puzzle game (after Polarium).  

Most of the game's action takes place on the bottom of the DS's two screens, where colored meteors plummet downwards towards a planet's atmosphere.  There, they form columns that the user can manipulate with either the stylus or a combination of the D-pad and A button.  When three or more meteors of the same color are arranged either vertically or horizontally, they "ignite" and rocket up towards the top screen.  Rockets carry upwards any other metors that happen to be above them, and by stringing together several ignitions it is possible to lift many blocks at once.  The ultimate objective of the game is to lift as many metors as possible back into "orbit" in the top screen; the game is over if the bottom screen fills up completely with meteors.  Meteos features many different "planets" that the user can play on, each with subtle variations (such as in gravity) that affect gameplay.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime - Hunters (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime : Hunters</name>
		<desc>It's the battle of the bounty hunters! Join Samus Aran as she goes up against six deadly rivals in a race to claim ancient artefacts that could spell doom for the galaxy. Metroid Prime Hunters transports pure first-person shooter action to Nintendo DS with pinpoint Touch Screen control and astonishing 3D graphics.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Might &amp; Magic - Clash of Heroes (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Might &amp; Magic - Clash of Heroes</name>
		<desc>Might &amp; Magic: Clash of Heroes is a mix of a role-playing and puzzle-game on Nintendo DS. The title offers five types of heroes, with specific powers and units,  as part of five scripted campaigns. The game also offers a Free mode which allows you to configure skirmishes, as well as a two player mode to face a friend.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capybara Games</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Moon</name>
		<desc>Renegade Kid returns to the DS with this second game, Moon. After updating the Renegade Engine, used for the first game, Dementium, this new shooter for the DS puts you in the role of Major Edward Kane, Chief of Military Operations for the Extra-Terrestrial Encounter Organization. The year is 2058 and you and your squad are sent to the moon to investigate strange things that have been happening at the new moon bases. An alien hatch has been discovered at the construction site of one of the bases. So you need to take charge and take care of business.

As its predecessor, it tries to fill the lack of shooters for Nintendo's handheld. With the stylus for aiming, the D-pad for moving and the shoulder buttons for shooting, Moon revisits the late 90's style of shooter started by the Quake series.

The game features 24 episodes, 7 different weapons, various levels of difficulty, bonuses and other game modes to unlock.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Kid</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nanostray (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nanostray</name>
		<desc>In Nanostray on DS take control of a ship in a futuristic shoot'em up. Improve the firepower of your ships throughout the 18 levels and modify their features in real time via the DS screen. In addition to the single player mode, thanks to the wi-fi features of the console you can play in 2 player co-op.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin'en Multimedia</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nanostray 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nanostray 2</name>
		<desc>Nanostray 2 is similar in gameplay to the original Nanostray, but has a few new features.  You can play over thirty missions with over six different game modes to play in.  You can play the Adventure Mode, which shows cut-scenes to tie into the story or you can skip the story and play Arcade mode and just go for the highest score possible.

You can also play in challenge mode, completing a set of four challenges that unlocks a new simulator mode challenge, which is similar to Arcade mode, but with a different scoring system.  It has sixteen massive bosses and over one hundred different types of enemies and you can change control styles, using the classic or using the left or right handed touch control.  There is also a Nanogauge that fills up when you destroy multiple enemies, earning you bonus multipliers.

You can play against a friend in duel mode or play in cooperative mode using multi-cards and can also upload your high scores online using the Wi-Fi connection.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin'en Multimedia</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros. (USA).zip</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>In an all new 2D side-scrolling adventure, Mario and Luigi return after nearly fifteen years. The first traditional Mario Bros. game since Super Mario World.

The character models are rendered in real time 3D, allowing for a far greater number of moves ever before seen in a Mario Bros. title. Also as the game is on DS, the touch screen allows players to store an additional power-up and view the distance still to go in a level.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors (USA).zip</path>
		<name>999 : Nine Hours Nine Persons Nine Doors</name>
		<desc>Junpei, a fairly normal college student finds himself involved in a deadly conspiracy that he couldn't have possibly imagined. He awakes aboard an old passenger ferry, dazed and confused he stumbles around the room trying to reclaim his memories. First thing he noticed was a number roughly drawn on the cabin's door. A bright red number 5. Junpei's memory then returned and he remembered what happened right before becoming unconscious! A mysterious person with a gas mask crossed his mind. He remembered the haunting words he spoke, I'm gonna make you play the game, the Nonary Game' the game of life or death".</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20101116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Aksys Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden - Dragon Sword (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Dragon Sword</name>
		<desc>This action-adventure title is presented in a third person, pseudo-3D manner, meaning all the game-models are rendered in full 3D, but the world the player travels around in is pre-rendered. When played, the Nintendo DS is held sideways, as in Hotel Dusk: Room 215 and Brain Age: Train Your Brain in Minutes a Day!. The left screen shows the area map, while the right displays the main gameplay, when set for right-handed play, and reverse when set for left-handed play.
Set six months after Ninja Gaiden, Ryu Hayabusa has rebuilt the Hayabusa Village. When fellow villager and kunoichi, Momiji, is kidnapped by the Black Spider Ninja Clan, he is forced to find her, while uncovering the secrets behind the mysterious Dark Dragonstones and their relation to the Dragon Lineage</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninjatown (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninjatown</name>
		<desc>Ninjatown is a family-friendly tower defense game for the Nintendo DS that features the artwork and characters of ex-EGM editor Shawn Smith's "Shawnimals" universe. In the game, players must build Ninja Huts at key spots along a set pathway to defend each of the game's 36 levels from the invading forces of Mr. Demon. Players can build up to eight different kinds of Ninja Huts, each kind containing its own category of Ninja, from Wasabi pea-shooting Sniper Ninjas to bearded Mountain Ninjas. 

There are also a variety of "Ol' Master Ninja Powers" that can help the player in a pinch. These range from blowing into the DS microphone to push enemies backwards with a gust of wind to tapping enemies on screen in a short period of time in order to deal extra damage to them.

The game is divided into 9 "districts", each containing 3 standard tower defense maps and 1 boss map. Each level in the game takes about 10-15 minutes to complete, with the full game clocking in at around 6-8 hours.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20081028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Venan Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Southpeak Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nostalgia (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nostalgia</name>
		<desc>Set in an alternate-reality version of 19th-century Earth, Nostalgia casts you as Eddie, a headstrong Londoner who amasses a group of memorable companions to traverse the world in his steampunk-inspired zeppelin. As you navigate the open skies, you'll explore mysterious foreign locales, slay all manner of fantastical enemies, complete a variety of thrilling quests, and ultimately, save the world from unfathomable evil.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Okamiden (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ōkamiden</name>
		<desc>In a fitting reflection of the relationship shared with Amaterasu, the powerful sun goddess who embodied a wolf in Ōkami, the child deity Chibiterasu manifests in the form of a white wolf cub in Ōkamiden. The game is set nine months after the events of the previous game, and the young sun god is summoned to battle a sinister force that has drained the landscape of colour, leaving it withered and faded where once it was luminous with life.

Ōkamiden shares many gameplay elements with its predecessor, including the paintbrush used as a weapon against enemies and for puzzle solving. Chibiterasu can also team up with various companions during the game for additional abilities.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Peggle Dual Shot (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Peggle : Dual Shot</name>
		<desc>It's the ultimate Peggle... with dual-screen action! Shoot and clear the orange pegs from 120 levels spanning two full adventure modes in this action-packed PopCap hit! Learn 11 Magic Powers, score amazing style shots, and discover the exclusive Bonus Underground filled with valuable gems and power-ups. And the action doesn't end there take your best shot in Multiplayer Duel and Quick Play modes, then put your skills to the ultimate test with 90 challenges!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>PopCap Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright : Ace Attorney</name>
		<desc>Not everyone is innocent until proven guilty! Players star as a defense attorney, who must prove his seemingly guilty client's innocence no matter how dire the circumstances may seem. The game presents twisting storylines and intriguing gameplay in a comical anime style. Players must collect evidence, weed through inconsistent testimonies, and overcome corrupt agendas to ensure that justice prevails.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Visual Novel</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney - Justice for All (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright : Ace Attorney - Justice for All</name>
		<desc>The second game in the popular court room battle series from Japan introduces four new cases featuring new characters, plot twists and gameplay features. Players resume the role of Phoenix Wright, a defence attorney who must prove his client's innocence against the toughest of odds and most ruthless of adversaries. Players must exercise their legal prowess as they collect evidence, examine witnesses, analyse testimonies and seek the truth to ensure that justice prevails.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Visual Novel</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright : Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations</name>
		<desc>Phoenix Wright is back as the third game in the popular Ace Attorney hand-held franchise comes to the WiiWare service. As Phoenix Wright, you'll play through five shocking new cases in first-person perspective. The game features two unique modes of play. In Investigations Mode you'll survey crime scenes, interview witnesses and gather evidence. You'll then present findings, listen to testimonials and examine witnesses in Court Mode. Trials AND Tribulations also includes the "Psyche-Lock" feature that allows Phoenix to use a line of questioning to reveal inconsistencies in witness testimony.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Visual Novel</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Planet Puzzle League (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Planet Puzzle League</name>
		<desc>Take on the world in Planet Puzzle League, a simple but addictive puzzle game that you may recognize as Tetris Attack, Panel De Pon, or Pokémon Puzzle League.  Colored tiles rise up from a bin, and its your job to arrange them horizontally or vertically in lines of three or more of the same tile.  This causes them to disappear.  Advanced players will be able to arrange tiles so that when they land, they clear additional tiles to stop the tiles from rising and score even more points!

Planet Puzzle League features a wide variety of different game modes to keep even the most dedicated puzzler busy:

1.  Endless - Play forever until you fail.  The tiles rise faster over time.
2.  Clear - Remove all the blocks down to the 'CLEAR' line, buried deep down.
3.  Garbage Challenge - Garbage blocks rain down on your bin - clear as many as you can!
4.  Vs. COM - Play against the CPU.  Try to get their tiles to reach the top of the bin first!
5.  Time Attack - See how many points you can earn in two minutes.
6.  Puzzle - Either clear the preset mind-bending puzzles, or try the various missions that you are given.

Similar to Brain Age, Planet Puzzle League features a 'Daily' Mode.  Play these short games once a day to track your skill over a long period of time.  Are you getting better?  Or worse?

You can also play multiplayer modes of the game, either locally, or over Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.  Modes of play include Birthday Battle (play against people who share your date of birth), Free Play Battle (play an unranked match), and Friend Battle (play against Friends you've traded Friend Codes with).</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version</name>
		<desc>A NEW WORLD FILLED WITH NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN POKÉMON!
What are the true motives of Team Plasma and the mysterious N? What is the secret of the Legendary Pokémon? Adventure across the Unova region and discover all-new Pokémon!

The game changes with the seasons!

New battle strategies and moves!

This is Pokémon Black Version. The types and likelihood of Pokémon that will appear differ from Pokémon White Version. This game can communicate, battle, and trade only with the various language versions of Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version. After completing the main story, you can communicate with Pokémon Diamond, Pearl, Platinum, HeartGold, and SoulSilver Versions (English-language versions only) to transfer Pokémon to this game. Pokémon transferred in this way cannot be sent back. This game is not compatible with the Pokéwalker accessory. Basic reading ability is needed to fully enjoy this game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version 2</name>
		<desc>TWO POWERS COMBINE...A NEW LEGEND ARISES!
Set off on a new Pokémon adventure to save the Unova region! You and your Pokémon can accomplish anything together!

Unova, Two Years Later...

Film Movies at Pokéstar Studios

A New Story!

This is Pokémon Black Version 2. The types and likelihood of Pokémon that will appear differ from Pokémon White Version 2. This game can communicate, battle, and trade only with the various language versions of Pokémon Black Version 2, Pokémon White Version 2, Pokémon Black Version, and Pokémon White Version. After completing the main story, you can communicate with Pokémon Diamond, Pearl, Platinum, HeartGold, and SoulSilver Versions (English-language versions only) to transfer Pokémon to your game. Pokémon transferred in this way cannot be sent back. This game is not compatible with the Pokéwalker accessory. Basic reading ability is needed to fully enjoy this game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20121007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Diamond Version (USA) (Rev 5).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Diamond Version</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the next generation of Pokémon!
As a rookie Pokémon Trainer, you will need to catch, train, and battle Pokémon on your journey to become the Pokémon League Champion. You will face many challenges along the way, as you search for the Pokémon that rules time in Pokémon Diamond Version.

-Discover more than 100 new Pokémon in the Sinnoh Region!
-Meet goals and earn the ability to import Pokémon from your GBA versions!
-Battle and trade with your friends around the world using Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection!
-Watch as day turns to night with the return of the real-time clock feature!

</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - HeartGold Version (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon HeartGold Version</name>
		<desc>PREPARE FOR THRILLING NEW ADVENTURES AS LEGENDARY POKÉMON AWAKEN!
Explore the Johto region as you catch, train, and battle with your favorite Pokémon by your side. Reach for the sky--call forth the Legendary Pokémon!

Enjoy minigames with your trained Pokémon!

Travel with your favorite Pokémon!

Take your Pokémon with you! Introducing the Pokéwalker accessory!
The Pokéwalker is a special pedometer only for Pokémon HeartGold and Pokémon SoulSilver Versions. It can communicate with these games using an infrared signal!
By storing a Pokémon in the Pokéwalker, it can earn Experience Points and become friendlier as you walk in real life!
You can catch Pokémon and find items in the Pokéwalker, then transfer them to Pokémon HeartGold Version!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Pearl Version (USA) (Rev 5).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Pearl Version</name>
		<desc>This is the Pearl version of Pokémon. The differences between the Diamond and Pearl versions include how often and which types of Pokémon appear. This game can communicate with the Diamond version using Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection and DS Wireless Communications. This game can also be connected to the Ruby, Sapphire, FireRed, LeafGreen, and Emerald versions of Pokémon using the Dual Slot feature of Nintendo DS. This game CANNOT be connected to Game Boy, N64, or GameCube versions of Pokémon. It is also not compatible with any Pokémon Battle-e Cards.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Platinum Version</name>
		<desc>ANOTHER WORLD HAS EMERGED IN THE SINNOH REGION...
...A world where time and space are altered!
Catch, train and battle your favorite Pokémon, and discover ancient, mythical Pokémon in this exciting new adventure!

NEW DISCOVERIES, NEW CHALLENGES!

EXPANDED ONLINE OPTIONS!
New experiencs in the Wi-Fi Plaza and Battle Frontier!
*Wireless router and broadband access required for online play.

-This Platinum version of Pokémon, an extension of the Diamond and Pearl versions, contains new story elements and expanded play features, including different types of Pokémon.
-This game can communicate with the Diamond and Pearl versions and Pokémon Battle Revolution using Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection and DS Wireless Communications.
-This game can also be connected to the Ruby, Sapphire, Emerald, FireRed, and LeafGreen versions of Pokémon using the Dual Slot feature of Nintendo DS or Nintendo DS Lite.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon SoulSilver Version</name>
		<desc>PREPARE FOR THRILLING NEW ADVENTURES AS LEGENDARY POKÉMON AWAKEN!
Explore the Johto region as you catch, train, and battle with your favorite Pokémon by your side. Turn the tides--call forth the Legendary Pokémon!

Enjoy minigames with your trained Pokémon!

Travel with your favorite Pokémon!

Take your Pokémon with you! Introducing the Pokéwalker accessory!
The Pokéwalker is a special pedometer only for Pokémon HeartGold and Pokémon SoulSilver Versions. It can communicate with these games using an infrared signal!
By storing a Pokémon in the Pokéwalker, it can earn Experience Points and become friendlier as you walk in real life!
You can catch Pokémon and find items in the Pokéwalker, then transfer them to Pokémon SoulSilver Version!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version</name>
		<desc>A NEW WORLD FILLED WITH NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN POKÉMON!
What are the true motives of Team Plasma and the mysterious N? What is the secret of the Legendary Pokémon? Adventure across the Unova region and discover all-new Pokémon!

The game changes with the seasons!

New battle strategies and moves!

This is Pokémon White Version. The types and likelihood of Pokémon that will appear differ from Pokémon Black Version. This game can communicate, battle, and trade only with the various language versions of Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version. After completing the main story, you can communicate with Pokémon Diamond, Pearl, Platinum, HeartGold, and SoulSilver Versions (English-language versions only) to transfer Pokémon to this game. Pokémon transferred in this way cannot be sent back. This game is not compatible with the Pokéwalker accessory. Basic reading ability is needed to fully enjoy this game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version 2</name>
		<desc>This is Pokémon White Version 2. The types and likelihood of Pokémon that will appear differ from Pokémon Black Version 2. This game can communicate, battle, and trade only with the various language versions of Pokémon Black Version 2, Pokémon White Version 2, Pokémon Black Version, and Pokémon White Version. After completing the main story, you can communicate with Pokémon Diamond, Pearl, Platinum, HeartGold, and SoulSilver Versions (English-language versions only) to transfer Pokémon to your game. Pokémon transferred in this way cannot be sent back. This game is not compatible with the Pokéwalker accessory. Basic reading ability is needed to fully enjoy this game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20121007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Blue Rescue Team (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon : Blue Rescue Team</name>
		<desc>And if that's not enough of a dilemma, you've woken up one day to discover that you've mysteriously transformed into a PokÃ©mon yourself!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon : Explorers of Darkness</name>
		<desc>In this action-packed adventure, players journey as actual Pokemon through a fantastic land untouched by humans. Before the game starts, players take a test to help them figure out which of 16 Pokemon best represents their personalities. Players then experience their adventure through the eyes of a Pokemon as they explore the land and embark on an epic journey through time and darkness. They talk and team up with other Pokemon to set out on an epic voyage while navigating an endless array of randomly generated dungeons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon : Explorers of Sky</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky expands on the fun found in Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Darkness. Players become a Pokemon and team up with a partner Pokemon. Together the two set out on an adventure of exploration and discovery, ultimately saving the world from destruction.

With additional Pokemon to become, new Special Episodes and enhanced communication features, this is a grand adventure with a moving story and stunning finale. This game is a great starting point for players to enter the world of Pokemon Mystery Dungeon and for returning players to discover even more secrets.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon : Explorers Of Time</name>
		<desc>In this action-packed adventure, players journey as actual Pokemon through a fantastic land untouched by humans. Before the game starts, players take a test to help them figure out which of 16 Pokemon best represents their personalities. Players then experience their adventure through the eyes of a Pokemon as they explore the land and embark on an epic journey through time and darkness. They talk and team up with other Pokemon to set out on an epic voyage while navigating an endless array of randomly generated dungeons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>PokÃ©mon Company</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Curious Village (USA, Australia).zip</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Curious Village</name>
		<desc>After hearing about a strange inheritance dispute in the town of St. Mystere, Professor Layton and his young apprentice, Luke, travel there on behalf of Lady Dahlia, who has requested their presence to resolve the issue.  However, it quickly becomes apparent that St. Mystere is quite strange... all the townsfolk seem to be obsessed with puzzles, and Baron Reinhold's fortune isn't the only secret that the town has hidden...

Professor Layton and the Curious Village is a puzzle game which uses the works of Akira Tago, author of the Japanese series of Head Gymnastics books as its basis.  As both Layton and Luke, players explore the town of St. Mystere screen by screen.  Each screen contains puzzles, either hidden in the scenery or by talking to characters.  Upon finding a puzzle, the screen changes and the player is presented with the puzzle itself: the description of the puzzle on the top screen, and the puzzle (as well as the place to input the answer) on the bottom screen.  Some puzzles require simple calculation, some have a trick answer, while others are riddles.  The selection of puzzles is quite varied.  If the player gets stuck, they can purchase a hint with 'Hint Coins'.  However, these are limited - more can be found hidden in the game world, but there a set number of coins in the entire game.

Professor Layton has a visual style similar to that of a watercolor painting.  While most of the game does not have much animation, key story sequences are told in fully animated and voice acted scenes.  The game also used Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection to connect to the Internet and download additional puzzles for players to solve.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box</name>
		<desc>When Professor Layton and his assistant, Luke, receive a letter from the Professor's mentor, Dr. Andrew Schrader, Layton feels uneasy.  The letter mentions that Schrader has acquired an elusive artifact called the Elysian Box - legend has it that anyone who tries to open it dies.  The pair rush to Schrader's apartment, but it is too late - the box appears to have claimed another victim, and yet is missing.  The only clue is a ticket for the luxurious Molentary Express, found in the apartment.  Will Layton and Luke be able to solve this latest mystery?

Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box is the sequel to Professor Layton and the Curious Village, taking place directly after the events of the first game.  Players take the role of the titular professor and his assistant Luke as they explore the Molentary Express for clues to the mystery of the Elysian Box.  By talking to people and examining the environment, players discover puzzles, which when solved progress the story further.

As with the first game, puzzle can range from logic problems, to riddles, to simple calculation.  If stuck, players can spend 'Hint Coins' that they can find throughout the game - but there are a finite amount available, so they should only be used when needed.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Last Specter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Last Specter</name>
		<desc>Three years before the events in the first game, Professor Layton receives a letter from his old schoolmate Clark Triton. It states that ?a mysterious giant shrouded in fog has been laying waste to our houses.? The professor heads to the town of Misthallery to investigate, and is joined by Emmy, his new assistant. What is the meaning of all the destruction, and is it related to the village?s folklore legend of a ?specter?? The unfolding story details how Professor Layton and his apprentice, Luke, met.

Professor Layton and the Last Specter follows the structure that has become a staple for the series, in which the player is presented with a succession of puzzles scattered throughout the game world to solve with logic using the touchscreen, with bonus puzzles made available to download on a weekly basis.

In the Japanese and North American releases, the game also includes Professor Layton's London Life, a bonus role-playing game wherein the player?s character lives in Little London with Professor Layton and a number of characters from the series. Players can customize their character with special clothing and collect items and furniture. Some of these help the player?s character to enter certain areas of the city or perform tasks that help out the townspeople.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20111017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Unwound Future (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Unwound Future</name>
		<desc>Professor Layton and his assistant Luke attend the unveiling of a new invention called a time machine.  The Prime Minister of London is volunteered as a test subject, but the machine explodes and there is no trace of him.  With the Prime Minister missing, London is in chaos!  Shortly after these events, the puzzle-solving pair receive a letter, which has apparently been sent by Luke's future self, stating that London is in serious trouble.  The Professor and Luke follow the directions in the letter, which leads them to their most exciting adventure yet...

Professor Layton and the Unwound Future is the third installment in the Professor Layton series. As with the previous games in the series, players explore game scenes by tapping on areas of interest with the stylus.  Doing so can cause Layton and Luke to examine objects, talk to characters, finding hint coins (which can be spent on hints for difficult puzzles) and most importantly, discover puzzles that can be solved.  Puzzles range from math, to logic, to riddles to sliding block puzzles, as well as many more different types.  There are also "secret" areas in scenes which, when tapped, may leave a puff of dust or a rustle of leaves.  Repeatedly tapping on these areas reveals a hidden secret, such as a bonus hint coin, or even a hidden, more difficult puzzle.

New to Unwound Future is the addition of the 'Super Hint'.  While as with the previous games, you can spend a hint coin to unlock up to three hints, there is also another option.  Once these three hints have been exhausted, for the price of two hint coins, you can unlock a more detailed 'Super Hint' as a last resort.  There are also three new minigames incorporated into the game.  In the Picture Book game, you must place the correct stickers in the right spots to make a story that makes sense.  In the Toy Car game, you must place tiles which navigate a toy car around the board, collect all the objects, and then reach the goal.  Finally, in the Parrot game, you must tie ropes onto pegs to help your parrot deliver parcels to people who have requested them.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radiant Historia (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Radiant Historia</name>
		<desc>In the midst of an unending war for dominance between two super-powers, Special Intelligence Agent Stocke is assigned to a routine escort mission that goes horribly awry...</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Japanese RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Retro Game Challenge (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Retro Game Challenge</name>
		<desc>Arino wants to be the greatest gamer in the world, but he's continually defeated by his friends at every new game that comes out. His obsession has spawned a digital version himself within his own Nintendo DS. This digital version of himself has come to be known as "Game Master Arino", who haunts gamers around the world with retro game challenges. You have been chosen by Game Master Arino, and are now trapped in the 1980s until you can defeat his game challenges.

Retro Game Challenge, based on the Japanese TV show Game Center CX, has you playing faithfully-recreated clones of popular NES-era games, attempting to complete challenges and freeing yourself from Game Master Arino. You are accompanied by Arino himself as a young lad, who will cheer you on as you're playing each game. You can also read the latest gaming mags for tips, cheats, and previews of upcoming titles.

There are eight games total, each modeled after 8-bit classics such as Galaga (Cosmic Gate), Dragon Warrior (Gaudia Quest), and Ninja Jajamaru-kun (Robot Ninja Haggle Man). Each game has multiple challenges from Arino to complete, such as clearing a certain stage or earning a set number of points, and can also be played in a free play mode once all challenges have been cleared.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20090210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rhapsody - A Musical Adventure (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rhapsody : A Musical Adventure</name>
		<desc>Originally released in 2000, Rhapsody: A Musical Adventure is a musical RPG that has musical numbers, complete with vocals. The game has a wide appeal thanks to its simple game style and clean anime art. Players will take on the role of Cornet, who can talk to puppets and has a magical horn that grants wishes. She must save Prince Ferdinand, who has been turned into stone by an evil witch.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rhythm Heaven (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rhythm Heaven</name>
		<desc>Get ready to feel the rhythm!  Rhythm Heaven is a game based entirely around musical rhythm and timing.  The game is a collection of games based around a song, where the player must perform actions in time to the music to successfully complete the game.  All games are based around the simple motions of tapping, sliding and flicking the stylus.

As each game varies from each other, at the start of each game, you're given a brief tutorial to get the hang of how the game you'll be playing works.  Tasks for games include (but are not limited to) flicking to construct machinery, releasing the stylus at the right time to belt out a loud note, sliding to rub a lizard's tail in time to a mating dance beat, tapping to gulp down dumplings, tapping and flicking to harvest vegetables and get rid of moles, and more.  After every four games, a special "remix" game appears, which combines the previous games into a hectic mix, where you never know what will be up next.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dancing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rune Factory - A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<desc>You awaken to find yourself in an unfamiliar village with no memory of who you are or how you arrived. Mist, a beautiful young woman comes to your aid and helps you start to build a life for yourself on a farm. Till the land, grow crops, raise animals, catch fish and battle monsters!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070814T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory 2 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rune Factory 2 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<desc>In Rune Factory 2 the player, Kyle by default, is an amnesiac who wanders into the town of Alvarna and is discovered by a girl named Mana. 

Like in the first Rune Factory game, the gameplay is a mix of the farming found in the Harvest Moon series and battling. The player must grow and maintain crops and build up their home, and there are also dungeons to battle and befriend monsters in. The stamina of your character still depends on the meter of rune points, and once it is depleted it will start draining the meter of health points. 

The player will marry a potential girl in the town and have child with her, the gender of the child will be of the player's choosing. Unlike the Harvest Moon games, the player will then continue playing as the child which is an integral part of the game's plot. At the point the goal of the game is to build a school, a goal left behind by Kyle one night when he left home.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory 3 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rune Factory 3 : A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<desc>In Rune Factory 3 the player, Micah by default, is an amnesiac who wanders into the town of Sharance and is discovered by a girl named Shara. Micah is a half human, half monster who can shift between human and wooly forms. 

Like in the other Rune Factory games, the gameplay is a mix of the farming found in the Harvest Moon series and battling. The player must grow and maintain crops and build up their home, and there are also dungeons to battle and befriend monsters in. The stamina of your character still depends on the meter of rune points, and once it is depleted it will start draining the meter of health points. 

New features this time around include dynamic schedules for NPCs, the ability for NPC villagers to accompany players into dungeons and multiplayer with the ability to play dungeons with up to two other players.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>2-3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scribblenauts (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).zip</path>
		<name>Scribblenauts</name>
		<desc>Scribblenauts is a side-scrolling action game based on puzzles. The goal is to have the character Maxwell overcome obstacles by summoning objects based on a dictionary of more than 20.000 words, partly based on the concept of the real-life game Mad Libs. This is done by writing an object's name on the touchscreen, letter by letter. When the word is recognized, the object spawns in the world, where it can be manipulated or act on its own. This leads to an endless amount of possibilities to progress through the game. For instance, when an item needs to be retrieved from a tree, you could summon a ladder to get it out, a football to hit it, or just a helicopter or an albatross to fly over there. There are also more bizarre examples, such as summoning a time machine, going back in time to fetch a dinosaur egg, make it hatch and then use it in the future to defeat an army of robot zombies. The list also includes weapons, historical people, and even references to popular cultures and internet memes. Profanity and trademarked objects are not recognized. There is also a spelling checker included to offer suggestions.

This game is a logical sequel to the gameplay mechanics of Drawn to Life, an earlier title by 5TH Cell, relying on the same concept of emergent gameplay, where the actual game is more of a toolbox, shaped through the player's interaction and different in each session. During the game Maxwell needs to collect starites. To do this, two to four objects are often summoned at the same time. There are general, slow puzzle levels, but also faster action levels filled with enemies, platforms, switches and traps. Often, the summoned objects and characters need to interact with each other. Players can earn "merits" for not using weapons in a level for instance and finding a more creative approach. When a level is completed, a silver star is awarded and the Free Play mode for the level is unlocked. When the level is then completed three more times, using a different approach each time, a gold star is provided.

By solving puzzles, Ollars are awarded, the game's currency. It can be exchanged for different avatars or visual changes. The game includes a level editor and support for Wi-Fi to share the levels. The existing levels can also be edited and the way certain summoned objects interact with each other can also be modified.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>5th Cell Media</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor</name>
		<desc>Devil Survivor is set in modern-day Tokyo and follows a 17-year-old student and his friends, who see an outbreak of demons with some of them becoming their allies. The Protagonist also finds he has the ability to see a person's remaining lifespan and decides to work to avoid as many deaths as possible. Devil Survivor is a tactical role-playing video game where the player and computer control a number of squads composed of one leader and two supporting characters. Between combat, the player can explore several districts in Tokyo to either advance the plot by speaking to specific characters, discover new information, or take part in "free battles". The narrative can branch in multiple ways that result in different endings, which depend upon the player's decisions during critical moments throughout the story.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor 2</name>
		<desc>When a new website that shows the manner of people's deaths in advance makes the rounds amongst Japanese high schoolers, a trio of students is shocked to witness their own deaths in a terrible subway accident just minutes away. They narrowly escape the carnage, only to find themselves in a worse situation--facing otherworldly demons. Desperate to survive, they fend off the demons and flee, but the destruction at the station is only the beginning...</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20120228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ghostlight</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Strange Journey (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei : Strange Journey</name>
		<desc>SMT:Strange Journey is the 4th official Shin Megami Tensei game of the series.It departs from the usual urban Japan setting,and takes place in the future,in Antarctica.It is more sci-fi,with the main protagonist wearing a 'Demonica' suit,which allows for the use of apps throughout the game.You also have guns,swords,and armor that you can acquire and use throughout the game</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solatorobo - Red the Hunter (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (NDSi Enhanced).zip</path>
		<name>SolatoRobo : Red the Hunter</name>
		<desc>Get ready to suspend reality and be brought into a world of floating islands where personal robots are a necessity and pirates and vicious monsters roam the skies. You'll see many dogs and cats along the way, but don't expect your furry friends to be on all fours – they're anthropomorphs. With his cigarette-like bone sticking out of his mouth, Red Savarin, an overconfident teenager, and his specialized robot Dahak have made a name for themselves by taking on odd jobs. Red's curiosity gets the best of him when he comes across a mysterious medallion. Ruh-oh, strange artifacts? This can't be going anywhere good. But before Red runs off with the medallion, he comes across Elh, a sullen, enigmatic creature who shares an unknown link with the medallion for Red to uncover.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CyberConnect2</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush</name>
		<desc>Sonic's first outing on the Nintendo DS system features action in two screens with a story featuring Sonic getting involved in another one of Dr. Eggman's evil plots. A mysterious Emerald is left behind by Dr. Eggman, but an unfamiliar character makes off with it before Sonic can investigate! Sonic gives chase, and thus the adventure begins. Playable characters in the game are Sonic the Hedgehog and new character Blaze the Cat. Appearances from other characters include Miles "Tails" Prower, Amy Rose, Cream the Rabbit, and Knuckles the Echidna. Each playable character has four moves as well as a variety of "Trick actions" which, when performed, will raise your Tension Gauge. Filling the gauge allows you to do a Boost which will propel Sonic or Blaze at a high speed across the ground or along the air to defeat enemies or move certain blocks.There are 14 levels that play out over both the top and bottom DS screens, giving you a bigger view of your surroundings. You will race through the levels collecting rings, using "gimmicks" such as bungee ropes and giant waterwheels, performing tricks, collecting power-ups, and defeating enemies. When you beat each level, or "act", you will face a Boss Act which is played out over the top screen in 3D. In addition to these levels, there are Special Stages. These are played on the touch screen, and unlike the rest of the game, feature control with the stylus. Upon completion of the game, Time Attack mode will be available. In it, you play levels/boss acts for the best time record. Battle Play is a multiplayer mode in which two players compete to finish a level first. It can be played over single-card download or multi-card wireless.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush Adventure (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<desc>While flying in their plane across the ocean, looking for a strange energy source, Sonic and Tails' plane is struck by lightning!  They plunge into the murky depths of the ocean...and awaken on a small island.  A local, a raccoon named Marine, informs them that they are on Southern Island.  With Marine and Tails' help, Sonic sets about to explore the nearby islands.

Sonic Rush Adventure is a side-scrolling adventure game, and the sequel to Sonic Rush.  Sonic's goal through these platform levels is to zip through as quickly as possible.  By pressing the B Button while in the air, Sonic can increase his Tension Gauge by performing aerial tricks. Pressing Y uses a Super Boost, which will allow him to plow through anything in his path at amazing speed, but drains the Tension Gauge.

When Sonic reaches the treasure chest at the end of each level, he will be given a material that can be used for construction of ships and other devices.  At first, Sonic is stranded on Southern Island, but after the construction of the waterbike, he can travel to other islands and explore them.  Similar to The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass, the player must plot a path to the next island using the stylus, and then provide limited control over the ship as it travels.  However, Sonic has different ships, each of which are notably different from Link's steamboat.

Sonic Rush Adventure also features a Battle Mode, where players can either play locally with a friend, or across the world through Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.  Players can take each other on in a one-on-one race through various levels as each player aims to get to the end first.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Bubbles (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).zip</path>
		<name>Soul Bubbles</name>
		<desc>Soul Bubbles is very similar to Bubble Ghost and requires the player to save lost Spirits by transporting them in bubbles to the exit of each level.

The player takes over the role of a Spirit Herder who is tasked with ferrying souls to the underworld. To move the Spirits and keep them relatively save, they need to be be enclosed in soup bubbles. The Spirit Herder then can blow those bubbles through the level, deflate them if they are too big and even cut them into two bubbles and rejoin them later when required. If a bubble bursts, the Spirit will slowly suffocate and eventually die if the player can't draw a new bubble around it fast enough.

But the way to the Gateway Cube isn't an easy one and it's not just as simple as blowing the bubbles from start to finish in the 40 levels. Besides the natural dangers in form of rocks, plants or hungry critters that all destroy the bubble, there are also environment puzzles waiting to be solved like activating a switch which requires a big bubble. There is also Star Dust and so-called Calabash waiting to be collected. While the Star Dust will increase the light emitted by the Spirits and can be collected by simply drawing a new bubble around it, the Calabashs are well hidden but once the player found them all, he will unlock the eighth World called Agartha, the Land of the Dead.

To help with the search, the Spirits will change their shape to heart if a Calabash is near or turn into yellow triangles if there is imminent danger.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20080701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mekensleep</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Dodgeball Brawlers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Dodgeball Brawlers</name>
		<desc>Super Dodgeball Brawlers is a remake of the classic dodgeball sports NES title with characters that resembles those from River City Ransom and Double Dragon.

The original mode still exists, but now has new rules that allow punching, kicking and using weapons against the opposing team.  There is a create-a-character option as well.

There are also over a hundred special attacks that can be used against opponents such as Cactus Attack, Panda Shot and Spear to name a few. The new Super Gauge System, when filled, can be given to a player on the court to boosts stats or unleash an "Instant Kill" against an opponent.

Friends can go head-to-head against a friend or even join up against eight people using Wi-Fi.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20080527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aksys Games</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Dodgeball</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<desc>Mario, Luigi, and Wario have all gone to the Mushroom Palace for some of Princess Peach's famous home made cake. However, when they don't return its up to the heroic dino Yoshi to find out what's wrong.

In this portable remake of the original Super Mario 64 You' are able to play as different characters from the Mario franchise. Wario, Yoshi, Luigi, and of course Mario. Each character has different abilities to be made use of during the games expanded quest. 

The game now features 150 Stars to collect up from the previous 120, new stages with new bosses, changes to old stages and bosses, and a multiplayer in which player compete to get the most stars.

The game also includes over two dozen mini games that make use of both screens and the touch pad.

The DS touch screen can be used to mimic analog control.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Princess Peach (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Princess Peach</name>
		<desc>For once, Bowser has changed his tactics. Instead of grabbing the Princess every chance he gets, he's gone straight to the source of all his problems this time around. The two people who always get in his way and halt his chances of owning Mushroom Kingdom all himself. Mario and Luigi are suddenly whisked away, and only one person can save them...

Princess Peach, always the one in distress, will use all her unique abilities and items to travel the length of the Kingdom to save her heroes. Her main attack uses a parasol on enemies, which can also double as the perfect way to float down from the heights. 

Princess Peachs' emotions will also come into play. Make her cry to drench enemies or help plants grow to reach higher ground, meanwhile her happy singing can distract many foes and open up further areas.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Scribblenauts (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).zip</path>
		<name>Super Scribblenauts</name>
		<desc>Super Scribblenauts for Nintendo DS expands the innovative elements from the award-winning first title with inventive new features, including an adjectives system and upgraded controls to create an incredibly fresh and entertaining gameplay experience. Created and developed by 5TH Cell, players use the stylus and touch screen along with their imagination to help Maxwell, the game's hero, solve robust puzzles and challenges in redesigned levels to acquire the ?Starite.?

In Super Scribblenauts, players now have the ability to write any object that comes to mind and modify it in any way they desire, using adjectives to reach the goal in each level. Adjectives can change the color, size, elements, behaviors and many other aspects of the object they are describing. Multiple adjectives can be combined together to produce incredibly creative objects, allowing the player's imagination to run wild for a truly unique and individualistic experience.

Features

? Brand New Levels: Experience 120 brand new, in-depth levels that include task such as finding a cure for the plague, populating an office or identifying animals with shells.
? All-New Adjectives System: Create a shy green polar bear or an angry zombie pear! 10,000+ adjectives reflect real life behaviors, personalities and characteristics when applied to objects.
? Multi Layered Hints: Just can't figure that puzzle out? Purchase more explicit hints at a decreasing Ollar cost over time.
? Universal Feedback System: Visualize progress throughout each level! Relevant objects summoned get a thumb up, while irrelevant objects get a thumb down.
? Updated Dictionary: Summon more than 800 all-new, customizable objects to solve puzzles and earn Starites.
? New Control Schemes: Control Maxwell with the D-pad or with updated and more precise new Stylus controls! Weight, buoyancy, friction have all been reworked to make objects interact better to the player's input and reflect any adjective that is applied to an object.
? New Level Editor: Create both puzzle and action levels to build your very own custom playground. The unique new template system allows players to create all kinds of objectives for their levels with ease.

? Innovative UI: An exciting new UI gives players more control over gameplay, with more detail on how to navigate through new levels in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20101012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>5th Cell Media</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris DS</name>
		<desc>At its base, Tetris DS is the same Tetris gameplay that's been around for years: rotate and arrange Tetriminos to create full lines and make them disappear.  However, it also has a style very different from earlier Tetris games, new play modes, and online play.

Graphically and aurally, Tetris DS is based on classic NES games.  A portion of the graphics are sprites directly ripped from Mario Bros., Super Mario Bros., Super Mario Bros. 3, Donkey Kong, Balloon Fight, Metroid, Yoshi's Cookie, and The Legend of Zelda.  Remixes of music from these games are also used.

Standard mode includes the standard endless play option, the standard "get 25 lines to win" option, and the standard versus mode where clearing multiple lines at once adds lines to the bottom of your opponents' well.

Push mode is a versus game with a twist.  The player's moves and pieces are shown on the top screen, while the opponent's are on the bottom screen, both with gravity moving towards the center.  Instead of multiple line clears adding extra lines to the bottom of your opponent's well, though, the center is pushed towards their end, giving them a smaller play area.  Push back and forth until one side loses.

Touch mode presents you with a tall uneven stack of large Tetriminos.  The goal is to nudge or rotate them by dragging or tapping on the touch screen to create full lines and eventually clear the stack.

Puzzle mode offers 200 Tetris scenarios and presents you with a number of pieces.  You choose the order and rotation of the pieces to try and empty the well.

Mission mode gives you specific goals like "Use a square block to clear a line" or "Clear 3 lines with an L piece".  Finish the mission and you'll be given another.  Don't finish the mission and several rows of random blocks will be added to the bottom of the well before being given another mission.

Catch mode has the Tetriminos falling without direct player control.  Instead, the player controls a moving core of blocks which can rotate as a whole, as well as latch on to the falling Tetriminos.  The goal is to create a square of at least 4x4, causing an explosion which keeps the size of your core small.  Lose by allowing your core to get too large, or by losing enough energy; which occurs when you allow a Tetrimino to scroll past the bottom of the screen, your rotating core smacks into and destroys a Tetrimino, or you hit a falling enemy.

Multiplayer Standard, Mission, and Push modes can be played locally using one copy of Tetris DS.  Mission allows for up to 10 players competing for a high score.  Standard allows for up to 10 players, and has an option for Mario Kart-like items to aid you or harm your enemies.  Push mode remains a one-on-one experience.  With Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, you can play a two-player Standard game without items, a four-player Standard game with items, or a two-player Push mode game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle / Fall</genre>
		<players>1-10</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's American Sk8land</name>
		<desc>The portable addition of Tony Hawk's latest skating craze (American Wasteland) provide an altogether different experience, especially in terms of the visual presentation.

Pushing aside realism, Sk8land goes with a cel-shaded atmosphere, where the same gameplay mechanics of skaing around each park completing objectives and challenges are as addictive as always.

Nintendo DS players will also take Sk8land online through the wi-fi mode, along with touch screen controls. GBA players aren't left behind either, with an updated create-a-park and skater modes and multiplayer to boot.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trauma Center - Under the Knife 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Trauma Center : Under the Knife 2</name>
		<desc>GUILT is no more. Dr. Derek Stiles and Nurse Angie Thompson faced humanity's greatest threat and triumphed. Now, in the aftermath, they find themselves in unknown territory, forced to deal with the disastrous consequences of the killer virus. Join them as they scramble to address questions left unanswered and put an end to the mystery behind the disease.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vanguard</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarioWare - D.I.Y. (USA).zip</path>
		<name>WarioWare D.I.Y.</name>
		<desc>This game, which puts the concept of user-generated content on center stage, allows players to design their own micro-games from scratch. Every element, such as the characters, the environment, the actions and even the purpose of the micro-game itself, is controlled entirely by the player. Players will then be able to share their completed micro-games with other WarioWare D.I.Y. owners.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarioWare - Touched! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>WarioWare : Touched!</name>
		<desc>Wario makes his debut on the Nintendo DS with hundreds of all-new minigames. Now you must complete your goals by using the touch screen and a stylus. Tap, scratch, and rub your stylus on the touch screen to play minigames that have you do everything from milking a cow and drawing a mustache to hurling stars at evil ninjas. You can even play some minigames by blowing into the DS's built-in microphone. The more minigames you clear, the more characters and items you unlock.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Ends with You, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The World Ends With You</name>
		<desc>The World Ends With You is an action-RPG that puts players in the role of Neku Sakuraba, a sullen, loner of a teenager who wakes up to find himself in modern day Shibuya, Japan, with no memory of how he got there and a ticking clock in his hand that tells him to complete the mission... or face erasure.

Neku and his partner Shiki Misaki find themselves as "Players" in a game that lasts seven days.  Each day, players are given various missions to perform by the "Reapers" within a certain time limit, or be erased from existence.

Players use collectible pins to amplify their combat powers against "The Noise", animal-like creatures which can corrupt the people and environment around them.  Each pin is activated in a different manner, from tapping the touchscreen, making sweeping motions with the stylus, or even blowing into the DS microphone.  Neku fights on the lower screen of the DS, while his partner fights on the upper screen.  Their combat styles are different, but can be combined to form more powerful attacks.  

Players can purchase clothing to increase the effectiveness of their attacks, and gain PP points to enhance their pin abilities.  PP is usally gained through combat, but can also be gained by coming into wi-fi contact with another person's DS.

There is also a wi-fi mini-game called "Ten Pin Slammer", where players can use one pin at a time to knock the other players' pins off the gameboard.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20080422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
